georgehotz: hellooo
EbeneezerPrime: what's up?
toolegit2quit_: no mic?
HaVoCPanda69: yo live
washedeveloper: yo
EbeneezerPrime: can't hear anything, man
toolegit2quit_: here we go
GenericUsernameBro: wuddup
toolegit2quit_: sound
fafws321: Yo afk streamer?
washedeveloper: no sound
archiveutility: George why you gotta stream I just was about to sleep
dvdutch: Is there a repo for the chess engine u wrote?
davidbarreroo: New crip?
filipeoliveiraa: good morning
EbeneezerPrime: loud and clear
washedeveloper: bzzz
moizai: good morning!!
gagehelton: You rule, keep crushing.
toolegit2quit_: are you back on the east coast?
jiggliepuff1: YO George I’m from the town you grew up in
k_o_r_a_l: Приветики
efiggs: Whaddup
foti_kasparov: yo yo
kklisura: Hi George
mkdrmnd: Real European Hours
ogrockefeller: The Hotz Father
warpoit: top of the morning everyone
borang: good morning
TheXtremePerson: Hahaha
alexmchugh: jeez people get in here fast
zeroalligator: Good morning George
ThePepe3012: Are comma offices closed?
foti_kasparov: Apologize Video
GenericUsernameBro: lol
tdubey: inflammatory + face diaper, nice
Descrout: is george anti-masker Kappa ?
quelsarprime: apology accepted. big pp
ogrockefeller: Lolz
TheXtremePerson: Agreed
HaVoCPanda69: lmao on the website i clicked on the science is clear and it lead me back to politics
JohnnyThe_Hobo: georgeee <3
badpartyhouse: yeeee
DrewHintz: need to replace that propaganda with references to scientific studies.
jamieemb_: The government in Scotland have mandated that masks are required in public. A friend send this yesterday https://royalsociety.org/-/media/policy/projects/set-c/set-c-facemasks.pdf?la=en-GB&hash=A22A87CB28F7D6AD9BD93BBCBFC2BB24
YouvanYakk: Not a viewpoint but a fact LULW
efiggs: I hear schools are going to open up with the use of masks... lol
badpartyhouse: no more night streams?
foti_kasparov: Is anybody in the chat with covid?
fury766: Hello George Hotz! I live in Korea and my dream is a programmer! And I respect you!!
k_o_r_a_l: Че там у п3ндосов ща?
l_mbert: hi @everyone!
efiggs: Hospitals aren’t actually full.. it’s a lis
taquitobandito_1: Finally! I catch one live
k_o_r_a_l: Оппа
levinson2504: @foti_kasparov im against covid
quelsarprime: lost close friend to covid last month
breezyronster2: !uptime
badpartyhouse: George can you share via set up?
badpartyhouse: vim
mimagind: There is no need for a formal study. Countries where masks are culturally accepted had much lower rate of transmission. QED
MrJeff_: I find it funny the WHO says they're not effectvie and now our Gov says they do. So.... yeah its all fun and games.
alexmchugh: bro write a sim
toolegit2quit_: @georgehotz what is the cost of wearing a mask vs potential gain?
dvdutch: vim
foti_kasparov: @levinson2504 good for you
neel421997: j
washedeveloper: there may not be marginal benefits but I think it gives people a sense of security, which is what some people need.
efiggs: No one gave a fuck when people dies of strokes and heart attacks... why should we care about covid deaths?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: @georgehotz whats would you say if something use this as evidence? https://www.insider.com/microbiologist-shows-how-a-mask-catches-droplets-coronavirus-2020-7
roibeardo: cloth not porous? lot of ppl making masks from tshirts...thought tshirts wanted to let air in, by design! NotLikeThis
32bitrobo: Have a great day today brother
neel421997: opinion on the donotpay startup? they just brought out self cancelling temporary credit cards!
Tal_X_Tal: yo
YouvanYakk: Seatbelts?
alexmchugh: what are the negative effects of mandating the use?
jamieemb_: Even the evidence showing the effectiveness of masks, specifically state that it's just medical masks, not cloth
ro6m: What about "encouraged"?
32bitrobo: have you Nicholas Nassims Medium post about evidence for masks?
Kalland: but it is a math game. one virus particle does not equal you are infected. The more you are exposed to the larger chance you get effected.
mkdrmnd: @mimagind Cultural adherence to mask wearing is associated with adherence to social distancing
toolegit2quit_: Here in Belgium you will get a 250EUR fine for not wearing a mask inside a shop
efiggs: We should put as much effort into heart attacks and strokes as we do covid
mimagind: Why does mandating or banning something trivial must have the same threshold as mandating or banning something important?
Tal_X_Tal: i c
mannekchin: yo
abe8k: really nice book
YouvanYakk: Rational Andy
Descrout: isn't the point of using masks not protecting yourself but other people ?
allrz: PJSalt
moizai: zoom in pls
Tal_X_Tal: YouvanYakk LUL
anguscupcake: people just don't exercise or eat healthy
seldard: Isn't more rational to mandate masks even if they are not that effective since the inpact on wearing a mask and not being effective is less than not wearing them and them being effective?
pranav1198: zoom in
Tal_X_Tal: "fake news"
mannekchin: copy cats
dempseytr: Whats up my man
maxschneider96: what if cloth masks or surgical masks consisted of multiple functional layers? that could make a difference, innit? Are there any corresponding studies?
neel421997: opinion on the donotpay startup? they just brought out self cancelling temporary credit cards!
numbaeon: Skewed towards preventable death
pioterexe: my fav streamer hello
lesserthangood: whats ur opinion on climate change
zak_abdou: Hi, can you please give your personal advice how to learn and be good at binarary exploit how should a start what is your personal advice im asking because your are good on it
abe8k: evidence is clear though
Ceono: NotLikeThis
snowbola: oh no he's still at it
ro6m: is there valid science/math for intelligent betting before that procedure is carried out?
Koduck007: hey bro
k_o_r_a_l: Sup dude we love from РОССИЯ
mannekchin: drug overdoses is lower than what i thought
k_o_r_a_l: U
Tal_X_Tal: i pray to the homie 2 pac
pierzor: Is it me or is the audio fucked up?
utahjazz777: Less wrong is awesome. Just saw the last few seconds. Did George recommend Yudkowsky's book?
mannekchin: when will comma become a public company? TriHard
tallestmollusk: Can we go back to the log growth thing? Why does the internal growth pattern matter for the likelihood of getting sick with/without a mask?
mimagind: @mkdrmnd Mask wearing cultures are in crowded countries which will correlate with many collectivistic traits like trust in government authority and fear of contagious infections.
Koduck007: beliefs are hard to change sadly
javiercmh: metal god, that sounds so metal
k_o_r_a_l: Передай привет Роме плиз чел
32bitrobo: "The propagandist's purpose is to make one set of people forget that certain other sets of people are human." - Aldous Huxley
Tal_X_Tal: we live in a post truth world dude haHAA
b2kemann: you can't use logic to justify logic, read godels incompleteness theorem
drkolenklow: truth is delusion, logic gets disillusioned when politics and religion are combined
Koduck007: logic squad PorscheWIN
k_o_r_a_l: Передай привет 6tango2mango
yamesboard: just to clarify why you should use medical cartridges from 3M, when the filtering membrane gets wet such by other people's spit when talking , the filtering is inhibited. Therefore, the medical filters has a protective plastic shell. See this rundown of 3M filters by (nerd) australian doctor.
bichid69: lol this chart is fucking hilarious
HaVoCPanda69: faith is stupid, faith is lack of logic
yamesboard: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FigbakqJRZw
basement199: newsflash...you are going to die.
yungtoad1: sounds like a fun party lmfao
k_o_r_a_l: Передай привет Соне плез
pioterexe: is k e y b o a r d word already banned?
iwicdti: everything is a scam
ro6m: It's not automatic that faith is less environmentally fit everywhere, under all circumstances, at all times.
gouzzz: !uptime
maxschneider96: do u mean, u want ur body to live forever or do u want to preserve ur consciousness somehow?
zer0gap: you still believe in corona?
dalvasorsali: dalvasorsali subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 3 months! welcome back
ghostmars919: Hi George :)
ro6m: That in itself is an assumption. Probably not even in the realm of provability.
Einnod: !keyboarf
voodoorama: drinking cofee?
pierzor: !keyboarf
tdubey: the boxer visual was pretty good though...
drkolenklow: see i am convinced thanks for addressing me
bichid69: can we go back to the causes of death vs google vs media chart? it's so fucking funy
kklisura: Glad you shared that with us. Respect.
32bitrobo: Yeah, but now a days questioning the popculture consensus is enough to be cancelled
b2kemann: why not black background on terminal?
iwicdti: Life is suffering. Why do you want to live forever?
ro6m: https://ourworldindata.org/does-the-news-reflect-what-we-die-from
neel421997: opinion on the donotpay startup? they just brought out self cancelling temporary credit cards! what do you feel is the legality to it?
mimagind: The scientific method is hard to apply in practice to human subjects in their natural habitat.
musashhhi: this paper is being pushed by the news now about cloth masks https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/69/wr/mm6928e2.htm
IWearATinFoilHat: IWearATinFoilHat subscribed with Twitch Prime.
bichid69: why instagram but not facebook?
Kmerck313: That’s power
c0mputable: can you name a few ways to make money?
Skillath: Wise words
c0mputable: online
HaVoCPanda69: instagram live lol
JohnnyThe_Hobo: 1 million followers 2020
neel421997: SeemsGood
lesserthangood: lol he doesnt use twitter but uses instagram
32bitrobo: You think blockchain is the solution to pseudonymous work?
b2kemann: zuckerberg got your back
pranav1198: still not verified xD
linearpup: Build P2P streaming service using PeerJs!
Kmerck313: Only fans
toolegit2quit_: @georgehotz what about SSC?
iwicdti: G.O.A.T
mimagind: Not everyone is genius like yourself, most of us mediocre mortals can easily be cancelled.
JohnnyThe_Hobo: you never post on instagram tho
soiax_: they allow MASK DENIERS???
borang: oh the cool SF swing
soiax_: LUL
goeo_: "i'm not on facebook" "come to my instagram"
seesdeadpeeps: Five GeoHoTz
k_o_r_a_l: А как донатить
ZOLD1ER: bitconnect?
Rafabld1996: needs more yatchs and girls
bichid69: what do you think of onlyfans?
HawkMonk: monkaS
B1_Renekton: i just scraped all of SSC from archive.org, will host on Github soon
neel421997: opinion on the donotpay startup? they just brought out self cancelling temporary credit cards! what do you feel is the legality to it?
lesserthangood: money laundering TriHard
C3r0C3r0C3r0: what's your insta uname?
kklisura: Does LBRY support live streaming?
joshperri: Links own wiki article, 9 of 10 pics selfies
Skilion1: what did we came up with yesterday?
Digital_donger: new wave PogChamp
WhispyHerc: the fact that twitch can just take someones entire lively hood without disclosed reason is just ethically fucked up
Rafabld1996: god bless ethereum
steventwtch: I heard it had to do something with an old rock, stone
kornez: yo geohot and chat HeyGuys
snwlol: hewooo :3 @kornez
linearpup: Linode
marschr: federated networks?
eaterenrgy: !uptime
bichid69: can we not just do p2p?
neoptomelus: good side hustles for plebs?
lesserthangood: @neoptomelus drug dealing
WhispyHerc: @georgehotz what are your thoughts on the rumors of tik tok getting shut down because of "extreme data collection"? do you think the allegations are real in terms of the data farming
neoptomelus: @lesserthangood Sadge
quinquanonagintilliard: get some vitamin D
bichid69: tik tok fucking suck anyway
snwlol: is George, dare I say, /ourguy/ ?
NilsIRL: what do you think of peertube?
sadokaah: @georgehotz monopolies are toxic, if twitch would have a comparable contender the streaming industry would change in a good way I think
k_o_r_a_l: Передай привет Алексею Станкевичу
joshperri: Algorithms are the means of production in the Information Age.
linearpup: What are your thoughts on Richard Stallman issue?
b2kemann: 70%
lesserthangood: peertube is just software its nothing
HaVoCPanda69: what about LBRY
s3menthr0w3r: looks garbage
joshperri: They take too much capital to create
codingquark: Discovery on peertube is hard, and servers still have to be paid for.
eaterenrgy: how do you get banned from github?
Pepa489: @HaVoCPanda69 ^^
leuza0: @sadokaah but which platform woud be a contender? There is always one trying but none succeed
codingquark: It is like the mastodon picturer
dvush: They can ban you on domain level, as they did with daily s. That’s creepy
B1_Renekton: Maybe we will have to make a a decentralized internet like in Silicon Valley TV series
snwlol: GitHub has contract with ICE, true?
roibeardo: tnx for pointing me to rationality ebook. reading it now...
sk4y__: gitlab and github both are shit
kornez: prolly indian IP pool was his problem LUL
quinquanonagintilliard: have a mirror on your local repo via gittea
oxtuq: yoo, what's going on?
Skilion1: @georgehotz can you not bang on the table? We hear it amplified
ro6m: GNU Satellite Constellation bro
mrr08040: mrr08040 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
s3menthr0w3r: lol wanna be Richard Hendricks
ro6m: Internet eterna
sadokaah: @leuza0 youtube is slowly growing but ideally something new would come up, hard to do that at the moment
MrJeff_: bebo....
drkolenklow: google SEO for gitlab is poor - just an observation
eaterenrgy: Intel LUL
言語サム一語言山姆: I feel like I gotta back up all my own stuff, but I'm just a paranoid
maxschneider96: Do u think a platform that has an algorithm that promotes truth would be competitive to other platforms that fully rely on digital marketing?
goeo_: i was very surprised about nintendo's age
Reelix: ... Who remembers Yahoo? o_O Am I that old?
Digital_donger: Yahoo! FeelsBadMan
snwlol: I remember PogChamp
zelkh9: george out here rediscovering company intranets LUL
ck1956: taboo the goat
soiax_: who will remember comma.ai? :P
tdubey: Gitlab is selfhosted or hosted by them
tjobremannen: @Reelix yes ur old Kappa
bichid69: gitlab fucking sucks
synthblade7080: isnt intel untouchable<
linearpup: Gerrit is great
ro6m: gitlab is developed on SVN in Perl
drkolenklow: I meant your projects on gitlab not the gitlab website itself
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: Everything is happening faster and faster now, everything will be completely different in 50 years
sk4y__: sourcehut.org look at that
Reelix: What next - Do people remember AskJeeves? :p
codingquark: The concepts in Accelerando are impressive.
neoptomelus: what type of tech companies do you think can disrupt the current leaders?
codingquark: Yes
bichid69: What do you think of GPT-3?
ck1956: lol
言語サム一語言山姆: if you want it done right ..
drkolenklow: sifive seems interesting
HaVoCPanda69: just wait for ARM lol
RapidEU: What do u think of the new DNS vulnerability that was just published?
SurajkAxim: Nvidia is the future?
drkolenklow: sifive is alacart for risc v processors
marschr: buy intel put LOL
言語サム一語言山姆: do you think the intel me stuff is concerning or just conspiracy
Kalland: we use gitlab at work. it has lots of nice features. but i would say github is better. somehow gitlab struggles with large diffs.
bichid69: intel gonna go boom
lesserthangood: i upload screenshots of my code to redtube to archive it
deva73: do you know about jio inia
B1_Renekton: ruqqus and .win is trying to compete with reddit
MrJeff_: yep
anguscupcake: SELL
RapidEU: lol
HaVoCPanda69: LUL
programmingmouse: yeah
Digital_donger: nearly Jebaited
Warbayx: he knew LUL
sadokaah: Jebaited
stupac62: gitlab is great. integrated ci pipeline
s3menthr0w3r: lolll
neoptomelus: Jebaited
yungtoad1: beeg.com
Koduck007: dodged
bichid69: hahahaha
Pepa489: LULW
Koduck007: LOL
snwlol: @deva73 Jio India is trash is what I know
言語サム一語言山姆: it's their management engine on their CPUs, security flaws
Koduck007: I love Product
BurntOut157: hey George, long time no see
snwlol: coonsooom
RapidEU: @lesserthangood almost LOL
Koduck007: Product helped me become more efficient
codingquark: https://gogs.io/ self hosted git service
bichid69: is ML dead?
neel421997: @snwlol even if jio is trash, it is a very very cheap option to it's competitors and they are slowly monopolizing the market
RapidEU: Really wondering his is your self driving car startup going?
optimodev: "just dont have a facebook account" ... " check out my instagram account"
snwlol: @neel421997 True.
smurfd0: https://d.tube/ decentralized youtube alternative
optimodev: instagram /is/ faceobok no?
quinquanonagintilliard: https://matrix.org/
jeffbezos6: ni hao george, from china!
linearpup: Gerrit is also pretty good: https://www.gerritcodereview.com/
codingquark: Riot recently renamed to Elements (matrix.org follow up)
JohnnyThe_Hobo: witches? monkaS
言語サム一語言山姆: hey China :)
zak_abdou: Why you dont make courses ?
ro6m: People need ways to impose proportionate costs on each other.
thealtchemist: silver looks like a good buy
blazelp1: Yooo
quinquanonagintilliard: Gerrit ui is confusing, but I head it's pretty powerful
bichid69: @zak_abdou are you fucking kidding bro
codingquark: Check https://gogs.io
neoptomelus: KKona Clap
codingquark: Minimal web ui
vay_man: hey
whit_314: Chat, witches are a new term to me. What does George mean by 'witches' in this context?
oxtuq: @thealtchemist yeah, i've been buying it for the last two years.
neel421997: @snwlol also, jio, reliance has the Indian population with them. And when 1.3 billion are with you, you surely are gonna grow. I honestly feel Mukesh Ambani, the pace at which he is going could become the first trillionaire, if he plays his cards right
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: @georgehotz I think they should allow everything as long as it is not illegal, spam etc
snwlol: fuckin libtards with their politics in my tech, I just wanna code KKona
yungtoad1: FUCK CONDE NAST
bichid69: reddit started doing DMCA takedowns which sucks
marschr: mops?
PhosphoricAcid: clowns :)
whit_314: Ahh, ok.
Rafabld1996: PrideStrong Cancel George
blconciuness: what r we doing today george?
linearpup: https://www.meta-nomad.net/avoiding-the-global-lobotomy/
B1_Renekton: reddit quarrantined donald for hate against police, and then they removed the reasoning after riots happened
optimodev: instagram is facebook
言語サム一語言山姆: @whit_314 people deemed undesirable
okonofox: doesn't make any sense to get banner from it
whit_314: Thanks.
neoptomelus: wait why did he say intel is gonna tank
qlutoo: users should ban users, not the service itself
vay_man: what are we doing today?
dvush: What do you think about urbit? Can we “host” internet without big tech?
RapidEU: Whats up with your self-driving startup, are u still working on it?
JumpTwiice: LULW
s3menthr0w3r: Check out this cool decentralized recipe database MeatSpinner
neel421997: isn't vimeo a good enough alternative?
whit_314: supremeshrubbery, so people who have been 'witch hunted' from other platforms?
Reelix: He's self Employed - Until he gets all his accounts banned.
optimodev: instagram -is- facebook
言語サム一語言山姆: yup
ro6m: Princes
codingquark: I came to know about urbit from one of these streams :)
jeffbezos6: https://www.reddit.com/r/Kanye/comments/hrhemp/kanye_in_the_house/ #kanye2020
whit_314: Magic, I understand now. Thanks.
Rygaros: @georgehotz seems drdisrespect got banned cause he talked about David icke
b2kemann: i liked his quote on what power is
b2kemann: in that article
bichid69: how about pied piper from silicon valley?
mero_1181: Is this your new home or you are squatting?
okonofox: @rygaros wtf? really?
washedeveloper: @jeffbezos6 Kanye dropped out the race
bichid69: david icke is a fucking troll though
drkolenklow: i saw an interesting webiste, unwoke[dot]hr seems funny in a way. The times we live in.
oxtuq: @washedeveloper no way, really?
vay_man: I am conservative
washedeveloper: yup
言語サム一語言山姆: im convinced icke believes what he says
Reelix: @Rygaros With the recent mass banning of people on multiple social media platforms for disrespect of women, I'm not surprised that someone literally named "disrespect" got caught in the wave :p
oxtuq: damn, was hoping for some epic entertainment.
codingquark: "esoteric jargon" is a good phrase
snwlol: @rygaros so the lizard elite brotherhood got him or something?
washedeveloper: his campaign team made announcement
HovaCarlito: george, did you move? where is the empty kitchen-room?
duncansclarke: postmodernism uses other argumentative strategies beyond just jargon
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: groceries?
duncansclarke: but to be fair it's one of the most jargon-ridden philosophy circles
言語サム一語言山姆: critical theory doesn't have predictive power
ro6m: Winning arguments not= winning
ro6m: It's weird af
vay_man: is this that new os shit?
illdealer: arvo is an os
JumpTwiice: thats some obscure shit
astrocraft23: hello
maxschneider96: looks disgusting
qlutoo: schizo-ism
thealtchemist: Looks like brainfuck + assembly
b2kemann: lool
lzrdkng21: Banned Kappa
0wld3v: B)
Koduck007: indigo children in action lol
言語サム一語言山姆: you wouldn't get it harryb8Sunglassharry
okonofox: is like brainfuck
ro6m: I met some of the Urbit guys. I actually think the obscurity is for filtering most human interest.
oxtuq: lmao
linearpup: Have you read White Noise by Don DeLillo?
codingquark: https://gogs.io/
b2kemann: showoff of brainpower
ro6m: To grow slowly on purpose.
thealtchemist: Difficult to get hacked, when nobody knows the language, hmmm
illdealer: ro6m its a waste of time through obscurity
davidbarreroo: what do you think abut Urbit ?
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: so it's security through obfuscation then
32bitrobo: You have a really high iq i think
JohnnyThe_Hobo: how long until we get into magic?
qlutoo: how is BAP not banned from twitter yet lmao
JumpTwiice: F
J3rwin: F
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: F
RapidEU: f
maxschneider96: F
言語サム一語言山姆: SoonerLater
2Good5You: F
xksteven: F
Epo97: F
soiax_: F
okonofox: f
hi_im_drakster: f
chillguy269: f
ImJ4Gu4R: F
OG_KNOCC_OUT: sodSAD
Digital_donger: they got him :(
programmingmouse: F
DaveSoDave: F
f0xpc: F
JohnnyThe_Hobo: they came after gerge
pioterexe: f
deva73: f
snwlol: F
km1no: f
ImJ4Gu4R: banned?
WuDC: like....?
km1no: got banned
RapidEU: FBI is up to him
illdealer: just refresh
Koduck007: f
paulierco: RIP
grenaderaven: LUL
snwlol: TheIlluminati
dra031cko: F
J3rwin: You are losing frames
vay_man: no joint today?
Koduck007: the fuzz got him
programmingmouse: twitch ban Kappa
Rafabld1996: CANCELED
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: oh you're back
hi_im_drakster: FBI TheIlluminati
wgz90: TheIlluminati they are watching
JohnnyThe_Hobo: they dont want us to know the truth
bichid69: f
JumpTwiice: we back
okonofox: ghahahaha
bichid69: ffff
bichid69: fffff
32bitrobo: cancelled HAHAHA
JumpTwiice: nvm
illdealer: you need starlink internet
bichid69: fff
km1no: f again
soiax_: back
THE_korbi: is anyone else hearing those bumbs whenever he types or touches his desk?
programmingmouse: FBI
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: SIKE
xksteven: we back
bananaconda: was nice to know him
hi_im_drakster: F5
nico_d0t: heloo
qlutoo: comcast, not even once
km1no: FBI at your door
drkolenklow: they have self driving cars but stable internet is still np hard lol.
bichid69: u back motherbitch
ro6m: GNU Satellite Constellation bro
mimagind: Just as it was getting interesting CoolStoryBob
qlutoo: bap book out how long????
lucretius0: thoughts on templeOS ?
roibeardo: too many keywords trggered
snwlol: George, who's behind you?
imgifty: @georgehotz what key -board do you have?
Faceless_Bard: instagram , is that where you put your twitch schedule ? Kappa
davidbarreroo: If you want to life foverer why do you smoke weed ? It can affect to your mental health in long term right ?
imgifty: Kappa
bichid69: what book is thet
codingquark: hah, templeOS is now known because of LTT
BigBurrito_09: Kappa
lucretius0: yeah pretty much
ro6m: haha TempleOS! The only valid appeal to authority.
qlutoo: BAP is modern day nietzsche
codingquark: Okay, gotta read this one
Digital_donger: the amazon reviews LUL
programmingmouse: game of thrones book? Kappa
thealtchemist: Author: Bronze age pervert what???
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: you read too much
JumpTwiice: i dont read books LUL
STuaRTRuLeS: Yo cr00ze!
jamieemb_: have you read mindset by Carol Dweck?
ro6m: b/c Terry was the greatest programmer that ever lived, RIP
snwlol: too much red pill for me
crackmybones: @georgehotz half the people watching you never took calculus or pass college. you def need to say.
maxschneider96: @jamieemb_ nice one, yeah
vay_man: I saw that
davidbarreroo: Favorite book ?
phrixus_bro: college makes it worse not better dude
soiax_: shrinking of grey matter
soiax_: LUL
shaan_razal: hey
jamieemb_: @maxschneider96 one of the most important books i've ever read
jeffbezos6: yay
oxtuq: lmao from the reviews on Amazon: " You will fly through this book if you are not a brainlet soychild who has forgotten that the will is the most powerful tool in the arsenal of the human."
shaan_razal: bug fan
ro6m: All human statements need a few implicit legal disclaimers
codingquark: huh, interesting
jeffbezos6: awesome!
drkolenklow: hahaha oh george , it is so hard to be public these days. I wonder how people like Kabir survived . If he was alive today he would have been in jail :P
crackmybones: it's like a casino gambling slot machines
quinquanonagintilliard: We need to create a new platform to have a constructive discussion, Twitter is not sufficient
vay_man: we think you are on coke
thealtchemist: Only dopamine -> No motivation?
crackmybones: LUL that's me
quelsarprime: sounds like Japanese TV programming
shaan_razal: Kappa Kappa
drkolenklow: Some twitter threads are nice though, naval or chamath
ipo___: Hotz i'm loosing my mind.. can I stay around?
codingquark: Oh damn, so like tunnel focus of caffeine but too much?
ro6m: No negative feedback, shit gets chaotic.
davidbarreroo: Which is you favorite book ?
ebrahim_31: Slo
shaan_razal: CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob BatChest BatChest BatChest BatChest BatChest BatChest BatChest CoolStoryBob BatChest CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob
ebrahim_31: slow slow slow
lucretius0: they are yeah
JumpTwiice: F
dvush: Lots of dopamine = psychosis
OG_KNOCC_OUT: NotLikeThis
rektiwow: f
Descrout: F NotLikeThis
illdealer: is he using wifi?
m_o_r_g_o_t_h: DDOSED
nico_d0t: f
bananaconda: f
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: F
lesserthangood: f
crackmybones: f
dcipko: f
nico_d0t: ff
taxad0: f
nico_d0t: F
num_air: f
snwlol: F
HovaCarlito: for a master hacker, geohotz' internet is hella shit
JumpTwiice: they're on to him monkaS
okonofox: f
nico_d0t: zF
firehawq: How do you start a tweak??????
crackmybones: back?
km1no: f
BurntOut157: f
chillguy269: If you bring down quality of video it comes back
snwlol: TheIlluminati b o i
thealtchemist: Maybe he's ddosing us
lzrdkng21: we back
num_air: back
lucretius0: schizo is more complicated but dopamine is one aspect
sureom: fffff
breadhamandegg: did you move house?
codingquark: ISP no good?
km1no: back
whit_314: You are in America and it's 2020. How can internet still suck.
illdealer: instead of tesla stock, you should invest in a quality internet
ebrahim_31: it dosssssssse
num_air: back again
washedeveloper: rip
O_Dunravin: oh cool, hey George, hey chat HeyGuys
mimagind: Just watch on potato quality and it's fine.
guchiflamingo: why don't you use Linux as your daily driver
okonofox: FBI is watching for u TheIlluminati
linearpup: What is the egress bandwidth?
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: If you talk about a certain peripheral used to input data into the computer, your message gets deleted. It sounds different in NY, was hoping to find out what it is
Stunt3000: stop uploading your github stuff to redtube ^^
davidbarreroo: Favorite book ?
shaan_razal: yoi How to type quckly??
chillguy269: Oh, yikers
snwlol: American Internet KKona
bebytesback: Where are you streaming from, def not the cloud with that connection.
thealtchemist: You did the iphone, you can do the wi-fi haha
mero_1181: Is this your new place?
shaan_razal: *
bananaconda: DDosed
sureom: hacked monkaS
mero_1181: You should invest on internet then
m_o_r_g_o_t_h: linux
b2kemann: close some tabs
ebrahim_31: everybody telecommuting again?
rektiwow: its the isp, its always the isp
ro6m: Hasn't dropped here
yamesboard: just to clarify why you should use medical cartridges from 3M, when the filtering membrane gets wet such by other people's spit when talking , the filtering is inhibited. Therefore, the medical filters has a protective plastic shell. See this rundown of 3M filters by (nerd) Australian doctor: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FigbakqJRZw
linearpup: Comma Bio?
codingquark: Alright, I'll get it too
illdealer: TheIlluminati TheIlluminati TheIlluminati u there fbi
Landepbs: "/fun/corona" nice
32bitrobo: we'll wait bro
Ziv0: that 8k monitor tho
lesserthangood: whats drugs my dealer
drkolenklow: you were saying something about naval
32bitrobo: talk about keyboards now that he's gone
alrealre: walk more softly dude
shaan_razal: How to type Quicky
shaan_razal: ??
lesserthangood: they cancelling Jimmy Kimmel the King of Cancel Culture
shaan_razal: How to type Quicky??
snwlol: cmonBruh
shaan_razal: How to type Quicky
JumpTwiice: @shaan_razal just do it 4Head
alrealre: you are banging the floor
programmingmouse: cmonBruh
lesserthangood: f
Ziv0: lag
m_o_r_g_o_t_h: i also like your mic. pls, lift it from the desk
synthblade7080: @shaan_razal practise
crackmybones: LUL
thealtchemist: yesss tyler ma man
STuaRTRuLeS: illuminati is fictional.
s3menthr0w3r: it's not
thealtchemist: mayb enot
anguscupcake: lmao
JumpTwiice: LUL
Skilion1: @m_o_r_g_o_t_h thank you
lesserthangood: just turn the PC off 4Head
rektiwow: coffe? I thought we drank tea around here
snwlol: LOL!
s3menthr0w3r: sometimes yes but not all of the time noob
jeffbezos6: https://www.reddit.com/r/Kanye/comments/hrhemp/kanye_in_the_house/ BibleThump BibleThump
codingquark: On the topic of alternate internet: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gopher_(protocol)
kornez: just dont listen 4Head
guchiflamingo: why don't you use Linux as your daily driver
breadhamandegg: did you move house?
snwlol: Kappa but kill themselves because of online bullying Kappa
alrealre: Tea has so much Oxalate. Kidney BOOM
STuaRTRuLeS: Coffee is the real deal.
Jski101: Nah Cofefe
crackmybones: @georgehotz the problem is social media is as addictive as drugs are. it's like saying "just don't do drugs 4HEad "
oxtuq: Tea is an afternoon drink. Coffee is for the morning.
programmingmouse: so this a medical stream now xD
drkolenklow: lemon ice tea!
linearpup: Bubble tea
s3menthr0w3r: #uncancelRKelly
whit_314: Gopher? Isn't that from the 1500's?
yamesboard: just to clarify why you should use medical cartridges from 3M, when the filtering membrane gets wet such by other people's spit when talking , the filtering is inhibited. Therefore, the medical filters has a protective plastic shell. See this rundown of 3M filters by (nerd) Australian doctor: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FigbakqJRZw
chillguy269: hot take
HaVoCPanda69: LUL
Skilion1: tea is for when I had too much coffee
ipo___: You have the same curtains as I do.. super black no sunlight edition.
Ziv0: gopher is only good for xxe into rce LUL
Ellsherlock: LUL
whit_314: I've opted out a few years ago.
thealtchemist: What's the overall goal of this series of streams?
linearpup: is comma bio happening?
ipo___: Luckly for facebook new people are born too..
nikhilr14: u been reading mRNA from last stream
yungtoad1: "I've opted out" he comments on twitch
lesserthangood: white youtube DansGame
s3menthr0w3r: @thealtchemist entertainment
jeffbezos6: https://www.reddit.com/r/Kanye/comments/hrhemp/kanye_in_the_house/
codingquark: ha ha
Skilion1: we hear nothing
whit_314: I was just looking for thing to make me angry, keep scratching that rage itch.
lesserthangood: kanye dropped out bro
illdealer: ye2020
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: george why cant we talk about your board of keys? This one isn't your HHKB right? Pls don't ban me bro
rektiwow: @lesserthangood incognito tab i think
ro6m: I'm addicted to Twitter since I have no human contact anymore.
Warbayx: don't follow anyone political on social media and you will be ok
guchiflamingo: NO LINUX?!
sadokaah: @georgehotz what do you think about identity verification on big social networks like facebook or twitter?
crackmybones: kayne never dropped in LUL
O_Dunravin: wut are we coding?
synthblade7080: yes you do :)
mexeroserisback: friendly stream :)
s3menthr0w3r: don't even disrespect kanye
Ziv0: no :)
yungtoad1: yes
OG_KNOCC_OUT: Went for a crown replacement, the dentist had something similar to that
lef_xyz: ez
linearpup: Can't they just cancel Covid-19?
codingquark: Don't get us non-subs mute dudes!
chillguy269: Nancy Regan was ahead of her time
thealtchemist: <3
crackmybones: LUL
RapidEU: How is openpilot going george?
JumpTwiice: Politics ResidentSleeper
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @georgehotz what do you think of $IDEX
lef_xyz: can you link please
32bitrobo: what do think about naval?
yungtoad1: poggers
lesserthangood: saying no to politics is in itself a political statement
言語サム一語言山姆: WutFace
crackmybones: politics is addictive tho 4Head @georgehotz
kornez: @georgehotz link it
anxova: Kappa
Rafabld1996: total state WutFace
xksteven: @georgehotz how do you recommend preparing for comma interview?
s3menthr0w3r: laaaaaame
lef_xyz: https://graymirror.substack.com/p/1-a-general-theory-of-collaboration
neoptomelus: monkaS
madmocro: @georgehotz Off topic: Do you have any tips for CS graduates? I nearly finished my bachelors, and am interested in data science, should I do a masters (like Big Data) or just start getting work experience
snwlol: there's politics in everything George NotLikeThis
shaan_razal: Your a nerd
ipo___: All that matters is rich vs poor
Ziv0: monkaS
Skilion1: r/enlightedcentrism
lesserthangood: @madmocro go to work
phrixus_bro: vry moldbugian
s3menthr0w3r: brah did u used to get your head flushed
crackmybones: just don't engage 4Head
cactusvacuum: Maybe already discussed, but what is the viability of peer to peer replacements of YouTube twitch etc via WebRTC , only need lightweight signaling if you don’t care about turn fallback
whit_314: No war but the class war!
shaan_razal: Doesb he believe in god??
JumpTwiice: 4Head
mexeroserisback: sounds like a guided meditation
drkolenklow: check out kabir bro
hiddenkumquat: thats very doomer
OG_KNOCC_OUT: 4Head
ro6m: You building bro?
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @georgehotz what do you think of $IDEX
drkolenklow: way ahead of his time he was
anguscupcake: ya just find a job, masters doesnt help that much
thealtchemist: Isn't to be detached, being engaged in detachement?
serRLNDT: hey geohot, are you interested at all about the upcoming apple silicon? I know you use a MBP
Ziv0: don't engange cus divorce feeds
32bitrobo: You're my buddha
codingquark: Alright, mRNA
ro6m: The Buddha
O_Dunravin: "Science the shit out of it"
comatross: is this just buddhism?
言語サム一語言山姆: I mean you can avoid the politics, but they can still come for you. the academics were killed in maos China
shaan_razal: what is he coding for??
linearpup: train a wavenet on george's voice
kornez: if you are in your 30s, you have like 15k days of your life left, half of that gonna be wasted of sleep. Imagine wasting energy on politics you have 0 impact on
shaan_razal: VAccine
shaan_razal: ??
illdealer: coronoa
shaan_razal: Damn
snwlol: George is a centrist, so barbeque when?
lesserthangood: the vaccines are already made bro
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: anyone know what keeb he has in NY? Sounds delicious Kreygasm
JohnnyThe_Hobo: new data about moderna vaccine. we are close o getting one by november
madmocro: @lesserthangood any field specifically as CS graduate?
linearpup: HE COUGHED
illdealer: he uses a hhkb
ro6m: Most of us won't out-politic politics, so you need something else.
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: @illdealer It sounds very different here though, not thocky like topre
bichid69: can we do a dettol vaccine?
phil4820: zombies monkaS
shaan_razal: lol
STuaRTRuLeS: @georgehotz how about this ivermectin?
HaroonsLIVE: could someone explain what's going on here?
lef_xyz: have you guys seen foam on github (research tool)
言語サム一語言山姆: ain't nobody kno
HaroonsLIVE: kinda confused what hes doing
shaan_razal: he is coding a corona virus vaccine
HaroonsLIVE: lol
lesserthangood: @madmocro what u mean
O_Dunravin: i'm confirmed anti vaxx after reading a lot of books on the subject, terrain theory > germ theory
s3menthr0w3r: @lef_xyz nah but I shoot foam out of my gitschlong aayyooo Kreygasm
HaroonsLIVE: anti vaxxers NotLikeThis NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
thealtchemist: Did we ever find out if hydroxychloroquine was effective?
illdealer: O_Dunravin idiot
shaan_razal: yoo how much do you make
shaan_razal: >>
shaan_razal: ??
言語サム一語言山姆: SoonerLater
lef_xyz: @s3menthr0w3r Kreygasm
tdubey: @thealtchemist generally ineffective against covid-19
O_Dunravin: excuse me illdealer ?
snwlol: anti vaccine KKona
B1_Renekton: @thealtchemist we will find on 31st july when clinical trial is over
thealtchemist: @tdubey coolcool thanks for sharing
HaroonsLIVE: anti vaxxers WutFace WutFace WutFace
JumpTwiice: F
Epo97: F
lef_xyz: !uptime
HaroonsLIVE: how many doctor anti vaxxers are there ResidentSleeper
Thelazysinpe: howdy fellow people of twitch
言語サム一語言山姆: we can see viruses with SEMs
serRLNDT: 7
drkolenklow: find z_critical using significance value
HaroonsLIVE: @Thelazysinpe yoyo
crackmybones: i don't believe anti-vaxxers exist, they all actors
2Good5You: PogChamp
shaan_razal: google says that George makes about $100k in A WEEK!!LOL
HaroonsLIVE: @crackmybones paid actors LUL
drkolenklow: higher the p value the better it is
HovaCarlito: p value of 0.3 is shit fyi
crackmybones: @HaroonsLIVE exactly LUL
anguscupcake: anti-vaxxers were invented by bill gates
Thelazysinpe: i heard that countries that have mandatory tubercolosis vaxing have lower death rates
nhyy24: first time i'm catching you online. What's up george
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: my p value increases drastically after a can of monster
HaroonsLIVE: @crackmybones hired by republican party LUL
ofey: is there a sync problem or is it on my end?
drkolenklow: p value is the probability of samples
illogicalism: i get stream cuts too
km1no: my screen is black wth
warriorgiggles: 'tis a bit laggy
Grav48: lag between stream and sound huh
Skilion1: statistic 101
言語サム一語言山姆: mine does with 🍻
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: is the p value there found with a chi-squared test?
Rafabld1996: ewww p-values
HovaCarlito: especially if it's against a null
Thelazysinpe: does anybody have any tips for pushing myself to study
corpus_cule: p-hacking is a thing tho
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @Thelazysinpe fuckin do it
s3menthr0w3r: how do I calculate the d value?
mero_1181: Usually H0 is that they are the same
drkolenklow: no p value is around z-test
yungtoad1: @thelazysinpe don't study
warriorgiggles: yeah, study @Thelazysinpe
Thelazysinpe: i have to pass my maths bout to fail fucking first year of cs
mero_1181: Under H1 to be different
Skilion1: tl:dr the p-value is the percentage of the standardized test to be incorrect @georgehotz
snwlol: Audio isn't synced with the video, @georgehotz
smurfd0: https://www.wikihow.com/Calculate-P-Value with pictures :P
mero_1181: So if p-value < 0.05 you accept H0
illogicalism: @Thelazysinpe the only way to study is find a meaning in the study
semihisinvalid: what we making
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: audi osync is fine for me, F5?
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @drkolenklow p-value can be found from standard dervation or T test or chi squared test, silly
drkolenklow: most importantly you never accept null hypothesis, you either reject null hypothesis
drkolenklow: or you fail to reject it
programmingmouse: LUL
JustLOL__: @Thelazysinpe check out Learning how to learn course (free on coursera), deals with math learning as well
0xnan: hey any thought about the "moderna" vaccine? approach used and so on...? https://www.google.com/amp/s/amp.cnn.com/cnn/2020/07/14/health/moderna-coronavirus-vaccine-phase-1-study/index.html
drkolenklow: @fdfdfdfdfdfdff agreed, made a mistake sorry
snwlol: @quote_if_self_aware It's just a slight delay in audio for me. donno
mero_1181: The distribution of the test statistics change
Skilion1: tl:dr the p-value is the percentage of the standardized test to be incorrect @georgehotz
言語サム一語言山姆: @thelazysinpe just sit down and work your A off, I regret being lazy in college. also think of equations as black boxes and understand the overview of what you're trying to do before approaching a problem. imo
harrydieehre: @Thelazysinpe moving your ass. Nah just kidding. Try some background music. It helps me alot and I forget time so thats great
thealtchemist: ^background music without vocals prefferably
s3menthr0w3r: because when you get a nice bell curve the hard d value is somewhere on the right side and the soft d value I believe is on the left
bignickyg123: HACK THE WORLD
b2kemann: p val -> prob that you observed the given data if the null hypoz is true
crackmybones: one day george will be president
s3menthr0w3r: yes yes the mega d value is located around the mean
Thelazysinpe: thanks for the tips, i will try
illogicalism: as a dev anyone else feels sometimes completely inferior to practicioners of true science?
bignickyg123: mega d lol
thealtchemist: @Thelazysinpe Don't just try :-))
randomuser27485: hey, how did you remove the fake box on chrome new tab? @georgehotz
serRLNDT: @illogicalism that's some dumb shit
JumpTwiice: D:
Thelazysinpe: i need to pass only one math to get to the next year, calculus and the second one is discrete mathz
biniar_: ublock can remove things
snwlol: imagine falling for college scam Jebaited
anguscupcake: tfw high iq but lazy genes
言語サム一語言山姆: @thelazysinpe also I guess its a lot about time allocation. computers and smartphones are huge distractions. if you can manage it, I would just bring pen and paper to class .
thealtchemist: @Thelazysinpe If you show up from the beginning and read the course work, then it's not difficult
chillguy269: @Thelazysinpe Separate yourself from distractions, if you are sitting in a Twitch chat asking people for tips, you are probably just stalling. Learn your shit, get it done, feel good, and profit
言語サム一語言山姆: @thelazysinpe I'm so passionate about this because I'm finally tryna get my stupid ass bachelor's
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: being intelligent and not pushing yourself enough will be a fking disaster
mero_1181: Did he get Corona? Is this why he’s home and working on this again?
Grav48: JUST USE BRAVE
b1nk: s is standard deviation
mkdrmnd: @georgehotz pieter levels posted an extension that does this about 15 minutes ago (twitter)
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: i just tutored my girlfriend in stats and she got an A+. I'm so ready for this
B1_Renekton: @georgehotz you can use ublock origin to delete certain html elements based on tag/class/id from a webpage so that will do
ghostcomrade: @thelazysinpe for most topics, if you can find em on YT, just play a video and sit back, and then try another video, and things sometimes start to click
Skilion1: tl:dr the p-value is the percentage of the standardized test to be incorrect @georgehotz
nanbread_: first time tuning into the stream, just curious on your background I didnt see anything in your bio. Didnt even realize science & tech is a category on twitch which is cool
semihisinvalid: its all of them not clean
Jehhred: s = sample size most likely
smurfd0: the 2 in those pictures is x^2 so its like (-10)^2 = 100
chillguy269: stand dev sum of the variance squared and square root no?
adroniser: standard deviation is square root of the variance which is the average squared distance from the mean
s3menthr0w3r: tl:dr the b val is calculated from the p val + the hard d val. hard d val = soft d val + p2
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @georgehotz you probably have to use a T distribution here, given that we're talking about a sample space and not a population space
Thelazysinpe: the shit that we dont have a textbook, so i am finding stuff online from other colleges
thealtchemist: @nanbread_ clever it-guy that is now trying to decipher what vaccines do in regards to the covid MRANA vaccines
Rafabld1996: @georgehotz can you do something with Pymc3 to teach how real scientists do inference
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: if im wrong someone correct me
Skilion1: sigma - epsilon
Thelazysinpe: but imma go study now, have a nice day guys
illogicalism: i really hate the font they use for math notations, there are so many more friendly fonts that coule be used
CompestLive: Hey
Thelazysinpe: also gl to anyone that goes to college hah
chillguy269: @Thelazysinpe good job my friend get after it
言語サム一語言山姆: cya sinpe ty
thealtchemist: @Thelazysinpe go get em
b2kemann: standard deviation is : sqrt(E(x)^2-E(x^2))
b2kemann: width of the prob-dist
drkolenklow: sample mean = population mean - zc*(sd/(sample size)*0.5)
semihisinvalid: https://www.thoughtco.com/two-population-proportions-hypothesis-test-4075530 its m
thealtchemist: Is the "Introduction to algorithms" book the best for an indtroduction to the basic algorithms and datastructures?
tdubey: If you are using the chi-squared test for P value, that isn't "x-squared" that is "chi-squared"
tdubey: That x is the greek chi
z0rac: what is he rly doing in this stream? xD
adroniser: https://www.mathsisfun.com/data/standard-deviation.html
mero_1181: Standard deviation is estimated
mero_1181: As well
thealtchemist: chi-chi do you love me
CompestLive: First step to not be a newb, is don’t think like a newb
mero_1181: Is the sqrt of variance
illogicalism: confirmed by greek guy
Rafabld1996: look de moivre laplace theorem wiki article
drkolenklow: proportions
tdubey: you can calculate P value from any sort of "score" test, such as Z score, T score, Chi Square (X^2), or F-score
mero_1181: A robust estimator of the standard deviation is sqrt(s)
b1nk: p-hat is the population proportion
drkolenklow: those are proportions
xksteven: why do you try so many things? why not just leave stats to those who know? like you said isn't it worse only having a little knowledge and doing things incorrectly? @georgehotz
O_Dunravin: numpy np.std()
bignickyg123: whats the point of this math?
Toastie1: evaluating the meaning of life
tjobremannen: @Toastie1 Pog
bichid69: lol this stats stream is hilarious
adroniser: @bignickyg123 Figuring out how significant medical results are depending on how big the sample size is and how pronounced the effect is.
jBRADY: @xksteven its just for his personal knowledge
Skilion1: tl:dr the p-value is the percentage of the standardized test to be incorrect @georgehotz
Skilion1: just read my message lol
drkolenklow: you need a significance level for p value relation
adroniser: He knows this lol @Skilion1
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: @xksteven I guess the reasons are (a) for fun; and (b) cos it's interesting to watch
thealtchemist: above 0.05 is bad
drkolenklow: @bignickyg123 https://www.math.ualberta.ca/mss/misc/A%20Mathematician%27s%20Apology.pdf
thealtchemist: how many tests?
Skilion1: @adroniser so what is looking for
aleDsz: KEKW
xksteven: @jbrady but then won't be just be doing what he complains about? spreading bad info potentially?
comatross: i would assume for medical tests its one sided
tdubey: above 0.05 isn't necessarily bad, it depends on the test you are trying to do
adroniser: There's an xkcd about the threshold.https://xkcd.com/882/
thealtchemist: makes sense
jBRADY: @xksteven he isnt spreading bad info this is called learning. He is saying over and over again he's a noob at this
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: @xksteven Benefit of streaming it: you get people who call you out on your shit :P
Skilion1: chi has a differnet standardization
tjobremannen: @georgehotz can you make things bigger so its easier to read on stream?
z0rac: I think it depends on the way they defined the hypothesis. two tailed or nah
gettinggroceries: two tailed is less than or greater than
gettinggroceries: one tailed is only less than or only greater than
comatross: two tailed is 2x one tailed
xksteven: @quote_if_self_aware that's only true if there's an actual statistician watching though
gettinggroceries: stats major here
adroniser: Its pretty obvious that hes just trying to learn it. Dont think anyone would take away "incorrect info" from this
nanbread_: ^
b2kemann: don't give the idiot any attention
gettinggroceries: it's possible that he makes an incorrect assertion
AliFromThe313: intro to stats - hotz
nanbread_: you dont come to twitch for a course lesson lol
gettinggroceries: unless your school has moved to 100% virtual and your prof is streaming
kenqzzzz: sup george <3
b2kemann: we're hanging out
nanbread_: i really like the channel premise
codingquark: You like doing this and we like taking part?
tdubey: yoooooooo 4 gang
Krakatoa77: Sadge
tjobremannen: @georgehotz have you moved?
Zippy_NZ: I dont even know how to read mathematical notation just9nFeet
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: @xksteven but yeah you do have a point; I find these inspiring, though I don't believe and learn everything he says
thearthtyagi: yo whaddup bruh
nanbread_: i havent done stats since second year university ughh
soiax_: so what is your longevity stack then? :P
mozzerbob: haha
lesserthangood: just invent general artificial intelligence and make it do the work for u 4Head
thealtchemist: WE'RE HAVING FUN WITH STATISTICS BOYYS
thearthtyagi: we need coding today man
thearthtyagi: a lil bit
thearthtyagi: stats is cool tho
harrydieehre: Cheer100 just trashtalking and saving the world doing so.. SeemsGood
SaiBavun: Snake Pog
jluiiizz: @georgehotz Totally extreme off topic question, did you already had to deal with rsi or wrist pain in your days of hacking/lot of time coding ?
tjobremannen: simulations
austin__be__saucin: sudoku solver
adroniser: Code a simulation of the human body
codingquark: This stats will help us in reading papers boys
C3r0C3r0C3r0: hack the internets
Toastie1: bubble sort Pog
Krakatoa77: PogChamp math
guchiflamingo: why still using MAC?
nanbread_: https://twitter.com/sharifshameem/status/1282676454690451457?s=20 code this lol
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: molecular simulations/protein folding?
thearthtyagi: carpal tunnel syndrome
drkolenklow: this stream got me thinking
drkolenklow: this is nice - https://joyeuserrance.wordpress.com/2011/04/22/proof-that-p-values-under-the-null-are-uniformly-distributed/
linearpup: Coq!
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: PogChamp
linearpup: Sony got him
maxschneider96: back
harrydieehre: We should get starlink this internet sucks
Jehhred: He's BACK!
guchiflamingo: still using MAC OS?
thealtchemist: he didn't leave us :O
steventwtch: PogChamp
soiax_: how would u upload you mind with this connection?? pfff
codingquark: ah hello
tjobremannen: phising link Kappa
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: george keeb in NY?
Jehhred: down and up speeds?
brofessorbob: You not in SD anymore?
dark_krotonus: How's the new place?
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: is anyone else's streams buffering a shit ton?
case89: George don't become a douchebag like Martin shkreli
harrydieehre: 7 viewer lol
nanbread_: mine is clear now
tjobremannen: @fdfdfdfdfdfdff no
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @case89 wtf did you say about pharma daddy
codingquark: And the odds have to be... low?
comatross: if shkreli wasnt in jail, there could be epic george + shkreli coronavirus stream colab
asdhxc: free shkreli
linearpup: Build a fast nearest neighbor search
case89: @fdfdfdfdfdfdff fuck that guy
u1337ochka: looks like this shit always happens in clinical studies
aleDsz: LiveCoding is growing well on Twitch
joeyskitkat: you east coast!!
adroniser: Theres a stupid amount of fundamental clinical studies that haven't been able to be reproduced
nanbread_: F
Krakatoa77: did you look up p-hacking
Skilion1: @comatross lots of profit opportunities there for shkreli
drkolenklow: bye george time to cook some dinner. Bye everyone
aweasadbek: Why do you closed windows with closet
aleDsz: Here in Brazil we are trying to make LiveCoding something more remarkable
comatross: @Skilion1 yea, i wonder what are his options from jail
case89: George do you use scihub?
programmingmouse: i like pics too :)
Skilion1: I don't know, is he even still CEO of the pharma company? @comatross
adroniser: when was martin sentenced?
comatross: @Skilion1 no
zeroalligator: Every new technology was once never available for use, it’s a little dismissive to say since no current vaccines use the tech this one will not work.
thealtchemist: Score system for tests significance?
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: protein folding
linearpup: Monocular depth estimation
lesserthangood: simulation for Kanye West winning 2020
illogicalism: can we code my master thesis?
comatross: pong
maxschneider96: can u use machine learning to predict mutations for sars-cov2?
aPosterior: corona could use a patch
JohnnyThe_Hobo: can someone code my job task
tjobremannen: what is considered good?
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: robots in disguise
quinquanonagintilliard: hacking stuff with ebpf
SlenderSC: more than meets the eyes
thealtchemist: play me innn chess
xksteven: @georgehotz why not try out DETR from Facebook :)
joeyskitkat: Design a free platform for online schooling for school kids
TessituraAQ: I like this, keep doing this
Skilion1: @georgehotz so far do you reckon we gonna have any effective vaccines?
jib1337: Pog
tjobremannen: god i love cookies Kappa
case89: imagine George on methylphenidate
linearpup: Do this NIPS-2020 challenge https://bbochallenge.com/
thealtchemist: Trials will take yeears
volkerai: check out indias scam cure for coronavirus
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: @georgehotz Look up a bioinformatics course, find a thing they teach that you've not done yet, and do that if it sounds fun
codingquark: scan cure?
codingquark: *scam
iwicdti: do this https://www.udacity.com/course/ai-for-healthcare-nanodegree--nd320
codingquark: What did they do now?
patrickgekko: do a project euler lol
jib1337: This looks good
volkerai: some scam dude came up with ayurvedic cure for corona
case89: George you're a boss for talking to chat and learning at same time
oosed: never knew this guy streams
volkerai: claims it worked on many ppl
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: isn't that what ML is? Learning to assume?
volkerai: it is overpriced tablets
codingquark: Didn't Misky say something about making computers less uncertain?
zeroalligator: Moderna 3rd trial starts end of month on 30k ppl... they’ve never brought anything to market previously though, so...
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: or kina like genetic algos
thealtchemist: What's the next big thing in tech boooyyys
thealtchemist: Are we over blockchain yet?
oosed: @thealtchemist 666
thealtchemist: what is this
linearpup: The idea is to build a better ayesian optimizer. Finding better acquisition functions mostly
zeroalligator: Yes
jib1337: monkaW
zeroalligator: Very small trial size though
mero_1181: George, did you get Corona
bobrussel: yo what u up to
oosed: what's this guy doing, btw?
case89: George learn to Alt-Tab between windows more
oosed: developing covid vaccine?
JohnnyThe_Hobo: hacking corona
jonnie_dilly: Finding a cure for Bat Aids
zeroalligator: Moderna released phase 1 results recently, showed effectiveness in creating antibodies...
hsk1903: @georgehotz k3yboard?
Frenchism: When did georgehotz turned out to be Martin Shkreli
thealtchemist: https://humanbenchmark.com/
alrealre: @mero_1181 every one I know in real life got corona but they don't know or deny that they got it
linearpup: Predict when geohot opens a new tab vs new window :D
alrealre: there's no third option
RallPatej: yes geroge your alt tabbing skills are lacking n00b if you want to be a skilled hacker one day you need to be able to alt tab
zeroalligator: Lol exactly
Koduck007: well I run arch covid so i get exactly the symptoms i want
codingquark: *Real hackers* use tiling WMs
linearpup: *Elite hackers
oosed: breaking the lockdown on mass scale will prob work better
bobrussel: its so bright
Idanbotbol: Hello
volkerai: https://www.forbes.com/sites/meghabahree/2020/06/23/indian-billionaire-claims-his-new-herbal-concoction-is-a-100-cure-for-covid-19/#c652b5138ba8
Idanbotbol: Black windows, his room is in DarkMode
Denis0109: @georgehotz hey, how are you? Is everything doing great?
3lava: you moved?
maxschneider96: U could create a machine learning model that predicts antiviral peptides based on the sequence. There are research groups working on it. U could use data from this website for ur model: http://crdd.osdd.net/servers/avpdb/index.php
case89: https://www.nytimes.com/2020/05/12/nyregion/virus-orthodox-plasma-donation.html
alrealre: Yikes that cough hurt
codingquark: @maxschneider96 interesting! Thanks for the link!
Rain__1FPS: what r u doin
Ahowe444: It ruins the internet
ALICAImusic: Tru lmao
maxschneider96: @codingquark u´ re welcome, enjoy!
bobrussel: Pepega
programmingmouse: WutFace
I_am_paranoid: hachuDisgust
ratrapist: NICE
FargioFarmani: Nice
Digital_donger: accurate LUL
linearpup: See this cool paper on fast similarity search: https://arxiv.org/abs/1806.03198
codingquark: damn demo
JohnnyThe_Hobo: relase comma ai for free and charge people money if they don't want to get car accidents
koudbi: ahahah
J3rwin: Nice
DarkShadow1250: if i sub would you stop screeching :)
friedbeefed: my ears
STuaRTRuLeS: LUL
jonnie_dilly: You just scared my dog you son of a bitch
Jehhred: My neighbours are going to be so pissed
TessituraAQ: and it worked
Skilion1: sign up you cheap fuck
robodemia: geohot is a quack
CreedGamesOA: I just came in and got scared by the screaming sound gg's
zeroalligator: Signing up now...
illogicalism: i also agree, it is crazy how dumb people are to create so annoying business concepts
TessituraAQ: bought spotify premium immediately
aensaevhaerne: you didn't have to screech to demonstrate your point
joeyskitkat: LOLLL !!!!
her3hero: nice
RallPatej: lmfao
benjaminbreeg: WHAT THE.. I wasn't here for 2 minutes and I came back exactly in the moment when he started sreaming
parktype: parktype subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 5 months! PogChamp
airinspiration_: im gonna suscribe so I dont hear that sound
Denis0109: spclient.wg.spotify.com is the problem, cuz if you block it, nothing will work...What a bullshit
joeyskitkat: Do that again !
STuaRTRuLeS: :)
her3hero: no taco bell in Europe :(
tjobremannen: you computer is hacked, sign up for spotify to get rid of it Kappa
codingquark: I like that comma.ai is closer to Hacker culture than any other company
RallPatej: @georgehotz del taco is superior
xEHLE_: you trying to get a deal with taco bell? 4Head
zeroalligator: Buying a comma when I get a new car later this year... very excited
JohnnyThe_Hobo: @her3hero we have it in romania
gigafact: gigafact subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak! always interesting
bobrussel: can we get hotz screaming as a sub notification?
kuzan8: LUL
airinspiration_: @her3hero glad to hear that, tacobelll is Trash :)
TessituraAQ: every word in that abstract had at least 10 words yikes
THE_korbi: @bobrussel +1
TessituraAQ: letters
linearpup: finding nearest neighbors on 1 trillion vectors
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: 1 trillion and 1
RallPatej: which was worse, Ceaucescu or Taco Bell? @her3hero
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: obviously
bobrussel: ure cute <3
Tefosker: @georgehotz Hey George huge fan here! Did you see what we have done to BMWs? Letrons we made them as real transformers
Rain__1FPS: spread operator 4Head
linearpup: You train a network that maps inputs to a spherical lattice
programmingmouse: how to spread vectors? what does that mean lol
Einnod: !commands
ToshiCZ: will this be uploaded to youtube?
alrealre: Bike trip ? you must've inhaled a shit load of vehicle fumes and all that local air pollution
illogicalism: can we make a vaccine?
Frenchism: But they also assume it's linear and that they might use traditional stats such as P-value and those kind of BS. Isn't covid-19 non-liinear ? Maybe check this https://necsi.edu/corona-virus-pandemic
THE_korbi: @toshicz certainly
robodemia: quack
bobrussel: LUL
THE_korbi: LULW
dunehazard: KEKW
wutango: LUL
maxschneider96: hahahaha
myasovlavashe: LUL
skandd1: LUL
NotKarar: LUL
Bretel: ahahahaha
alliums_: hi George Kreygasm
THE_korbi: get rekt
skunsy: !uptime
parktype: OmegaLul
robodemia: comma.ai is a quack
illogicalism: is hotz trump supporter?
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: damn I missed that
nudax: WutFace
asdhxc: libtard gets btfod
her3hero: the vector stuff sounds like lattice space in physics
jib1337: Libs lose again
ToshiCZ: Corona cant be worse than inhaling diesel fumes whilce cycling
crispi____: KEKW
astrocraft23: Squid1 Squid2 CrreamAwk Squid4
jeffbezos6: HeyGuys hi george
Gefluegelrolle: this description is so woke, much wow
B1_Renekton: safespaces LUL
ck1956: you need to supress cytokine storm
jeffbezos6: Ni hao from beijing
medismailben: What are we doing today ?
dunehazard: oh shit, i love that term. PopScience
ck1956: exactly
linearpup: https://github.com/spotify/annoy
crispi____: lmao
Forcepain123: Is viral load a thing? Would make sense to reduce it by 40% then, no?
Frenchism: Sure, because it"s not linear, there are super-spreader, such as a single individual in South Corea contaminating a whole hospital if i recall correctly
ToshiCZ: what was that coough @georgehotz corona incoming?
jeffbezos6: Why c++?
volkerai: c++ can do shit java can't
volkerai: and that is facts
Tefosker: @georgehotz can comma.ai do something like this in the future? http://www.letrons.com/index_eng.html
RichyK1: c++ vs java... ResidentSleeper
jeffbezos6: Sure but c is better
volkerai: c++ when you need OOPs
noclip32: x is better than y ResidentSleeper
volkerai: for complex softwares
volkerai: C for systems programming obviosly
marschr: on the ebola epidemics in africa a lot of healthcare workers got infected when undressing the PPE (in related to masks)
Denis0109: @volkerai java is used in android programming, so it can do something that c++ cant do
cod1r: bro
RichyK1: @Denis0109 ?
volkerai: yeah
linearpup: I personally use approximate nearest neighbor search to find query similar images from millions of images. I vectorize the images using a neural net and index them in one of these indexes. Search is usually < 1 sec
cod1r: broskie
volkerai: but c++ > java
jeffbezos6: Oops are fine in c
iwicdti: diskrrrtttt
pilliam2: i wish i had better discrete math skills
haircutjimmy: Hi @georgehotz
volkerai: C++ is superior for OOPS
her3hero: do a college course on stream PogChamp
serRLNDT: any thoughts on the upcoming apple silicon? Are you excited at all?
TessituraAQ: yeah I wish I watched educational youtube in highschool
rai0xff: best streamer ever !
THE_korbi: yeah 3blue1brown is awesome
ck1956: 3blue1brown is the GOAT
Denis0109: lets go assembler
jeffbezos6: What advantage do u get?
aensaevhaerne: yeah linear algebra classes are shit in college
joedcv: what are we working on today?
volkerai: pointers
volkerai: vs java that is
haircutjimmy: Been a while - good to see the fella back on it.
bobrussel: i may be to stupid to follow whats going on
tajpouria: Remdesivir has positive effect?
linearpup: Use it to build a similarity search for comma street level videos and search for similar images for data augmentation
volkerai: C with OOPs is basically C++
jeffbezos6: C data type is more efficient ent but i agree this is just semantics
volkerai: if you are doing OOPS in C then you are programming in C++ rather than C
jeffbezos6: Im not sure entirely
volkerai: C doesn't have OOP
volkerai: look it up
jeffbezos6: Oop is the link right?
volkerai: C is not an OOP
THE_korbi: good points
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: o7
RallPatej: wait whats wrong with masks
mozzerbob: hmm
volkerai: object oriented progamming language
ck1956: https://masks4all.co/ - Jeremy Howard
any_truers: new here looks interesting so far
volkerai: classes, inheritance, etc
zeroalligator: *cloth masks
Frenchism: Am i a looser if I assume that since there's a slight chance we're better off with mask than without than I should use mask ? :p
volkerai: that stuff is not in C
aPosterior: NotLikeThis
imgifty: hahaha, is he saying wearing masks is useless?
angusmiguel: omg i just noticed @georgehotz looks like a younger David Costabile
t3rabyt3_: Hi @all
holysons11: whats wrong with mask
jeffbezos6: Oh i see
jeffbezos6: We dont use that language here
nudax: no mask in sweden
jeffbezos6: Sorry for bad english
deanfx: What's up man! Hope you're doing well
jeffbezos6: Not my first language
t3rabyt3_: t3rabyt3_ subscribed at Tier 1.
thealtchemist: no mask in denmark either
mozzerbob: I'm just oing to wear a mask, even something shitty, its not going to make me more reckless, and if it helps in anyway even small good
thealtchemist: yay science
volkerai: regardless, c++ is better over C for software engineering and encapsulation
zeroalligator: N95/P100 masks are effective if used all the time... and none are available so...
THE_korbi: @imgifty he says it might be useless
thodeannn: @volkerai u re boring, nobody cares ur opinions about languages. everybody aware which language offers which features
bobrussel: why is not wearing a mask believing in science
Denis0109: @georgehotz do you think that there will be a second wave?
jeffbezos6: I will have a look as i always avoided classes in anything as c was fast
bitcoin_to_zero: LULW
bobrussel: true
thealtchemist: :O
robodemia: DNA is a quack
illdealer: truth hurts
oxtuq: I'd subscribe if you streamed a lot, but I see you like once a month
Jehhred: https://www.worldometers.info/coronavirus/country/australia/ Australia got a second wave
4_realzies: check florida
B3by11: who has a similar dashboard with cases per million
haircutjimmy: bottom right
ebrahim_31: For second wave look iran
pilliam2: check victoria australia
B3by11: https://covid19.who.int/?gclid=Cj0KCQjw0rr4BRCtARIsAB0_48OAM0Iu7ZJ33NfogW85XFmLyP3OPgvpOtFJdbgCNWlhJ7PQSlsuAY4aAn9fEALw_wcB
Frenchism: Germany, they closed some departments there to avoid a second wave.
ck1956: phillipines is interesting, no deaths
maxschneider96: austria
Galveri: thats austria
brofessorbob: Look at case fatality rate per age group binned.
djokaraaa: serbia
JohnnyThe_Hobo: romania got a second wave 2
linearpup: There are no cases if there is no testing
Forcepain123: but they had 500 cases at peak lol
her3hero: i like this dashboard on corona. https://aatishb.com/covidtrends/
ck1956: lol
RallPatej: @georgehotz why not look at rt.live? there is clearly a second wave of infections if you look at reproduction rate
quinquanonagintilliard: Can't beat Vietnam though
Poisonslash: LUL
CyberNuance: lol
probably_sleeping01: oo shit what did i miss out on
pilliam2: we've had 5 days concurrent of +200 infections a day in Victoria Australia
skandd1: LUL
maxschneider96: search australia, not austria
NotKarar: Yep.
B3by11: 0 cases in north korea too
unrandomknown: LUL
ebrahim_31: lol you still remember that?
joedcv: lol
adroniser: UK has defeated the coronavirus
mozzerbob: Austrailia is a pretty big country too
Skilion1: @georgehotz spain number are kinda sketchy. They get 600 cases, then 0 for a couple of days, than 800. There are 200k people isolated in catalunya
Ahowe444: Vietnam is the one with no deaths
subwaymonkeyyy: Australia was more 1.5 not a wave 2
brofessorbob: 93% of covid deaths in US are of people over the age of 55
skandd1: link for that ?
Poisonslash: Seems like the homies in the Arctic are doing just fine xqcF
RallPatej: @georgehotz effective reproduction number shows second wave in every state including NY
subwaymonkeyyy: we never really had a inital wave
jamieemb_: @adroniser hahahahaha, everywhere in the UK except England has defeated the coronavirus. FTFY
serRLNDT: @Skilion1 did it ever cross your mind that maybe they don't report everyday?
Skillath: I flew from Sweden back home to Spain on Saturday and it's getting kinda interesting down here...
ido1m: @georgehotz Look up Israel's daily cases graph for a real 2nd wave
ck1956: sorry Vietnam is the one with no deaths
tajpouria: Iran more than 220 death per day
any_truers: I think the link you are using for the corona map is not trustable, I heard something about malware there, use the official site: https://coronavirus.jhu.edu/map.html
lzrdkng21: the covid median death age here was above the avg life span
ck1956: lol
Skilion1: @serRLNDT wow. thanks, genius.
her3hero: D:
Theguywhobea: vietnam made a cool song about how not to get it
serRLNDT: @Skilion1 then don't call it sketchy dumbfuck
quinquanonagintilliard: arc gis is a GIS company
arhamkaiser: what is a israel
alrealre: Covid is Tide for boomers
linearpup: Fun fact: The average age of Covid-19 deaths is higher than the average age of ALL deaths
Digital_donger: @any_truers that site is just a frame to the original site LUL
Frenchism: I'm still confuse about the f(x) you associate to the spreading of covid, if there are super-spreader, should we not use a Power law distribution that forbid P-value and this kind of propr. ?
case89: HeyGuys
bored_spagetti: finally george you are live !
bored_spagetti: how is your summer everyone ?
Poisonslash: @georgehotz There were some map sites that were infecting people with malware but those are sketchy sites lmao. I doubt you'd fall for one of them.
bitcoin_to_zero: drugs?
Ohi3enn: Geographical Information System company
Digital_donger: what does he sell? monkaS
Skilion1: @serRLNDT lol. you don't even know what you are talking about. They actually reported 0 cases for that day, and then the day after 850. 2 days before 652. dumbfuck
bobrussel: yourself
aPosterior: ye we know
Theguywhobea: dash cams
arhamkaiser: drugs?
alrealre: @linearpup yeah cause stillborn counts as a death and adds to that number
ItsAMarcos: I have drank too much beer so I can not keep up with yesterday's criticism
MajesticMack: Wait you dont sell life insurance?
mero_1181: Why are you not at work?
FirstNameAndLastName: YES
zeroalligator: Sure
arhamkaiser: watch sum steins;gate
ivylions: inserted furin site
adroniser: Mutation G614
thealtchemist: ayyy
ck1956: you should may be do a stream on economics of cornoavirus
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: Entropy analysis of the genome
Jamsong8667: build something cool noob
maxschneider96: u could look at genetic susceptibility
ionelaipatioaei: when is the next programming stream?
LimeTimeee: diabetes=insta death from covid ?
guchiflamingo: Listen Hotz
rektiwow: entertain us streamer
ItsAMarcos: I wore a face diaper for groceries today 😁
sliceserve: "keep it up"
Jensb6: must also note that the coronavirus also causes damage to organs and brain.
jorijnsmit: did you hack it? where can we download vaccin?
THE_korbi: haha
linearpup: Build similarity search for comma
Skilion1: @serRLNDT come to spain, read local new, than give your opinion.
kklisura: BCG vaccine protection from severe coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19). https://www.pnas.org/content/early/2020/07/07/2008410117
aPosterior: what's been your angle so far? cure?
CyberNuance: here for you, not the subject
qezuke: any good idle for C?
robodemia: blockcahing on corona
insignia_microwave: hey how are you today?
FirstNameAndLastName: Psychological impact of all this isolation?
jib1337: I’m feeling bullish on corona
pilliam2: what are we using spreading vectors for?
kvndsantos: This is just fun to listen to while getting some work done
guchiflamingo: Luc Montagier - nobel prize winner discovered HIV virus RNA sequence in Covid-19
qezuke: @georgehotz any good idle for C?
arhamkaiser: fuck rona
robodemia: blockcahing on corona
zeroalligator: Leave it up, you’re making my work day far more interesting
t3rabyt3_: t3rabyt3_ is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 1 in the channel!
t3rabyt3_: t3rabyt3_'s Gift shared rewards to 5 others in Chat!
t3rabyt3_: t3rabyt3_ gifted a Tier 1 sub to jo_renttt!
thodeannn: @qezuke ed
serRLNDT: @Skilion1 yes, I'm going to assume that you have uncovered some grand conspiracy that Spain has been hiding numbers
foxubu: Thanks for the PrideWorld @t3rabyt3_
serRLNDT: @Skilion1 even though I can't find anyone reporting on it
qezuke: @thodeannn thats the name ?
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: PogChamp
Skilion1: @serRLNDT ok, thanks for your input
DesolderingPump: @qezuke Have you tried Vim?
d4rkvist3r: hi
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: hype train
ItsAMarcos: George you're awesome, loved your talk on the simulation
ak0ya_: @georgehotz what was your final opinion on muzero?
thealtchemist: they found some bubonic plague around the world, pretty interesting, not deadly though
zeroalligator: train hype
jib1337: Scam train
serRLNDT: @Skilion1 gracias por el tuyo cabrón
fowlmoves: !commands
maxschneider96: genome wide association study of susceptibility to coronavirus: https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2020283?source=nejmtwitter&medium=organic-social
fowlmoves: Bogus lul
Denis0109: what's with hackthebox? don't you like it anymore? I mean there are a lot of machines, that don't require VIP.
guchiflamingo: Luc Montagier - nobel prize winner discovered HIV virus RNA sequence in Covid-19
DesolderingPump: Like my paper :(
insignia_microwave: I found a pretty cool paper on coronavirus. if you want it just ask @georgehotz
theknip: @georgehotz What do you think of fast.ai?
brofessorbob: I say we throw a "free" cochella for the age group that has a less than 1% (people under age of 35) case fatality rate and build the heard immunity.
anguscupcake: free corona
guchiflamingo: Luc Montagier - nobel prize winner discovered HIV virus RNA sequence in Covid-19.
guchiflamingo: look it up
Skilion1: @serRLNDT https://english.elpais.com/society/2020-06-24/the-problems-spains-outdated-data-methods-have-caused-during-a-21st-century-pandemic.html
Skilion1: @serRLNDT no coverage
ItsAMarcos: George have you had a look at the ARC challenge by chollet?
ItsAMarcos: energy based models? what's the path to AGI?
thealtchemist: pretty graph is pretty
guchiflamingo: https://www.europarl.europa.eu/doceo/document/E-9-2020-002429_EN.html
bloopsterr: f
thealtchemist: f
hi_im_drakster: f5
jeffbezos6: F
FirstNameAndLastName: laggg
THE_korbi: not f
zlziga: george can you show desktop please
bloopsterr: short f
insignia_microwave: george how long you gonna stream cause I get paycheck on friday so I'll sub then
THE_korbi: @bloopsterr yeah ^^
jorijnsmit: did you cough in your elbow?
jeffbezos6: HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HeyGuys HI GEORGE
ChronixSC: corona was found in spanish waste waters in march 2019 apparently. https://www.ub.edu/web/ub/en/menu_eines/noticies/2020/06/042.html
maxschneider96: illumina is the leading next-gen sequencing company
linearpup: Build an image super resolution GAN from scratch PunchTrees
thealtchemist: damn why are subscriptions so expensive
tajpouria: 'Iran Guards Commander Claims Machine Can Detect Coronavirus 100 Meters Away ' wrap up researches with this!
pielliepalie: We still busy with the rona?
guchiflamingo: Luc Montagier - nobel prize winner discovered HIV virus RNA sequence in Covid-19.
bored_spagetti: @ChronixSC just yesterday a university in Greece found covid in waste water here too
guchiflamingo: https://www.europarl.europa.eu/doceo/document/E-9-2020-002429_EN.html
jeffbezos6: SeemsGood Kappa RedCoat TheRinger StoneLightning OptimizePrime BCWarrior MrDestructoid Kreygasm SSSsss
FirstNameAndLastName: @pielliepalie yes
alrealre: rona's not going to go away for at least 2 more years
jeffbezos6: Iam gay
THE_korbi: KappaPride
FirstNameAndLastName: rona owes us all child support money
thealtchemist: @alrealre maybe one if we're lucky
xxblueshift: xxblueshift subscribed at Tier 1.
thealtchemist: Kinda hope i can work from home next year, not gonna lie
ItsAMarcos: I lagged did he reply to the chollet stuff?
neunaaz: any advice for a startup??
bored_spagetti: guys have you had a chance to find a girlfriend during the pandemic ?
maxschneider96: genome-wide association studies are usually quite good for complex diseases
maxschneider96: polygenic diseases
alrealre: @thealtchemist European govt officials said that their experts predict global market to be closed at least until 2021 Q4
tajpouria: Maybe create another like that phone call?
FirstNameAndLastName: @bored_spagetti no
4a6f686e446f65: @georgehotz You are such an inspiration to me!
zlziga: can we see your desktop wallpaper?
jeffbezos6: Europeans arent good at science and stuff
Skilion1: @serRLNDT sketchy means exactly sketchy, nothing that you assumed, no need to attach or be offensive. Just got to fuck off now
thealtchemist: @alrealre noot bad
bored_spagetti: @jeffbezos6 4Weird
THE_korbi: phenomena
thealtchemist: @jeffbezos6 stup we smart
thealtchemist: stop*
soiax_: and then you dont believe in correlation with mask studies... lol
Ahowe444: me too but kind of expensive for me
covac123: LUL
hi_im_drakster: LUL
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: not gonna be cheap
Forcepain123: monkaW
dogslayes: KEKW
Skilion1: @serRLNDT ok
cutza: you'll be hacked
Digital_donger: PogChamp
insignia_microwave: goodbye chances of being a murderer Kappa
thes1nbad: go! BloodTrail
imgifty: this guy on coke all the time
marschr: git clone geohotz
l1ttlemtman: sup
Vackin: it few thousand still
holysons11: debate destiny
jib1337: DO IT Pog
phrixus_bro: no trouble here boss
xxblueshift: git clone george
darkzade: monkaS
BabyfaceKappa: @georgehotz im looking forward to it and greetings from germany
Digital_donger: no sir monkaS
gtnftw: sequence my dna mami
insignia_microwave: yeah you did tell us
alrealre: is he seeing things? LuL
superluminal86: is that a wise thing to do?
atthem0ment: reeeBrr reeeRrr reeeRrr
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: @xxblueshift LOL
mozzerbob: @georgehotz good I have a few pull requests to make
shrysk: I'm a make a georgebot
jeffbezos6: Wow
4a6f686e446f65: but you didnt send it because you might have became a serial killer xD
musabkilic0: hi george, have you heard about Project Evidence?: https://project-evidence.github.io/ "Evidence SARS-CoV-2 Emerged From a Biological Laboratory in Wuhan, China"
FirstNameAndLastName: samshoOs samshoOs samshoOs samshoOs samshoOs samshoOs samshoOs samshoOs
Zeldorino: monkaS
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: George, do it and I will sub
alrealre: lol
yogi_1010: 'Career path' lol
Whynox: ola, tudo bem?
lesserthangood: shoutout edward snowden
atthem0ment: reeeD
marschr: tinder would become "pull requests" LOL
lzrdkng21: Is that only for US nationals ?
gigafact: stixeeHuh
wootawee: ffsk not the lab conspiracy
Skilion1: @serRLNDT im sorry, you're right. thanks for correcting my grammar
insignia_microwave: btw I'm logi I changed my username
numbaeon: I used dantelabs.com for my dna but I have doubts of their privacy policies.
xxblueshift: lol
maxschneider96: Systems biology is very powerful generally, all omics like genomics, interactomics etc provide powerful tools for the future of drug discovery
prince___amir: hi bro
不好意思: YEP
FirstNameAndLastName: SSSsss SSSsss SSSsss SSSsss
adroniser: If china made a very infectious deadly bioweapon they could release it in the us and the shut all flights and it would be like a nuke without mutually assured destruction
musabkilic0: yeah, i agree with you on the Project E
DeepBlender: Yes, no one knows. So why is there a need to pick "sides" about where it came from?
insignia_microwave: could someone plant your DNA at a murder scene. I doubt it but
THE_korbi: ...relevant?
hugokeys: These guys weren't even able to prove twins were identical tho. Not sure I'd trust their results
RapidEU: there's myheritage aswell I think
SpaceGhost8: blockchain PogChamp
hi_im_drakster: why is the screen so small XD
okeeeeeee: bingo
iskjmss: LUL
thealtchemist: YES BLOCKCHAIN BUY!
Zeldorino: KEKW
THE_korbi: @hugokeys who?
jamieemb_: who owns the data after a genome sequence? Does the company own the data?
jib1337: SCAM
linearpup: powered by AI
Sleeper009: This is good for bitcoin
marschr: genecoins
d4rkvist3r: how do viruses arise?
insignia_microwave: cant use blockchain cause we lost all our house in bitcoin Kappa
synthblade7080: PogChamp
ActForImpact: just curious, why would you want to sequenz your genom?
numbaeon: I have results from them after months of waiting
hugokeys: @THE_korbi Ancestry, MyHeritage, 23andMe, fasmilytree, and living all failed the twin test
maxschneider96: it´ s usually with saliva, right?
holysons11: pogChamp
THE_korbi: @hugokeys thx
hugokeys: https://www.cbc.ca/news/technology/dna-ancestry-kits-twins-marketplace-1.4980976
jamieemb_: just wait for celebrities to start licensing and selling their DNA for the inevitable designer genetics boom that will happen within the next 10 years
hugokeys: They were unable to show twins even come from the same place. Twins sent samples to both companies and they did not even source them to the same origin
cutza: do they offer you the raw data?
okeeeeeee: im gonna clone you :) @georgehotz
insignia_microwave: LUL
zeroalligator: www.veritasgenetics.com
phrixus_bro: thank you
whit_314: Thanks Goerge!
JohnnyThe_Hobo: we are gonna clone george
linearpup: GPLv3 please
xxblueshift: can i have ur intelligence
hi_im_drakster: nice LUL
okeeeeeee: PogChamp
pilliam2: thanks
TessituraAQ: pull requests?
thealtchemist: I'll clone it and make a super george
wutango: PogChamp
filipeoliveiraa: PogChamp
Joy_void_Joy: Aren't you scared someone will just do an Emulated Mind out of you o: ?
numbaeon: I heard dante labs makes up the cheap tests by selling your dna data for research.
PhantomYTReal: Can't wait til someone leaves your dna at a crime scene
linearpup: GPLv3
angusmiguel: scuffed beard LUL
qatarking24xd: PogChamp
thealtchemist: whaaatevveeer we like
ck1956: can you get Elon Musks DNA
insignia_microwave: can I plant your dna at a crime scene? Kappa
B1_Renekton: george for president
Mobius5: I'd like ur DNA george, i need some more intelligence in myfamily
koudbi: @hugokeys different companies have trained their model on different samples
serRLNDT: what if I commit a crime and plant your DNA Kappa
Ahowe444: lol
yogi_1010: lol
Zeldorino: phone calls DansGame
linearpup: LOLOL
xxblueshift: OMEGALUL
PhosphoricAcid: LUL
cnovacost: I will inject your dna into coronavirus so he knows how to program itself
okeeeeeee: 1000-600= 400 $ :)
thealtchemist: HAHAHA
koudbi: LUL
cipher_textt: lmfao
iskjmss: AHAHHAAHHA
cutza: LOL 400 profit
covac123: it is only logical
samsara_c: You're gonna get your great uncle arrested for a 1976 bank robbery where they found a cigarette left behind
shrysk: KEKW
insignia_microwave: what if I plant your dna at a crime scene
hi_im_drakster: Pog
pilliam2: Pog
jamieemb_: does honey offer a discount on 23&me?
tornix98: bat with coronavirus -> exotic animalls -> sold at wuhan seafoood market -> pass onto humans
gwatts: $33 per min to speak with geohotz
gwatts: bargain
Burton1: Pog
sanyadollar: LUL
myasovlavashe: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
alexanderrrrr: EZ Clap
hi_im_drakster: S T O N K S
okeeeeeee: LULW
anguscupcake: Damn 1k an hour is a good wage
SpaceGhost8: EZ
xksteven: why not discuss comma on stream?
CyberNuance: free 60
PhosphoricAcid: lucky day
thealtchemist: BUY MORE IT'S ALMOST FREE
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: LOL
kvndsantos: LOL
phrixus_bro: you should try 50-off
thodeannn: how bout 50-OF
alrealre: it's always 10% off
RobinMalfait: Now try 100-OFF
Joy_void_Joy: Just input 20-OFF :) ?
angusmiguel: what about 100-off=?
thealtchemist: try 90-OF
anantacodes: Why not use 20-OFF now?
yogi_1010: do it again 9 more time!
hugokeys: @koudbi i mean the results are by them. They weren't testing if different companies produced the same results, it was that each company had failed to id them to the same background
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: F
THE_korbi: F
okeeeeeee: F
JohnnyThe_Hobo: they got him
I_am_paranoid: -100-OFF
hi_im_drakster: f
thealtchemist: YES
Burton1: f
Burton1: saved
hugokeys: BIg pharma got him
THE_korbi: lol
PhantomYTReal: When george gets arrested for his DNA being at a crime scene I wanna be there
okeeeeeee: LUL
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: LOL
thodeannn: dfjoaslfkjsalfjkasdfkjhasd;f4
wutango: LUL
movAX13h: lol
cutza: LOL
I_am_paranoid: lol
filipeoliveiraa: LUL
Ropat: LUL
qatarking24xd: LUL
myasovlavashe: LUL LUL LUL LUL LUL
koudbi: ahahah
alexanderrrrr: LMAO
Mobius5: LOOOL
jakuhor: xddd
Toastie1: HAHAHA
thealtchemist: WE RIIIICH!
okeeeeeee: hahaha
alrealre: nice
hi_im_drakster: LUL
1donald: LUL
insignia_microwave: LUL
Koduck007: LOL
TessituraAQ: loool
xxblueshift: LUL
filipeoliveiraa: EZ Clap
NilsIRL: LUL
lzrdkng21: 10/10
phrixus_bro: haaaaa
thealtchemist: WE RICHHH
ayyken0: LUL
O_Dunravin: hax
her3hero: LUL
Rennem: LUL
gwatts: 30-OFF
bloopsterr: LUL
iskjmss: HAHAHAHAHAHA
jamieemb_: W
Ahowe444: LMAO
r0llingQUADS: LUL
kvndsantos: TRY 60
samsara_c: KEEP GOING
gwisr: LUL wtf
angusmiguel: OMEGALUL
skunsy: LUL
SSayMyName: LOOL
musabkilic0: LUL
Koduck007: 1337 hax
Burton1: LUL
cutza: 100 - OFF
anguscupcake: WTF
bananaconda: EZ Clap
PhosphoricAcid: ez
onefunkynote: Try 30 and 40
thealtchemist: MORE MORE
alexanderrrrr: try 30
qatarking24xd: go on
random11_real: ahahahaahh
Bretel: ahahahahahha wtf
okeeeeeee: try 25
JAKWAI: Hackerman
maikgs: Lol
Repunk: WOW
numbaeon: EZ
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: LUL LUL LUL
CyberNuance: try free
gwisr: 25?
random11_real: dont stop
不好意思: LUL
gtnftw: try "FREE"
aensaevhaerne: EZ Clap
gwatts: 25
kvndsantos: 60
movAX13h: its on the same website and they dont even check ... haha
thealtchemist: :((
angusmiguel: 25-OFF
samsara_c: COMBINE WITH 10-OFF
evildevil90: those are usually all client side. you can easily reverse that
maxschneider96: type in FREE
shrysk: LUL LUL
不好意思: FREE LUL
okeeeeeee: HACKS LUL
THE_korbi: EZ Clap
linearpup: LOLOLOL
bored_spagetti: EZ Clap
norflin221: 2020 hacking
Whynox: i was do this
SigmaHeavyIndustries: hackerman
thealtchemist: :(/
ck1956: try 25
brofessorbob: 100-OFF
Joy_void_Joy: LUL
Whynox: always
aurumvorax421: who is the dumbfuck that made that ?
her3hero: 100-off Pogchamp
thealtchemist: We'll resell to the 10-off suckers
qlutoo: 50-off ?
marschr: LOL
qatarking24xd: LUL LUL
musabkilic0: just saved 120$ LUL
filipeoliveiraa: try FREE Kappa
linearpup: Elite hacker
Mobius5: Scuffed LUL
her3hero: 69-OFF worked PogChamp
Xiffix: great you spinned the wheel!
insignia_microwave: @thealtchemist I love it
alrealre: coffee is better
JohnnyThe_Hobo: i already see the meeting with the programmer who did this
Sleeper009: 69 nice
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: holy shit, this guy is such a good hacker that he just got 20% off for nothing
alrealre: tea is some sweet kidney stone times
MrBankster: hackinsack
joshperri: You really did hack the PlayStation...
Rennem: earn 10 dollar by typing 110-off LUL
THE_korbi: always keep it 69
anguscupcake: tea is less taxing on the adrenals
thealtchemist: that chair has charchter
mr_ahab_: I miss the kitchen background
joshperri: Where did the kitchen go?
ido1m: @Rennem But it's %
jamieemb_: right bois, I need a new chair recommendation
yogi_1010: his beard has character. Get it from github
Zeldorino: No BTTV emotes FeelsBadMan
linearpup: dx racer
anguscupcake: just get the leap v2
JoRoFo: herman miller
JoRoFo: aeron
Rennem: @ido1m oh, true
thealtchemist: Herman miller ma duuude
prince___amir: i am also drinking green tea now
linearpup: herman miller mirra 2
mkdrmnd: Smh I stepped away for 20m and George is buying a genome sequencing test
SSayMyName: Well I need qwerty recommendation
joshperri: He dating someone again? I don’t think he got a conscience overnight and regretted diaper face
jamieemb_: wish i had the money for one, the broke uni student life will pay off one day
phrixus_bro: herman miller use code 20-off
O_Dunravin: the DNA is worth so much more to the company, they get paid twice!
anantacodes: When are we doing the house tour?
mattdougherty22: why are you back in jersey? just joined
Xiffix: great you spinned the wheel, 120$
brofessorbob: Greatings from North Park
PhantomYTReal: George what would happen if they found your dna at a crime scene but your dna is open source?
insignia_microwave: wait your in jersey?
thealtchemist: good plan @PhantomYTReal
thealtchemist: can't be convicted if it's open source
PhantomYTReal: Got it crime pays and a lot at that
joshperri: Is that a sign of a good person?
Relmnight_Live: except tax evasion. SHit pays good
Mobius5: Kinda does LUL
axlebear: is his DNA MIT licensed?
adroniser: What if someone uses your DNA and places it at crime scene
musabkilic0: dante also has an advanced kit for 850$
hi_im_drakster: LUL
her3hero: LUL
egghead0102: is their 30X genome sequencing somehow lesser than 130X + 30X genome sequencing?
thealtchemist: SCAM
axlebear: KEKW
insignia_microwave: cannabis health report LUL
JakeJ24: utter bollox
Xiffix: you earned 120 bucks tho :D
Zeldorino: Scam FeelsGoodMan
joedcv: yeah
Repunk: $34 jeez
alexanderrrrr: lmao
anguscupcake: nice
lulascoca: buy it PogChamp
4a6f686e446f65: @georgehotz Does that sign in the backgroudn say "Dreams" ??????
THE_korbi: oh jeeeezus
tatsumiss: LULW
bruh_imcoding: Georges DNA embedded in computer viruses hmmm
kvndsantos: DNA App Store
mozzerbob: Thats the subtitle for anything I make
Digital_donger: D:
SpaceGhost8: overwhelming data LUL
axlebear: Cytokine storm testing is a total bait and switch
mattdougherty22: just rewatched Aaron Swartz doc. Did you ever get to meet or have read any of his blogs?
angusmiguel: it does english :)
smurfd0: damn that app seem to know everything about covid :D
linearpup: lololol
thealtchemist: big computer go bip-bop
anguscupcake: computers are made of meat
mexeroserisback: download more genome ram . com
TessituraAQ: this is fun, I'm having fun
4a6f686e446f65: @georgehotz Does that sign in the background say "Dreams" ?
PhantomYTReal: Enchancing you genomes to make sure your offspring are better than you
pilliam2: liquid cooling is my computers blood
skunsy: cyberpunk stuff
Joy_void_Joy: *enhance*
wasphy: Hey George! In the podcast with Lex you said that you would like to physically move to the cloud. Can you expand on the mechanics behind that? Thank you!
tatsumiss: sophisticated scam
thealtchemist: Any thoughts on nootropics?
jamieemb_: @thealtchemist pretty sure he was taking l-theanine for a while
kvndsantos: LOL
CyberNuance: thats great
mozzerbob: hah
Digital_donger: LUL
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: @4a6f686e446f65 I looked it up yesterday, yeah basically, or "to dream"
d4rkvist3r: lol
insignia_microwave: lol
PhantomYTReal: No don't bring back the key gen flashbacks
iskjmss: generic WPF project
aurumvorax421: keygen music is pretty cool
thealtchemist: @jamieemb_ Interesting, you shouldn't sleep on that
anguscupcake: lions mane is my favorite
O_Dunravin: there's two routes wasphy, Tron or the Lawnmower man
insignia_microwave: hiding in the bookshelf LUL
maxschneider96: go one step further and do transcriptomics in all tissues of ur body lol
4_realzies: thought you were l theanine shill
movAX13h: the virus in the keygen becomes something completely different :)
4_realzies: a*
PhantomYTReal: tbh any iced tea is pretty good
thealtchemist: Pramiracetam == aderall
mexeroserisback: Kreygasm
axlebear: What about those brainwave machines
Joy_void_Joy: Chiptune Pog
thealtchemist: piracetam, mixing them up, what's what
mattdougherty22: just rewatched Aaron Swartz doc. Did you ever get to meet or have read any of his blogs?
cutza: lol
skunsy: Oh dude I hated these
wasphy: Piracetam is really really cheap in my country.
Ne0Zer0: LUL
brofessorbob: Woohoo!
SigmaHeavyIndustries: based
mexeroserisback: Louder SwiftRage
qatarking24xd: LUL
tatsumiss: WutFace
cutza: click the logo
thealtchemist: LOUDER
Digital_donger: 2007 again FeelsGoodMan
myasovlavashe: PepePls
jamieemb_: I've been taking 300mg caffeine and 700mg l-theanine for about a year now and barely notice any effect
airinspiration_: fuck my ears
4a6f686e446f65: @QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE Yeah i figured :-P
linearpup: xD
alrealre: permanent hearing loss LuL
d4rkvist3r: Kappa Kappa
Joy_void_Joy: What languages?
axlebear: Actual banger
SigmaHeavyIndustries: DAS RITE
PhantomYTReal: Pen-test your own company
JAKWAI: cant hear my professor anymore turn it down ^^
xxblueshift: learn html
gtnftw: do all leetcode problems in 1 stream
lesserthangood: KEKW
haircutjimmy: lisp
thealtchemist: learn css
SSayMyName: nootropics not worth it
JohnnyThe_Hobo: get all the followers from an instagram page in python
SpaceGhost8: DNA conversion tool
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: oh man, I remember keygen music, it was so fkin garbage
lesserthangood: lets beat the turing test :)
aurumvorax421: crack passwords from games from the 80s
lulascoca: what are you trying to do with the dna?
pilliam2: do some stuff with trees
adroniser: english to french translator
joedcv: what do you think about gpt-3
angusmiguel: create a google clone
alrealre: Tinnitus PogChamp
insignia_microwave: add instant messaging to voice app
4a6f686e446f65: Code
joshperri: When the serialz scene was really an underground music scene.
4a6f686e446f65: CodeCode]
DrRobotvinnik: make a successful cartpole Kappa @georgehotz
4a6f686e446f65: Code
mexeroserisback: corona dna keygen
Landepbs: Python script to convert any song into keygen style
gigafact: dun dun dun
serRLNDT: thought's on apple silicon?
insignia_microwave: and video calls to voice app
linearpup: Do hackthebox
mattdougherty22: man hacks prosthetic arm to control music: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qSKBtEBRWi4&list=LLybT7HEIhhT_9jyupkCOUPg&index=15&t=2s
stianz0: writing a patch to the dna
SigmaHeavyIndustries: Learn HolyC
RapidEU: create a poc to exploit the new DNS CVE!
THE_korbi: best music pepePls pepeJAM
xxblueshift: pirate sony vegas 2008
bruh_imcoding: I'm wondering which tiling window manager you use on the Ubuntu computer?
PigeonsDontFlyFar: Mr Hotz what do I do if I like cock?
pielliepalie: Raaaaaaaaaave
aurumvorax421: http://keygenmusic.net/
insignia_microwave: add to voice app
skykanin: did you ever finish that coq proof for sqrt 2 is irrational?
4a6f686e446f65: Code
tatsumiss: W I N D OMEGALUL W
qezuke: f
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: F
Xiffix: F
jib1337: WINDOWS OMEGALUL
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: back
haizenburg__: lovingkeygen
mmi18: @PigeonsDontFlyFar i dunno find one i guess
SSayMyName: are you using 4K screen Hotz
samsara_c: f wait no. wait f
insignia_microwave: windows ew
axlebear: nathanBogged
asgargg: f frames f
maxschneider96: create an improved version of the tinder bot: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lvFAuUcowT4
haizenburg__: glad i watched today
PhantomYTReal: Love the internet company waiting over a year still no signs of normal internet coming
smokyakasteve: did you see the windows dns code execution
linearpup: do hackthebox.eu/
mashafique: Hey Geo. Great to see you live again PogChamp
smokyakasteve: nice am slow
axlebear: You can get a windows 10 vm for free from Microsoft now
thealtchemist: windows not sexy
insignia_microwave: nah let's just add to voice app to make it more revolutionary
cutza: lol the detune
VegaGalaxy: is the stream going laggy only to me?
xEHLE_: checkpoint research has an exploit plan laid out for server2012 i think it was https://research.checkpoint.com/2020/resolving-your-way-into-domain-admin-exploiting-a-17-year-old-bug-in-windows-dns-servers/
thealtchemist: Link to the music?
polysoulz_: wait windows have a VM?
polysoulz_: orcale is better tho
chemicalflash: how about the flatland reinforcement learning on trains competition https://www.aicrowd.com/challenges/neurips-2020-flatland-challenge
gtnftw: yes, it will overwhelming your computer
linearpup: implement this from scratch https://what3words.com/
C4TFive: sometimes overwhelming
janpoonthong: Are you in office
kklisura: Build some REST API with accessibility support. :D
joshperri: Just spin up a vm on AWS...
thealtchemist: NAND-2-TETRIS?
SSayMyName: stream going laggy to me as well
janpoonthong: !os
Arxedorus: what computer is he using?
mrusli70: Dude Hotz I send you YouTube message check it out
janpoonthong: macbook pro 16
d4rkvist3r: hard lag
pielliepalie: Lag gone
anguscupcake: build a device intended for the purpose of smoking tobacco
insignia_microwave: ass to voiceapp
ck1956: do a remote desktop with someone you know has windows
insignia_microwave: add
pielliepalie: And back lol
sondreal: too old LUL never too old bro
mrusli70: George did your MacBook Pro 16 have T2 chip crashes
tatsumiss: downloading windows in 2020 KEKW
linearpup: It would be fun to make an open source version of https://what3words.com/
SSayMyName: LUL
C4TFive: that Fiverr name 'SIDRed'
joshperri: You get cred...
jib1337: Using and caring about windows in the current year OMEGALUL
RapidEU: Hahahaha
mrusli70: https://finance.yahoo.com/amphtml/news/technology-leaders-designer-launch-maker-130000718.html
yeah_haey: Play a ctf
anguscupcake: windows is ass for everything but gaming
yeah_haey: Ill sub if you play a ctf
joshperri: Would you have been able to start comma without your hacking cred?
smokyakasteve: exploit is on github already
musabkilic0: make-a-lisp?
maxschneider96: @mrusli70 great stuff
smurfd0: do something with machine learning?!
mrusli70: Check livescience and science direct website on Coronavirus
xEHLE_: @smokyakasteve got a link?
xxblueshift: teach us plebs something
RapidEU: Predict Tesla stock using machine learning haha
musabkilic0: https://github.com/kanaka/mal
GiantSweater: how is it going
mrusli70: George heard of Copper mask
sondreal: I would invest in geohot
blabbernab: confuse them with tech jargon
RapidEU: who wouldnt? @sondreal
sondreal: RapidEU wheres ur investment star?
pielliepalie: How about making an opensauce selfdriving platform. OmegaLUL
smokyakasteve: @xehle_ https://github.com/ZephrFish/CVE-2020-1350
alrealre: breathing copper is going to trash their liver the organ LuL
thealtchemist: copper be expensive
mrusli70: Copper can kill COVID-19 in 4 hours?!!!
ephil01: Build your own gameboy emulator
RapidEU: @sondreal :(
sondreal: LUL
blabbernab: run it LUL
gtnftw: decompile Android apps and remove their ability to show ads, then recompile and release
xEHLE_: ofc its a troll OpieOP
RapidEU: copy it! what can possibly happen
insignia_microwave: oh fuuuucccck no
Lol_for_lol5: it's a rick roll
qezuke: teach C @georgehotz
cutza: program a program that programs
SigmaHeavyIndustries: bruh a bit.ly link
musabkilic0: JPEG decoder maybe
SigmaHeavyIndustries: MYSTERY LINK
jasondesante: we need neuralink dammit
hi_im_drakster: lmao
VegaGalaxy: Do the CVE please
JohnnyThe_Hobo: get a noob from chat and teach him to program @georgehotz
sondreal: when my boss asks why I spent 2 days on 7 lines of code Kappa
RapidEU: teach us god-level python
linearpup: Make an image super resolution model
maxschneider96: python ftw
tjbrother: You could write a program that writes programs PogChamp
eldac_kno: heard latest news about nanite in Unreal engine 5? In the last video they said it doesn't work with foliage and skinned meshes. Now pretty bummed about it, was hyped
whit_314: Pihole get you an installation option for curling and piping into BASH
GiantSweater: me :)
yeah_haey: Play a ctf Ill sub
Ne0Zer0: me :)
polysoulz_: C is cool
angusmiguel: i do!
her3hero: pick me, im a sub
maxschneider96: teamviewer
FargioFarmani: MEEE
musabkilic0: repl
mattdacentaur: i do
xxblueshift: me#
cutza: join.me
insignia_microwave: lol
THE_korbi: mee
samsara_c: csvode can collaborate i think?
Poisonslash: @georgehotz Just wondering how long have you been doing comp sci? I been doing it for 5 years now but your technical analysis skills and aptitude for this stuff is impressive.
ephil01: vscode has collaborative editing
TekniqueTrading: vs code liveshare
samsara_c: vs*
I_am_paranoid: repl.it has collab edit
xksteven: c vs c++ vs rust?
yeah_haey: PLAY A CTF ILL SUBSCRIBE
axlebear: me :)
pilliam2: me!
PhantomYTReal: Me?
NilsIRL: google docs Kappa
myasovlavashe: LUL
ephil01: so can atom
Burton1: yeah me
insignia_microwave: vscode live share
maikgs: Me
i1uvatar: Vs code live share
pilliam2: jupyter?
qezuke: @georgehotz i want to learn C , I've never code
maxschneider96: teamviewer?
NilsIRL: me
yeah_haey: C IS TOO EAYS MAN TEAHC SOMETHING HARD
haircutjimmy: embedding Lua in C
polysoulz_: repl it???
joshperri: tmux
Xiffix: repl.io
her3hero: me, im a sub PogChamp
patrickgekko: me
pielliepalie: Google colab?
insignia_microwave: vscode live chare
okeeeeeee: zoom
kvndsantos: I'm in
myasovlavashe: C Pog
polysoulz_: repl repl repl
Xiffix: repl.it
insignia_microwave: I'll do it
marschr: from the transistor
qezuke: pls I want to learn @georgehotz
Ne0Zer0: her3hero PogChamp
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: lol, that link
okeeeeeee: zoom into website
b2kemann: zoom
her3hero: PogChamp
tatsumiss: PogU
mrusli70: Ha ha ha ha
tatsumiss: Pog
polysoulz_: we love repl all my homies love repl
qezuke: @georgehotz invite me , i want to learn C
xksteven: PogU
i1uvatar: Just use vs code live share
musabkilic0: dont you need subscription for that?
jamieemb_: @georgehotz what do you think the future of cybersecurity looks like with continued incorporation of machine learning in the industry? I can't decide whether to do my masters in AI & ML or Cybersecurity
polysoulz_: i think there is share feature
samsara_c: lol here i come
Bankshots7: Hello G
haircutjimmy: Just do it in Vim @georgehotz
pilliam2: does george write java?\
linearpup: just try this https://codeshare.io/5OylLN
xxblueshift: Vim Diesel tutorial
her3hero: nice
insignia_microwave: vscode live share
FirstNameAndLastName: nice
polysoulz_: nooooooooooo
pharaohskaro: !uptime
RapidEU: codeshare looks good
thealtchemist: @jamieemb_ do what you think is fun, you can always educate yourself afterwards
her3hero: lul
tatsumiss: LULW
Plurmorant: PogChamp real programming language
norflin221: baba is you +
tatsumiss: KEKW
insignia_microwave: yeessss
Poisonslash: Teach us how to code in Arnold C PogChamp
parktype: lets have a minesweeper tourney KappaPride
xksteven: baba FTW
daTruth: I do repl.it collab editing with my class, you need to sign in with an account
eldac_kno: heard latest news about nanite in Unreal engine 5? In the last video they said it doesn't work with foliage and skinned meshes. Now pretty bummed about it, was hyped
xxblueshift: download templeOS
insignia_microwave: learn temple os
yeah_haey: Play a ctf man ill subscribe if you do or anything with vulnerability explotiation
qezuke: @georgehotz teach me C pls
b2kemann: lets do monads in haskell
polysoulz_: t0m C
xxblueshift: @insignia_microwave lol
RapidEU: Easy, github - "merge sort" adn then filter C
QUOTE_IF_SELF_AWARE: did george actually buy the dna sequencing kit?
thealtchemist: merge()
synthblade7080: WAYTOODANK
jamieemb_: @thealtchemist i love both, although I have more fun working with data than I do with any of the cyber stuff I've done. I know there's a steep learning curve to be good at Cybersecurity though compared to AI
tatsumiss: PogU
georgehotz: https://codeshare.io/5OylLN
Plurmorant: let's do it
JohnnyThe_Hobo: lets goo cbrahCheers
pielliepalie: @georgehotz how about duplicating this? https://nanovc.io/
pharaohskaro: surrreeeeeee
thealtchemist: @jamieemb_ I would think that ML/AI would give you more general information aswell, where cybersecurity is more focused on one area
Ahowe444: recursive calls to mergesort
cutza: laggy link
qezuke: @georgehotz it doesnt load
her3hero: link not work :(
GiantSweater: we broke the link
illdealer: we ddos the site
luchesijoao: HeyGuys
i1uvatar: Vs code live share?
gtnftw: recursive or nah
Ne0Zer0: LUL
JohnnyThe_Hobo: this is why communism fails
pilliam2: divide and conquer!
sondreal: this is why we cant have nice things!!!!!!!!!!
RapidEU: Lets show how team work makes it work
VegaGalaxy: You can use https://codebunk.com/ much better
parktype: @JohnnyThe_Hobo lmao
kalbermatteralan: can someone share the link again
arbitrandomuser: how do they do the whole C repl thing ?
xxblueshift: LUL
Digital_donger: this isn't going to end well LUL
GiantSweater: OMEGA LUL
SurfCat: 800 man code session, yeah LUL
axlebear: This stream is only for the learned
dynamite_dragon: NotLikeThis
Repunk: I don't think this is gonna end well ://
DeepBlender: Faith in humanity is lost I guess
smokyakasteve: FailFish
xksteven: LUL
tatsumiss: OMEGALUL
synthblade7080: TriHard
FirstNameAndLastName: someone keeps writing 696969
pilliam2: need a partition function
kalbermatteralan: could someone share the link again
phrixus_bro: uh oh
myasovlavashe: LUL
iskjmss: hardcoding legend
ELITEGAMS: NotLikeThis
Ne0Zer0: Twitch Plays MergeSort
thealtchemist: can't get on :(
Digital_donger: site is down :(
jib1337: Stop messing around
mrusli70: LoL!!!
kalbermatteralan: my chat was closed when he shared
qezuke: i cant join
qezuke: @georgehotz i cant join
polysoulz_: they cant do it
lemmywemmy: I think all hope might be lost LUL
smokyakasteve: LUL LUL LUL
georgehotz: https://codeshare.io/5OylLN
asdhxc: crashed site?
kvndsantos: I think codeshare is overwhelmed
GiantSweater: we broke the link bro
jamieemb_: @thealtchemist yeah true, the masters courses in Scotland are quite in depth when it comes to the particular subject you're studying
Denis0109: be NICE to GEORGE plss
kalbermatteralan: tnks
Digital_donger: it's dead :(
Poisonslash: The link is laggy af LUL
numbaeon: Site don't update
her3hero: I think we crash the site
qezuke: the link is broken
fstab: type it in the morge sort functiom
NilsIRL: kinda
mashafique: I never knew how PepeHansd
bloopsterr: site crashed?
insignia_microwave: I'm joining now I'll get it
kvndsantos: Codeshare is dead
pharaohskaro: bro the site won't even load lol
ck1956: DDOS
haircutjimmy: Link is dead
Ne0Zer0: hahaha
mendax1: link is broken
thealtchemist: link broke
tatsumiss: DDOS
linearpup: YES!
cutza: write your own code share app instead
kalbermatteralan: actually what we have to do?
hunt_fmj: nice clicky sound :)
t3rabyt3_: link is loading and loading
Roman182: LOL the whole website is actually down
xksteven: I does but I got a PhD so it not fair
qezuke: i cant see your code ! @georgehotz
Mobius5: wtf is mergesort?!?
insignia_microwave: we ddosed codeshare
jib1337: Yes write our own distributed coding app
knilecrack: I can't see it
insignia_microwave: its dead
insignia_microwave: codeshare is fucking dead
aloofbit: the site it broken :<
axellben: !uptime
qezuke: site is broken
musabkilic0: we killed it boysss
iotku: I don't know how to program I only know golang
PhantomYTReal: We did it we crashed a website
qezuke: Find another one
gtnftw: write a function that merges 2 sorted lists first
tatsumiss: even the site cant load up KEKW
pharaohskaro: Happy: time here. its DONE
pharaohskaro: from heapq import merge import time import random #m= random.sample(range(1, 100),99) #m= random.sample(range(1, 1000),999) #m= random.sample(range(1, 10000),9999) #m= random.sample(range(1, 100000),9999) #m= random.sample(range(1, 10000000),99999) m= random.sample(range(1, 100000000),999999) arr =m # sorting m with amerge sort def merge_sort(m): if len(m) <= 1: return m middle = len(m) // 2 left = m[:middle] right = m[middle:] left = merge_sort(left) right
anguscupcake: this is where I would just google mergesort and copy and paste it
musabkilic0: WutFace
FirstNameAndLastName: WHAT ARE WE DOONG AGAIN
iotku: twitch character limits be like
5GToren: LOL
janpoonthong: is this c or c++?
ph1shstyx: I finally made a twitch stream!
iotku: yes @janpoonthong
insignia_microwave: I just for a 524 error from codeshare
JAKWAI: why you code in vi?
Denis0109: vim is better than anything!
janpoonthong: what yes?
xxblueshift: vim is king
joshperri: #include <stdlib.h>
Denis0109: vim is love
thealtchemist: void merge( int arr[], int lower, int middle, int r)
arbitrandomuser: is some alarm going off in the background ?
Suspecthum: jesus
ph1shstyx: emacs
PhantomYTReal: Ah yes construction noises
insignia_microwave: down detector has codeshare down
sondreal: void mergesort(int a[], int i, int j){ int mid; if (i<j)
janpoonthong: what language is this c or c++?
5GToren: fod damn trash truck
lzrdkng21: C
cutza: ERROR
janpoonthong: okay
blabbernab: i'm learning so much
FirstNameAndLastName: I want to get timed out
qezuke: you write so fast that I DONT get anything
linearpup: include stdio.h
atthem0ment: @janpoonthong c
5GToren: you got a new basement?
lzrdkng21: Well could also be C++ since c is a running subset
iskjmss: >not using ml to merge sort
lzrdkng21: but c
cutza: merge merch
tatsumiss: hacker right there
tatsumiss: hackerman
linearpup: can't be done
quiqeh: whats merge sort?
xksteven: you also need the else
Roman182: Have to create a copy I think
Adolfich: what he is doing?
eddyrdqsk: u can
thealtchemist: I'm out, have a great day boooyyys!
vloood: Yes using pointers
FirstNameAndLastName: George just flexing on us on his INstagram
Dabux_: @georgehotz are you a good singer?
mashafique: It's time to unlock our galaxy brains
aensaevhaerne: yes pointers
zazealot777: FeelsGoodMan
iotku: Just load the NPM module it'll be fine LUL
Smoress: They usually give you like 10 minutes for this question. Wouldn't you have failed by now? Kappa
jamieemb_: @thealtchemist have a good one
insignia_microwave: codeshare is dead
gtnftw: split list in half repeatedly, until the size of list is 1, then merge the sorted lists, which is trivial
axlebear: Somebody’s grinded leetcode
M03x: @georgehotz which is harder competitive programming or CTF ?
oguwan: What's the point of memorizing
B1_Renekton: its easy if you have done segment trees
arbitrandomuser: poor backspace key
Talgathy: code is done on codeshare
RapidEU: Easier to go to github and find a sampel code LUL
pharaohskaro: link doesn't work but I am happy to post mine if you want it done
FirstNameAndLastName: His keys are triggernig me
snapcs1: cool
yeah_haey: Write a fuzzer
that_lad_koby: Finally made it to one of the streams! YES!
angusmiguel: what is * ?
yeah_haey: Write a fuzzer with RL for the mutation
RapidEU: pointer
metallsimp: pointer
pharaohskaro: @yeah_haey that actually takes quite a bit more effort
鼻史: @angusmiguel pointer ?
angusmiguel: what's a pointer @鼻史
snapcs1: lol...
ykahveci_: use temp?
RapidEU: address
knilecrack: don't you want to sort them 1st?
jamieemb_: @M03x After learning the key CP concepts and putting in a lot of effort you can solve most problems if you try hard enough. It's basically the same with CTF although you'll have to understand more technologies
insignia_microwave: let's just add to voice app
illogicalism: old man coding
asdhxc: @georgehotz chat was faster than you
Poizzoned: is that C++?
machineman101010: it is
knilecrack: no, c
myasovlavashe: C
machineman101010: C
Level_002: question, isnt there libraries that actually already do this?
knilecrack: yes
lzrdkng21: yes lol
Digital_donger: @Level_002 imagine using libraries in 2020 LUL
RapidEU: He's just having fun @Level_002
tatsumiss: yea its also all over the internet
insignia_microwave: click answered on voice app
zenderbeg: I haven't seen C++ in years xD
mendax1: it's c people
RapidEU: MERGE SORT does NOT exist on the internet, he is the first one who is gonna implement it.
ykahveci_: why he using pointer?
RapidEU: you were here!
enders0uld: where did you learned coding?
鼻史: @angusmiguel basically a pointer points to a memory location, and that's how we keep in touch with the memory space
illogicalism: kinda verbose answer
Level_002: because is c @ykahveci_
THX1342: chat is subpar today
esk0p: What is he trying to accomplish?
illdealer: easy to sort 0s lol
ykahveci_: @level_002 but he can handle merge without pointer
insignia_microwave: yo get a voiceapp id
pharaohskaro: code a mergesort
lucasfernsilva: dont know how to use pointers til today
eldac_kno: quality content
mendax1: can't you just use undef?
pharaohskaro: data structures and algorithms assignment / coding assignment in a coding interview
linearpup: Please use GDB
pharaohskaro: check line 29******
mryosta: whats up my man hotz
maxschneider96: Any other dart programmers here? (flutter)
axlebear: not using ZZ to save and exit vim PepeLaugh
鼻史: let's go with gdb peda LUL
loreleva: That’s c
insignia_microwave: @linearpup we use qira around here Kap0a
illdealer: linearpup he has his own dbg
insignia_microwave: Kappa
tdubey: are we back writing voice app the best 2020 Hotz corp startup?
pharaohskaro: your line 29 and line 40 are the problems
Roman182: Pog
Poisonslash: PogChamp
linearpup: oh yeah qira is the shit
cutza: how long will it take you to now write it in python?
yogi_1010: PogChamp
tatsumiss: PogU
chemicalflash: try the Flatland competition: (scheduling trains) https://www.aicrowd.com/challenges/neurips-2020-flatland-challenge
NilsIRL: @cutza sorted() Kappa
machineman101010: you gave 10min for that
lzrdkng21: its just annoying af to do that shit in c
linearpup: Please timeless debug mergesort
pilliam2: can you walk over it?
machineman101010: who*
J3rwin: lol
不好意思: yes python Pog
mryosta: what vim application do u use
FirstNameAndLastName: python is FAST boi
iotku: ngl I thought you were going to type import mergesort at the top
linearpup: vanilla vim
Poisonslash: Hacker mode activate
Appz_x: lol wtf
mryosta: oh whatt erminal is that that lets u open tabs
FirstNameAndLastName: George hacked my bank account and GAVE me money
NilsIRL: @mryosta tmux
joshperri: @mryosta iterm2
machineman101010: :DD
illogicalism: can we stop with the hack remarks, this is mid level developer stuff
oguwan: @mryosta iterm2
FirstNameAndLastName: George "Dont talk to my son" Hotz
maxschneider96: pace bro
Level_002: i sadly havent learned vim yet, I know some super limited vi and the hated "nano". More of a vscode guy or atom.
BrodatyWhiteBear: @mryosta vanilla like linearpup said. You can also check we're true in the bottom of therminal;
tatsumiss: hacking stream PogU
TRIMES1: hEY
snapcs1: vscode supports vim keybinds
oguwan: @Level_002 It's definitly worth learning
illdealer: illogicalism u never watched kung fury?
oxtuq: Learn it, then @Level_002
insignia_microwave: @level_002 vim is not for everyone but I think its great
FaceTheWolf: line 6 is missing a colon, right?
smurfd0: python is cheating :P converted some neuralnetwork stuff from python to rust was abit tricky
coProof: Oh no 🤦♀️
rifukkawa: @Level_002 learn emacs Kapp
rifukkawa: Kappa
oguwan: both are great
eldac_kno: hey completely out the field question, but don't you think that infinite sums explanation of zenos paradox is kinda overrated. Like change the problem to runners who pass a baton after they run half of the distance and then the question won't be answerable with infinite sums, because we assigned halves of the distance with a person
B1_Renekton: @georgehotz implement quicksort?
iskjmss: else if OMEGALUL
Smoress: It's incredibly sad that you do not get to write a lot of algorithms in what's seen as "programming". You just work with new requests and implement new logic + UI in the apps. That's the usual case at least.
machineman101010: line 6
rifukkawa: @oguwan emacs + evil is Kreygasm
oguwan: @rifukkawa LUL
haircutjimmy: How about doing it in Racket??
insignia_microwave: noice
Raiwo: Pog
cutza: nice
worraaa: what are we doing
Streetmaniac: what is he working on
yeah_haey: Make a mario rl bot or play ctfs please sorting code is boring
Poisonslash: @georgehotz Now write mergesort in genetic code Kappa
worraaa: merge sort in 100 languges?
iskjmss: Time both programs?
machineman101010: 2.36 min
pharaohskaro: posted mine in code share
gtnftw: now java
insignia_microwave: ruby
mryosta: scheme
RapidEU: GO
haircutjimmy: Racket
hi_im_drakster: java LUL
b2kemann: haskell
cutza: php!
themorph3: go
Digital_donger: php PogChamp
J3rwin: php KEK
ZuppaSalata: java
THX1342: brainfuck
RapidEU: Golang
worraaa: lean
metallsimp: LUA
oguwan: brainfuck
Timeisnotrelative: java
iwicdti: hoon
xxblueshift: ASSEMBLY#
lzrdkng21: StandardML
DuifjeRoekoe: assembly
7martim7: JAVA
DesolderingPump: My C is a bit Rust-y :P
colanzio5: APL
FaceTheWolf: brainfuck
worraaa: coq
BrodatyWhiteBear: golang
illogicalism: COBOL
bobrussel: PHP
Appz_x: html
Dabux_: fortran
metallsimp: LUAAAAAA
bloopsterr: binary
b1nk: NIM
reesync: haskell
Entrodox: haskell
THENEXTMOSES: go
snapcs1: brainfuck
haircutjimmy: LISP
zenderbeg: php
b2kemann: haskellhakell
phrixus_bro: rust
woodmann: Java LUL
metallsimp: LUAAAAA
mexeroserisback: julia
NilsIRL: brainfuck
turkkk: Java
EsKuel_: Brainfuck
RapidEU: Goalng
xxblueshift: ASEMMBLY
cutza: PHP
linearpup: GO
tornix98: SWIFT
b2kemann: HASKELL
mryosta: haskell
yeah_haey: Assembly
PhantomYTReal: Assembly
actuallymad1: HOLYC
7martim7: kotlin
kklisura: java
xxblueshift: ASSEMBLY
musabkilic0: haskell
blabbernab: haskell
Raiwo: PHP LUL
tomaesh: cobol
Mathews02: ASM
Streetmaniac: Motorola 68k assembly
sendmeintothevoid: GO GO GO
不好意思: LISP
djokaraaa: GO
Roman182: Ocaml
Xiffix: LUA
RapidEU: Golang
insignia_microwave: haskell
1donald: PHP
foon123456: JS
arty_a64: java
davidnsun: SML
knilecrack: assembly
ephil01: RUST
Appz_x: templeOS
codegito: java
OttoCavalry: COQ
pielliepalie: Golanf
Saeq1: assembly
metallsimp: LUAAAA
aleDsz: Elixir?
worraaa: COQ
pilliam2: java
probably_sleeping01: haskelllll
gtnftw: Dart
mattdacentaur: B
smurfd0: rust
4_realzies: asm
arbitrandomuser: JULIA
THX1342: ASM
kvndsantos: Swift
aleDsz: Elixir? Elixir? Elixir?
pilliam2: JAVA
kklisura: javascript
cutza: PASCAL
lulascoca: assembly
oxtuq: Ruby
adam_xxd: swift
pielliepalie: Golang
qatarking24xd: holyc
Level_002: C###########
HiyeTide: am i watching a wizard or something
machineman101010: ruby:DD
DrRobotvinnik: LISP
ToshiCZ: Pascal
janpoonthong: java
asdhxc: assembly
i1uvatar: Lisp
Impod10: Haskellz
tdubey: rust!!
maikgs: Assembly
O_Dunravin: Rockstar
Xiffix: make a strawpoll!
axlebear: assembly
jib1337: JavaScript
FirstNameAndLastName: C#
B1_Renekton: HASKELL
ZuppaSalata: machine language
advik_77: rust
arbitrandomuser: its ghc
b2kemann: yey
不好意思: assembly lul
Smoress: @georgehotz Cobol FTW
iotku: GHC OpieOP
Appz_x: templeOS.
arbitrandomuser: not haskell
data_dude: MORSE CODE
iwicdti: hoon
colanzio5: APL Merge Sort
Syrkaz: it's just macOS now :P
THENEXTMOSES: brew has haskell
THENEXTMOSES: brew
joshperri: holy. C
FirstNameAndLastName: George "I know every language" Hotz
turkkk: Binary
TasosTheLord: c++ LUL imagine that you have to declare the type of a variable on 2k20 WutFace
qatarking24xd: do it in holy c
leuza0: fortran
tatsumiss: coronaS
hi_im_drakster: make a poll @georgehotz
Syrkaz: `brew install haskell
turkkk: Binary!
JakeJ24: GO
data_dude: Morse
quinquanonagintilliard: emacs lisp
xxblueshift: assembly
Digital_donger: emojicode PogChamp
white_rose: what are you doing
haircutjimmy: Racket
coProof: monkaW
colanzio5: https://www.dyalog.com/blog/2014/12/quicksort-in-apl/
iskjmss: @quinquanonagintilliard pls no
pharaohskaro: use brew to install
smurfd0: you have a haskell-stack in brew
insignia_microwave: lol
aleDsz: asdf haskell?
weeva: 8051 plz
ephil01: Got any life advice
cutza: PHP
joshperri: Just use a repl...
Wrathedd: haskell DansGame
pharaohskaro: do you want another in the code share?
DesolderingPump: LOLcode?
gtnftw: should have chosen Dart smh
O_Dunravin: Shakespear
turkkk: Binary!
iskjmss: oneliner LUL
eldac_kno: hey completely out the field question, but don't you think that infinite sums explanation of zenos paradox is kinda overrated. Like change the problem to runners who pass a baton after they run half of the distance and then the question won't be answerable with infinite sums, because we assigned halves of the distance with a person
quiqeh: where can I start to learn about ai?
lzrdkng21: haskell's mergesort is around 6-7 lines
colanzio5: https://www.dyalog.com/blog/2014/12/quicksort-in-apl/
quinquanonagintilliard: you can use repl.it instead
colanzio5: APL is shorter
lzrdkng21: maybe less
bruh_imcoding: would love to learn how to use qira
lzrdkng21: theres no arrays
J3rwin: how did this stream turn into this
musabkilic0: https://learnxinyminutes.com/docs/haskell/
cutza: CODE IN TURING MACHINE
celike1ns: Use rosetta code
不好意思: can he write machine code
haircutjimmy: Yeah - Haskell is weird.
iskjmss: assembly next
lzrdkng21: let me check my old assignments lol
b2kemann: haskell is so smouth
lzrdkng21: nvm they were on a vm lmao
Avelansh: yo Goerge where you've been, hope everythings good
linearpup: just do ALGOL 60
white_rose: this is interesting
b2kemann: x:y:[] for two elements
white_rose: hey geohotz, what is the key board that you are using?
linearpup: hhkb
snapcs1: he loves that question
linearpup: lol
t3rabyt3_: lol
bigbawsboy: Do you have any plugins on your vim @georgehotz ?
Lite98: "fun -> corona" lol
kvndsantos: LUL
lzrdkng21: fak I only have insertionsort and quicksort in haskell on hand
Vinndy: solve this next in haskell https://www.reddit.com/r/programming/comments/hr3k1l/this_ship_city_programming_challenge_seems_pretty
haircutjimmy: TDD
Alpasfly: what is he doing?
weeva: haskell 13 lines
Agren__: mergesort elixir Pog
lzrdkng21: mergesort in haskell
white_rose: how is george able to analyze the output so fast lol
jamieemb_: wait wasn't this supposed to be teaching a coding noob? LUL
moodoo80h8: new here...what's going on??/ thank you for showing there are not only videogames on twitch
insignia_microwave: @white_rose you only have to look at certain parts
DevoE444: @georgehotz IS THERE ANY PYTHON PROGRAM FOR AUTOMATING CAPTCHA?
mattdacentaur: @jamieemb_ a noob for him is basically a cs major
musabkilic0: @moodoo80h8 he is coding mergesort algorithm in haskell programming language
FirstNameAndLastName: @white_rose MAGIC
white_rose: honestly george is so smart
jamieemb_: @mattdacentaur you've got a pouint hahaha
lzrdkng21: im pretty sure that using an auxilliary function would avoid the need for the let
moodoo80h8: @musabkilic0 roger that, much appreciated
yeah_haey: Write it in assembly or it doesnt count
linearpup: tr00 hack3r
Tsoding: That's a weird looking Python. Kappa
illogicalism: infinit
cutza: LOL
insignia_microwave: lol
tommee23: NomNom NomNom
Tsoding: `div` 2
musabkilic0: @moodoo80h8 np mate
parktype: you forgot to cherish her Kap
takkeo: @tsoding, HeyGuys
doomhammerorgrim: I'm a bit of a noob when it comes to coding, in what aspects is haskell better than python?
Tsoding: takkeo, sup :)
bobrussel: PogChamp ?
pilliam2: i need to start learning vim, anyone know how i can go about getting started?
linearpup: m̴͛͝ė̵̊ř̵̓g̸̑͗e̵͗̄s̸̋̉ö̴́̒r̵͇͘t̷̋͐
oguwan: @doomhammerorgrim not better, different
snapcs1: haskell is functional programming
Waldoqq: does mergeshort solve the coronavirus???? PogChamp
insignia_microwave: @waldoqq yes
oguwan: @doomhammerorgrim it's a functional language
alganet: vimtutor is a great start @pilliam2
parktype: @pilliam2 I had to use it for a class a couple years ago and the best thing I found was just to start using it regularly
FirstNameAndLastName: Hebrew is like Arabic Chinese
bobrussel: why code in a vim to begin with?
janpoonthong: When do you usually stream
janpoonthong: When do you usually stream?
nzack_: @pilliam2 just search for "basics vim movement"
doomhammerorgrim: Hmm, I'll have to look that up more in detail @oguwan @snapcs1
linearpup: george got his monads in a twist
xlbLoOdlx: The Legend
jaegerbott: Why would someone use Haskell
linearpup: to flex
xxblueshift: @janpoonthong whenever he wants
pilliam2: did he do his python mergesort recursively or iteratively?
oMYTHRA: @pilliam2 ThePrimegean has good videos on YT, he is also a streamer on here
JAKWAI: 90% of people here for ASMR :,D
pilliam2: @alganet @parktype @nzack_ @oMYTHRA thanks all <3
Joy_void_Joy: Oh some haskell <3
lzrdkng21: the pattern matching for the single element and pair are redundant no ?
JAKWAI: gg
linearpup: HOLY SHIT
alganet: pure bash now
bobrussel: good job
insignia_microwave: lol
haircutjimmy: Functional programming
Waldoqq: lol
turkkk: Binary
iskjmss: @georgehotz assembly next LUL
cutza: ASSEMBLY
linearpup: TR00 HACK3R
FaceTheWolf: brainfuck
xxblueshift: ASSEMBLY
ph4tal_: ASM
RapidEU: Goalng
OttoCavalry: COQ or RIOT
Level_002: @georgehotz c#
RapidEU: Golang
white_rose: GOLANG
jamieemb_: hahahahaha
Digital_donger: php or emojicode
haircutjimmy: Common Lisp
Impod10: ASM
JAKWAI: java
janpoonthong: brainfuck
programmingmouse: RUST
ZuppaSalata: LUL
OttoCavalry: COQ
weeva: 8051
xxblueshift: DO IT
Farkzax: ASM PogChamp
SigmaHeavyIndustries: Do it inside of TempleOS in HolyC you coward
Ahowe444: x86 64
qatarking24xd: HOLY C
hjklhjklhjkl2008: brainfuck
takkeo: maybe some GO
OttoCavalry: Coq
cutza: php
iwicdti: hoon
ltjrpliskin: you gotta do ASM
hjklhjklhjkl2008: turing tape machine
xxblueshift: HOLY C
iotku: golang gonna be the longest LUL
DaveSoDave: DO IT
Fettyawper: java
gtnftw: Dart
alganet: rust?
deva73: c++
santi_264: go
knilecrack: :D
hjklhjklhjkl2008: Q#
pielliepalie: Golang
oguwan: ASM will be like 300 lines LUL
cutza: go
Ne0Zer0: machine code Kappa
colanzio5: APL
lasercatboss: you wanna do the hard things or the easy things
santi_264: gooo
OttoCavalry: Coq xd
agravkire: Holy C
programmingmouse: GOLANG or rust
bobrussel: rust?
blabbernab: PUSSA
hjklhjklhjkl2008: dude Q#
santi_264: goo
insignia_microwave: nah let's do something else
RapidEU: Oh my god assembly!
B1_Renekton: i did it in assembly for college project
Ahowe444: x86-64
iskjmss: oh no no no no
codegito: holy c LUL
b2kemann: looool
xxblueshift: GG BOYS LUL
cutza: LOOL
Joooooooooonas: rust
pilliam2: java
knilecrack: yesssssssssssssss
synthblade7080: PogChamp
不好意思: LUL
MrBankster: nasm
linearpup: WTF LOL
eldac_kno: c#
ido1m: @georgehotz No, do ARM
FaceTheWolf: LUL
gigafact: wow
Rafabld1996: algol Kappa
qatarking24xd: LUL
whit_314: Yes
knilecrack: at leat give it a try
foon123456: js
RapidEU: OH MY GOD
OttoCavalry: PogChamp
oguwan: LUL LUL LUL LUL
colanzio5: Dyalog APL
SigmaHeavyIndustries: do it in 6502 8bit fam
white_rose: hhhahahaha
iotku: LUL
bigbawsboy: Do you use any plugins on your vim or its vanilla @georgehotz ?
oMYTHRA: ARM Assembly Pog
xxblueshift: CHEATER
THX1342: ASM
linearpup: xD
renerocksai: 8051 asm or 6502 asm
SigmaHeavyIndustries: do it inside of Mesen it has a great 6502 debugger
oguwan: Jebaited Jebaited Jebaited Jebaited
alganet: now refactor that assembly code Kappa
reesync: 5Head
anon543264: xD
THX1342: brainfuck
yolargg: golang!
Toastie1: hey that's cheating
colanzio5: APL
insignia_microwave: loo
Ne0Zer0: ez
programmingmouse: LUL
insignia_microwave: lol
jamieemb_: hahahahahha
DesolderingPump: D:
Impod10: Lol
Tsoding: AT&T DansGame
snapcs1: lmao
Ne0Zer0: LUL
FaceTheWolf: nice 👏
fstab: bruh
parktype: Kappa
Fettyawper: looool
doomhammerorgrim: Assembly LUL
hjklhjklhjkl2008: Jebaited
cutza: lol
santi_264: lol
ltjrpliskin: THATS CHEATING
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: :) Clap
oguwan: Jebaited
bobrussel: rust
Digital_donger: no cheating 😡
deva73: lol
jaegerbott: what is that
parktype: SeemsGood
dr_set: hey that's cheating :D
knilecrack: ahahha
lasercatboss: @georgehotz when did you last pussy out on sth hard wtf
Toastie1: LUL
Farkzax: LUL
colanzio5: https://www.dyalog.com/blog/2014/12/quicksort-in-apl/
alganet: Refactor it Kappa
Rafabld1996: speedrun
davidnsun: isn't the first merge pattern redundant? the second clause should match it too
janpoonthong: lol
Fettyawper: big brain
Ahowe444: He's not wrong
t3rabyt3_: PogChamp
RapidEU: Hahahah
takkeo: cheater KEKW
ZuppaSalata: LUL
metallsimp: LUA
whit_314: Cheating
eldac_kno: c#
weeva: looks good to me LUL
colanzio5: APL
bobrussel: @georgehotz rust?
ido1m: @georgehotz DO IT IN BRAINFUCK
janpoonthong: go
aleDsz: Elixir
3ygun: LUL
Snobbysteven: Wait a minute.......
aleDsz: Elixir Elixir Elixir Elixir
janpoonthong: golang
Fettyawper: 5head
kenqzzzz: You're becoming popular on twitch geohot @georgehotz
davidnsun: lol
linearpup: ALGOL 60 PLEASE
programmingmouse: rust
bobrussel: try rust?
Ahowe444: Perl
xxblueshift: HTML
Level_002: c#########
gtnftw: Dart
cutza: Pascal
darkronus77: RUST?
ltjrpliskin: lets do it in clojure!
Joooooooooonas: rust
snapcs1: LUL
Farkzax: HTML
hjklhjklhjkl2008: coq
DuifjeRoekoe: assembly
qatarking24xd: holy c
XeLiatH_: brainfuck
zokimacola: Rust
ck1956: write in COQ
pielliepalie: Sql
ido1m: BRAINFUCK
ZuppaSalata: SCALA
bloopsterr: brainfuck
asthmaa: vlang
oMYTHRA: Rust Kappa
foon123456: COUGHING monkaS
josergdev: COBOL
naaabed: rust
colanzio5: APL https://www.dyalog.com/blog/2014/12/quicksort-in-apl/
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: PixelBob
hjklhjklhjkl2008: use coq or agda
DesolderingPump: KEKW
programmingmouse: yeees
7martim7: kotlin
darkronus77: HolyC
iotku: My mom could do it in golang and she's dead
takkeo: pascal LUL
linearpup: FORTRAN
deva73: kotlin
legalogen: PHP Kappa Kappa
parktype: Haskell Pros PogChamp
eldac_kno: c#
DrRobotvinnik: LISP
janpoonthong: java
leuza0: fortran
Fettyawper: do you ever write java? @georgehotz
jamieemb_: C
reesync: C
AlgoRhythmical: php Kappa
xxblueshift: C
B1_Renekton: if you code in Rust it will be top of HN tomorrow
joshperri: At least use the optimizer
santi_264: c
knilecrack: are you practicing for some job?
Impod10: Swift
fstab: HotPokket HotPokket HotPokket
adnaann: Swift
pilliam2: c
pielliepalie: Julia
Rafabld1996: machine code
tjobremannen: swift Puke WutFace
hjklhjklhjkl2008: oh god oh fuck affine types
THX1342: brainfuck
Fettyawper: ever write java ? @georgehotz
Tsoding: oh no no no PepeLaugh
oguwan: uh yeah daddy gimme sum lifetimes
MJT_au: @knilecrack yes, there are jobs that require you to use random languages each day
parktype: The one he wrote for C is literally on the screen you pepegas
blabbernab: ls -al
aceboi69: #perl next
Farkzax: lisp
THX1342: LUL thatwas fast
xxblueshift: rm -rf
koudbi: Nex has to be Matlab
gtnftw: Test with an odd-length array too @georgehotz
agravkire: Are you going to hack ps5 ? Kappa
koudbi: next*
Fettyawper: do java @georgehotz
oguwan: Welcome to the Borrow Hell
ck1956: write in COQ
insignia_microwave: pip3 install mergesort
comatross: pascal next please
white_rose: what key board is george using tho
Sleeper009: R next please
clearsense: @georgehotz learn rust in y minuts has all main syntax
marschr: yay, the borrowchecker lol
clearsense: "learn rust in y minuts"
parktype: @white_rose care of timeout KEKW
Bretel: marge sort to linked list
white_rose: @parktype no risk no fun
ArcherCreatlol: lmao
Sleeper009: do Assembly next please
takkeo: RUST is so difficult than haskell Kappa
riseglory: learning rust?
SpaceGhost8: now this is Rust programming
themorph3: LUL
joshperri: Don’t forget mut!
Tsoding: GachiPls Cannot borrow as mutable because it is also borrowed as immutable
Killeraing: how far are we on a cure ?
parktype: @Killeraing we found it already Kek
smurfd0: https://doc.rust-lang.org/std/primitive.array.html
b2kemann: write size
Farkzax: code the MNIST NN in ASM
joshperri: We’ve cured unsorted lists
b2kemann: [int; 8]
marschr: hahaha the magics of rust
lasercatboss: powerpoint mergesort next
parktype: @joshperri lol
Muzyd: Abort
jamieemb_: @joshperri hahahaha
Roman182: LUL
hobocoder: NotLikeThis
takkeo: LOL
oguwan: You must return a reference too
b2kemann: [int; 8] in function
ZuppaSalata: LUL
Killeraing: i thought rust was a videogame :/
stephen422: LUL we gotta get Rust maintainers right here
DesolderingPump: Is FX888D good for casual use?
SpaceGhost8: everyone starts off fighting the borrow checker
stephen422: this is the classic 'First Rust' moment
jamieemb_: @Killeraing rust is built with rust
joshperri: So the Iron moment?
Tsoding: I wonder what's easier. x86_64 by hands or Rust. Kappa
ᅟᅟᅟᅟ: KeK
stephen422: @joshperri PogChamp
SpaceGhost8: LUL
hobocoder: LUL
Roman182: Dam feels good to have good compiler error messages
oguwan: & mut
SpaceGhost8: EZ
takkeo: @tsoding, definitely rust
trestorm: lol
Ne0Zer0: LUL
oMYTHRA: Where my Rustaceans at Kappa
bobrussel: so few lines ;D
Tsoding: @takkeo, sure Kappa
volkerai: which terminal is he using here?
arbitrandomuser: why dont you write a random text generator and compile its output till you get mergesort ?
iotku: Do not pass golang, do not collect $200
parktype: lol
joshperri: tsoding in the house???
ZuppaSalata: LUL
SpaceGhost8: panic WutFace
Tsoding: joshperri, PogChamp
jaegerbott: im panicing
joshperri: Do a joint stream with tsoding!
Tsoding: ( =_=)
TheZanke: the people that like rust really seem smitten by it
Vinndy: @tsoding Pog
M03x: he did the golnag verisn ??
Bretel: implement quick sort
Fettyawper: so tricky this guy
M03x: golang version *
musabkilic0: nope
name100015: x = x+y
insignia_microwave: LMAO
MiserableGarbage: LUL
stephen422: LUL parens PTSD
stephen422: Abusive parens
parktype: parenthesis monkaW
aleDsz: what about the language be OCaml or Dlang?
parktype: my spelling monkaW
voodoorama: is he implementing mergesort?
MiserableGarbage: parens trauma NotLikeThis
r__o__b__e__r__t: imagine using rust
qlutoo: you're about to have a bad time
insignia_microwave: @r__o__b__e__r__t imagine having to spaces between every letter in your name
oguwan: Oof
lzrdkng21: Bruh
Fettyawper: pls make an ai-compiler that corrects errors PogChamp
Toastie1: what do people even use rust for
volkerai: @georgehotz which terminal are you using?
pharaohskaro: okay well i put one in java and one in python in the code share. much love gotta go back to work
lzrdkng21: I guess it becomes more intuitive but why ?
oguwan: 800 ppl watching a dude code merge sort LUL
volkerai: in RUST
Streetmaniac: bruh i still dont understand mergesort
1am2stoned4this: LUL SeemsGood
alganet: @volkerai looks like the vanilla macos terminal with tmux inside
palac105: Dude its a Wednesday morning - why aren't you at work. I thought work was life.
livehoc: @georgehotz Title is still coronavirus follow up visit
Fettyawper: I'm rusty in that language..
NilsIRL: @Fettyawper https://doc.rust-lang.org/cargo/commands/cargo-fix.html
pharaohskaro: @Streetmaniac I am gonna watch til the end of the rust code out what don't you understnad?
volkerai: @Fettyawper oof
iotku: Thousands of people watching someone play videogames instead of merge sort LUL @oguwan
jamieemb_: gtg boys, enjoy the rest of the stream
stephen422: anyone who've been here long, how come george come to the Rust land
insignia_microwave: @streetmaniac did you not pay attention at all he did it 4 times in front of you do I need to write a babies first mergesort book
advik_77: F
oguwan: @stephen422 chat wanted
Toastie1: @stephen422 masochism
MiserableGarbage: poor fbi agent watching trying to make sense of this on his report
gigafact: programming is the only game in the future
Fettyawper: @NilsIRL perfect
mattdacentaur: HeyGuys
renerocksai: parens again :-)
stephen422: Ah, classic chat at work
palac105: if the universe is all random, why sort anything?
lzrdkng21: @Streetmaniac you basically split the array until you have n arrays of size 1, then you merge them back sorting them at each merge
Streetmaniac: ok dont bully me i just dont understand how merge sort is any different than any other O(n) sort
illogicalism: image the if parentheses he will have to remove
haircutjimmy: Cannot take any more Rust. Gotta go. Bye!
volkerai: which sort is O(N) lmao'
lzrdkng21: Its not O(n)
ArcherCreatlol: dude brackets wtf 😠
Vinndy: @tsoding how would you rate George's rust skills from noob to 5Head
Streetmaniac: n2
stephen422: Rust designers should have been real burned by Lisp
Streetmaniac: woops
volkerai: it is O(Nlog(N))
volkerai: average case
Mamba12: its nlogn
volkerai: yeah
Tekrific: @palac105 cuz it's only pseudo-random
Toastie1: @Streetmaniac its o(nlogn)
RapidEU: ewww rust
volkerai: Rust do be gay ngl
Streetmaniac: i know its nlogn
volkerai: some sorts have an upper hand given certain kind of input
volkerai: in most average cases quick sort is best
volkerai: but some cases certain sorts are better
Mamba12: some sorts are faster than others depending on the data you give it
Mamba12: yeh
stephen422: idiomatic rust - that's not real, run george
volkerai: @Mamba12 this dude out here spittin' facts
Fettyawper: Dear FBI agent. this is a code for producing meth LUL
B1_Renekton: merge sort is nlogn in every case (best, worst, average)
oguwan: Use Box
agravkire: Do you do any hacking these days ?
arbitrandomuser: nextum quantumsort
Poisonslash: LUL
Sniky83: what is he trying to do actually ?
Streetmaniac: hack cia
mattdacentaur: mergesort
Poisonslash: Save the world
pilliam2: is it worth using merge sort for every sorting case or is that overkill? or should i just memorize insertion sort lol
palac105: is this a corona stream or a freaking rust stream
Fettyawper: mergsort array @Sniky83
musabkilic0: mergesort in rust @Sniky83
alganet: I'm here for the google searches
arbitrandomuser: you should use the library sort
aymen_kh: what is he doin this time? ratirlCoffee
Poisonslash: @palac105 It's a rustona stream
Streetmaniac: dont libraries usually use quicksort
arbitrandomuser: this took longer than haskell
arbitrandomuser: are we still on rust ?
Sniky83: thanks
iskjmss: what are his splits rn?
arbitrandomuser: i tuned out a bit
iskjmss: mergesort speedrun any%
Fettyawper: so many lines MonkaS
Poisonslash: PogChamp
insignia_microwave: noice
puckered_starfish_sniffer: python uses timsort
mattdacentaur: @iskjmss WR incoming
palac105: i'm only staying here because i'm on company time. not a fan of this rust
hobocoder: lmao
Ne0Zer0: LUL
semPa_: PogChamp
stephen422: LUL
TheKnopex: LUL
stephen422: We got rust!
bobrussel: LUL
1am2stoned4this: PogChamp
Tekrific: burn
linearpup: XD
SigmaHeavyIndustries: DAS RITE
semPa_: PogChamp WR
foti_kasparov: Do Euler project
Roman182: Now prove mergesort correct in Coq
FaceTheWolf: now brainfuck?
programmingmouse: WR PogChamp
SigmaHeavyIndustries: but it was safe fam don't you feel safe?
insignia_microwave: these streams are great
PhineasPhreak: do it in pure assemblyh
Tekrific: rust is rusty
Vinndy: now benchmark them
Farkzax: lisp
linearpup: FORTRAN NOW
TheZanke: php
MyLoveSachan: hi. new to the stream. what is he coding? adn what language?
cutza: which one is faster
musabkilic0: lisp
MiserableGarbage: gachiHYPER HYPERCLAP
Ne0Zer0: hahah
Mathews02: FORTRAN!
Thiagovgamg: 4k display?
Streetmaniac: motorola 68k assembler
DrRobotvinnik: LISP
musabkilic0: common one
aymen_kh: ratirlRiot ratirlRiot ratirlRiot ratirlRiot ratirlRiot
gtnftw: Test with an odd-length array too @georgehotz
Fettyawper: what are you doing
SigmaHeavyIndustries: download the TempleOS ISO and do it in HolyC you coward
GrumpyJeff_TTV: ADA
arbitrandomuser: can you profile them ??
Poisonslash: @georgehotz What language do you think would be fastest to code mergesort?
doomhammerorgrim: BASIC
pharaohskaro: lol mine in python and java are pretty esoteric hahaha
g____: brainfuck
ArcherCreatlol: do it in piet
pielliepalie: Do Julia
TheZanke: cobol
Ne0Zer0: julia
stephen422: ADA
linearpup: FORTRAN
qatarking24xd: holy c
pielliepalie: Julia
Bretel: implement quicksort .. complex is O(logn)
arbitrandomuser: what about SPEED?
insignia_microwave: If I buy a meeting can I just say bullshit
alganet: esoteric: piet
btastical: yea do it in HolyC
skatan87: brainfuck
nbkar: brainfuck!
Bowlgirlblergh: HolyC
smurfd0: https://docs.rs/ndarray/0.12.1/ndarray/ this is for rust what numpy is for python
b2kemann: do it in javascript using only strings
bruh_imcoding: https://github.com/aemkei/jsfuck
alganet: brainfuck is too hype, piet is the shit
SigmaHeavyIndustries: TempleOS has a JIT compiler and you can jump to any function from anywhere else in the editor
TheZanke: write Shakespeare next
Fettyawper: run every single one > write a run
SigmaHeavyIndustries: the whole OS is basically scriptable C
aymen_kh: ratirlRiot
alganet: TempleOS HolyC +
arbitrandomuser: use vim to modify all the files
RapidEU: C doesnt have 2 i think
Bowlgirlblergh: HolyC would be the greatest thing ever
btastical: HolyC, do it
RapidEU: ah hs doesnt
ArcherCreatlol: do piet PogChamp
insignia_microwave: who bought the meeting with comma
myaocat: hello!
anguscupcake: period
myaocat: what do you think about🦀?
stephen422: q.e.d.
Bowlgirlblergh: do HolyC. do it for terry. BibleThump
mattdacentaur: gg
b2kemann: lets benchmark
Poisonslash: I wonder how many keyboards George has gone trhrough LUL
palac105: Are you on PTO? It's freaking Wednesday man, godamn AI aint gonna solve itself
linearpup: PROLOG
aymen_kh: ratirlKing
coconutiraqi: MY BOO
Fettyawper: mergesort in PHP LUL @georgehotz
qatarking24xd: LUL
alganet: you can get a VM
coconutiraqi: how r u GEORGE?
myaocat: @bowlgirlblergh did he say how he design the language? im very curious on how you write one ..
SigmaHeavyIndustries: no you gotta run the TempleOS ISO
ck1956: https://github.com/coq/coq
asdhxc: you need temple os
coconutiraqi: I miss you dawg
pharaohskaro: so quicksort in the code share?
alganet: the TempleOS vm is pretty easy to use
cutza: clap
btastical: you gotta do it in templeOS
anguscupcake: Owner of the company doesn’t have PTO lol
不好意思: gg
drumbledope: hello :)
insignia_microwave: hope your meeting goes well btw
gigafact: this was fun
robg_10: templeos
b2kemann: BENCHMARK
num_air: more coding !
qatarking24xd: only 2 mb
asdhxc: rip Terry Davis
myaocat: hello u the boss PrideLove
1am2stoned4this: Kreygasm
Digital_donger: terry BibleThump
AlfaAnanasz: what kéyboard? i want my timeout and the answer too
linearpup: How much did you earn this stream? :P
aymen_kh: ratirlRiot LOT OF VIEWS ratirlRiot LOT OF VIEWS ratirlRiot LOT OF VIEWS ratirlRiot LOT OF VIEWS
t3rabyt3_: SeemsGood
xVipzin: greetins from brazil
joshuena: After the technological singularity AI will make this look too easy. Will be interesting to see where things go from there.
MiserableGarbage: smoking fingers NotLikeThis
SigmaHeavyIndustries: it's basically just C but you gotta do it in TempleOS which is the fun part
Ne0Zer0: LUL templeos
musabkilic0: HOLY C
codegito: Pog
qatarking24xd: templeos.org
DrRobotvinnik: do LISP ArgieB8
b2kemann: cause you're handsome
myaocat: run it in qemu Kappa
gtnftw: dart next time
xSlash333: anyone care to quickly explain what hotz is programming? :)
Fettyawper: such a troll language LUL
b2kemann: looks=viewers
joshuena: coronavirus is nanomachines merging with us
Fettyawper: HolyC
foti_kasparov: YOU HAVE TO KNOW GOD
SigmaHeavyIndustries: its simple AF just run the ISO fam
btastical: yea boyyyy
oguwan: @xSlash333 A sorting algorithm (mergesort) in multiple languages
alganet: this is going to be fun
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: its not 64 bit
xSlash333: @oguwan cheers
1am2stoned4this: LUL
Joooooooooonas: @fdfdfdfdfdfdff it is ?
alganet: it is 64, TempleOS doesn't run 32bit
qatarking24xd: no sound card
Fettyawper: 86-64
anguscupcake: very unknown
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: oops im a silly boy terry knew what he was doing
bananaconda: @oguwan in which languages did he do it yet
theknip: Now do a real sorting algorithm bogosort
joshperri: github.com/jamesalbert/holyc-for-linux
myaocat: LUL
white_rose: what is he doing w/ vbox
qatarking24xd: PogChamp
TheLongWillow: Hi guys! What is ge doing?
MatiGoG: POGGERS
Bowlgirlblergh: PogChamp
okeeeeeee: PogChamp
SigmaHeavyIndustries: when you get in you can open up the edit with like Ed("main.HC");
1am2stoned4this: PogChamp
xxblueshift: PogChamp
musabkilic0: PogChamp
white_rose: PogChamp
insignia_microwave: it dont go bigger
SigmaHeavyIndustries: and when you hit ESC it'll save the file and quit
Digital_donger: 640x480, that's what god wants
bruh_imcoding: spaghetti sort
alganet: Now we need a parrot screaming in the background
atthem0ment: what is that?
hjklhjklhjkl2008: 640 X 480, as god intended
SrArmando: host+C?
Bowlgirlblergh: @alganet LUL
lzrdkng21: the best os ever made
JanTSV: HE wants it like that
palac105: Resolution is fine, you just getting old
oguwan: @bananaconda C, Haskell, Python, Rust
M03x: no
myaocat: trashOS
M03x: you need to install it
qatarking24xd: PogChamp
hobocoder: it's beautiful!
anguscupcake: the only God-certified operating system
Fettyawper: defying god with that resolution
shakecross: windows xp install when
alganet: the UX is glorious
Bowlgirlblergh: when are you going to make your own OS dedicated to god @georgehotz
xSlash333: mic needs more static noise to properly programm in temple os
linearpup: please maintain aspect ratio
iskjmss: literally a sin to scale the templeos resolution
musabkilic0: what you are doing is a sin, god didnt intented it to be big
joshperri: 640x480 thus sayeth the lord
Roman182: LUL
skandd1: hahaha
Koduck007: Pog
semPa_: dont use capture mode
Impod10: What is that ?
pharaohskaro: lol your computer doesn't want you to be doing this ahahaha
aymen_kh: ratirlRiot ratirlRiot ratirlRiot ratirlRiot ratirlRiot
foon123456: temple os POG
xEHLE_: its not lag its how god wanted it 😠
god_damn: @georgehotz thoughts on bio-luminescent african-americans working for the american central intelligence agency
Digital_donger: terry used vmware
lef_xyz: virtualbox is dogshit
Tekrific: it's unholy
myaocat: god died
stratussox: the best programmer in the word xd
musabkilic0: you can never blame templeos
Fettyawper: HAHA
joshperri: You can just write HolyC in the shell
DesolderingPump: @lef_xyz D:
foti_kasparov: DO EULER PROJECT PROBLEMS
Fettyawper: i need a zanax
wutango: LUL
hoff_meister: beautiful
oguwan: The dude did this all by himself like holy f
grenaderaven: WutFace
1am2stoned4this: Kreygasm
stratussox: HolyC >> spacex
Raiwo: LUL
reesync: LUL
SigmaHeavyIndustries: make sure to take your TC out
joshperri: Install the vm tools
Joooooooooonas: I mean it was impressive what he coded
Pryetranka: LUL
anguscupcake: Looks good to me
Ne0Zer0: LUL the holy grail of programming
SHAVEYY_: interpreted C?
xSlash333: the world only had one designer, so why would templeos need another one? Kappa
SigmaHeavyIndustries: I32
themorph3: lol
Tekrific: this will induce a migraine attack
SigmaHeavyIndustries: instead of Int
oguwan: Jit compiled C LUL
foon123456: Holy C best C
JanTSV: No int
stratussox: ¨"IT HAS 3D GRAPHICS" - Terry A. Davis
joshperri: He ded :(
Poisonslash: I've only heard m,emes about templeOS... Now I know why LUL
aurumvorax421: how dare you, God is the designer, he passed the design to Terry
liberscience: LUL
Fettyawper: such a useful language :)
1am2stoned4this: BibleThump
anguscupcake: Greatest programmer who ever lived
hobocoder: rip terry BibleThump
bananaconda: dont forget your precious channels points guys -380
Digital_donger: press F7 for godword BibleThump
Sniky83: why using temple os xD ?
Fettyawper: @Sniky83 for the memes
musabkilic0: -380 TRAIN
myaocat: lol
oguwan: @Sniky83 To code in HolyC
SigmaHeavyIndustries: bruh you gotta use the TempleOS editor for true experience
stratussox: @georgehotz will comma.ai support TempleOS? xd
joshperri: Oh hey! cash that shit out -380
Poisonslash: LUL
iskjmss: or just talk to someone for half an hour for 1K LUL
anguscupcake: Uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Xiffix: 20-OFF :DD
OzOfVanilla: Lets do it
robg_10: what
MatiGoG: what do you think about rustlang?
Big_America_: Big_America_ subscribed with Twitch Prime.
myaocat: pls gift me i will write any code for you in python/rust/swift
SHAVEYY_: I think there is a setting to type your clipboard
OzOfVanilla: Save the world
1donald: what
不好意思: -380
Sniky83: okey
foti_kasparov: No u can't
nudax: is that templeOS?
atthem0ment: Pepehands
mattdacentaur: how do i highlight?
Joooooooooonas: there is no cheatin gin templeOS LUL
btastical: maybe reduce the power of the VM? its not needed anyway
semPa_: -380
OzOfVanilla: Sub to save the world plz
joshperri: Vim == cheating
Digital_donger: yeah no clipboard support LUL
TusKaN_BaNaNas: how much to get dna sequenced?
atzehji: chat what are we doing right now?
SigmaHeavyIndustries: Ed("main.HC");
qatarking24xd: You can create a file
hobocoder: he thought it was going to be an easy copy paste LUL
stratussox: deep learning in TempleOS with holyC??????
k_o_r_a_l: !time
alganet: I don't think TempleOS implements clipboard :/ You could send it char by char using VBoxManage on a serial port, but that would take some time to figure out
god_damn: god will challenge you in ways you cant forsee. The mouse bug is one of them.
darkronus77: play some holyC games :D
Ne0Zer0: this is honestly amazing LUL
teerv: i take a small brake and i come back to templeos jessus
Werrdd: press shift f6 for science
SHAVEYY_: is this all ASCII characters loool
insignia_microwave: gift me sub and I will write a surprise program in python
Fettyawper: "Hello World" in TempleOS is literally God speaking
Dicki__Minaj: would u pls show ur room and table setu
linearpup: install ghc in templeos
Big_America_: I'm on a higher plane of existence now that I'm a subscuber.
joshperri: Paste in TempleOS XD
liberscience: nano vs vim
1am2stoned4this: VoteYea
hobocoder: run it natively Kappa
SigmaHeavyIndustries: Dir;
myaocat: give it more RAM or download one Kappa
oguwan: Lol the autocomplete feature works
Level_002: wtf are we doing chat
god_damn: if you seemingly encounter glow-in-the-dark african americans in the next 3-5 business days i'd suggest you be weary
atzehji: gosh this dude makes me think I should start using vim. gosh I already know it would be fucking frustrating
musabkilic0: god has other things to do too, alright? it can be laggy sometimes
SigmaHeavyIndustries: @oguwan you can jump to any function from the autocomplete its nice
gunz4kids: @georgehotz have you tried nim lang? its so good I can't write python anymore
Fettyawper: Why is there no epileptic warning before launching TempleOS LUL
boogiebrice: oh god rip king terry
anguscupcake: Vim is ez
Ne0Zer0: its gonna blow
insignia_microwave: lol
hobocoder: LUL
okeeeeeee: DONT DansGame
Prinz_Sissi: hahaa :D
skandd1: LUL
GrumpyJeff_TTV: LUL
flickapotamus: WutFace
atthem0ment: Pepehands
Ne0Zer0: #cancelculture
iotku: LUL
myaocat: you can do it. use sudo for help
Shubsterz: !uptime
不好意思: but it's holy c
foti_kasparov: you go in hell
Aenopixel: the holy spirit can puppet you
pilliam2: D:
Koduck007: does it use master and slave
Poisonslash: Dude apparently the guy that made TempleOS did it what having manic episodes LUL I can literally see his insanity in this shit LUL
musabkilic0: thats a sin
Tekrific: Pope just died
joshperri: Best streeeeeeeem
Fettyawper: i hope the holy spirit puppets me
lef_xyz: when he is back everyone spam dont tell him PepeLaugh
linearpup: best geohot stream to date
NotKarar: Holy C Kreygasm
onpoint212: i have no idea whats happening Kreygasm
insignia_microwave: do vimtutor LUL
Fettyawper: don't tell him
lef_xyz: oh shit
Raiwo: @Poisonslash If you havent watched youtube documents about Terry... You should
foti_kasparov: government is pupping us
TheKnopex: @georgehotz why are you not streaming from the cloud?
semPa_: PepeLaugh he doesn't know
insignia_microwave: @theknopex he moved out
joshperri: Sony wrote the PS5 on TempleOS
joshperri: Safe
btastical: is this due to the virtualbox scaling thing?
Joooooooooonas: Codetools
Ne0Zer0: you gotta let the Holy Spirit guide you
Poisonslash: @Raiwo I'll check it out, thanks
zuggles: @georgehotz templeos and holyC are a real representation of every hacker movie ever, just add some more cgi.
SHAVEYY_: Kappa write a driver in HolyC to get networking
Digital_donger: terry used vmware
yungtoad4: FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan
btastical: terry used vm
aurumvorax421: 30fps=cinematic experience
SHAVEYY_: Terry used qemu iirc
solitaryyy: Best OS
aurumvorax421: terry used a vm on ubuntu
Streetmaniac: your eyes cant see past 24fps anyway
iotku: Terry used VMware because it had good PC Speaker emulation
lithiumx4900: You can get hardware acceleration with Parallels I think
musabkilic0: ctrl-m for menu
foti_kasparov: Try on comma 2
btastical: https://github.com/jamesalbert/HolyC-for-Linux
Bowlgirlblergh: not holy enough
zuggles: thou are not devout.
lzrdkng21: QEMU Kappa
mattdacentaur: it was designed so you can repent yourself
myaocat: run in qemu
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: you dont deserve holy C george
uduver: i guess you are not worthy enough
YouPowerRush: haha
joshperri: Oh you only gave the VM 2 CPUs?
SHAVEYY_: @georgehotz Terry has a tutorial on how to get it working with qemu Kappa
MRTOMZ123: hi @georgehotz
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: does temple OS has emacs?
Digital_donger: heresy D:
foxubu: Chewing ice? :o
joshperri: It dedicates tasks per CPU with no preemption
TheLongWillow: Guys why he is writiing merge sort in all languages can you tell me ? :D
iotku: Ported unholy C LUL
Fettyawper: that's an unpopular opinion
chemicalflash: OBS stream from temple OS ?
Ne0Zer0: you take that back about urbit LUL
pigporkman: What are we doing chat?
gunz4kids: i love it
Fettyawper: no one
solitaryyy: i like nim
gunz4kids: nim is the best!
myasovlavashe: OMEGALUL rbit
mattdacentaur: @TheLongWillow because
pigporkman: Did he do urbit already?
myaocat: use nano! apple engineers use nano!
iotku: cia foundation LUL
reesync: cia-foundation LUL
kuj0oo: wasn't the guy who made temple Os mentally unstable? lol
joshperri: I want geohotz to say Terry was a genius
catull: how about zig Lang?
myasovlavashe: LUL
1am2stoned4this: LUL
insignia_microwave: @kuj0oo yeah he killed himself
SHAVEYY_: @georgehotz You can get it working with qemu https://archive.org/details/TerryADavis_TempleOS_Archive/videos/2017/2017-01-03T00%3A03%3A00%2B00%3A00+-+TempleOS+-+Terry+QEMU+Install+(DWZChggg2Wg).mp4
Digital_donger: HolyC is pretty similar to C
mattdacentaur: @kuj0oo he was just a messenger of god
Fettyawper: ok i agree LUL
Plurmorant: Temple chapter 2 verse 5
kuj0oo: oh my
Ne0Zer0: let the hun be with you
weeva: that is disgusting
btastical: or try holyc for linux https://github.com/jamesalbert/HolyC-for-Linux
booberrystew: how about q?
joshperri: Kernel
qatarking24xd: LUL
mozforshort: D:
PhineasPhreak: lift1 lift2
Plurmorant: D:
wutango: FeelsBadMan
hobocoder: come on george D:
iotku: can confirm
bananaconda: D:
lef_xyz: true LULW
god_damn: most anyone will ever do
NotKarar: 100% true
reesync: FeelsBadMan true
YouPowerRush: ruyuF_SG
BrodatyWhiteBear: FeelsBadMan
Ne0Zer0: someone call the burn ward
Fettyawper: if only i had Gods will in me, i would do more LUL
grenaderaven: u dont kno me
Raiwo: True FeelsBadMan
Digital_donger: he built his own compiler
mattdacentaur: FeelsBadMan
pilliam2: TRUE
kuj0oo: ugh built my gamer chair yesterday
GrumpyJeff_TTV: NotLikeThis
Werrdd: He was a paranoid schizophrenic and he built an OS that is pretty impressive
linearpup: what are you eating?
pilliam2: pepeHands
KryekGG: @georgehotz should i start learning programming with C or Python?
foti_kasparov: Building the atomic bomb
uiq3eu: how is going with backspace.ai?
doomhammerorgrim: FeelsbadMan
anguscupcake: He was a genius
pilliam2: @KryekGG python
yungtoad4: "struck by a train"
joshperri: Truth
Fettyawper: yes you are
Kyoto_o: why would i work for google and facebook
Jrfjekr: TRUE LULW
pigporkman: Are you talking about Curtis Yarvin?
linearpup: have you met Richard Stallman?
mryosta: school
PhineasPhreak: I work at Sony
breadhamandegg: em :)
Fettyawper: start-up
FargioFarmani: me
Digital_donger: assuming we have jobs Kappa
foti_kasparov: student
zuggles: im an SE for a VAR
aurumvorax421: NEETs
insignia_microwave: school
mozforshort: NEETs
hobocoder: Kappa
breadhamandegg: me :)
bananaconda: student
Plurmorant: ?
Prinz_Sissi: me ofc :D
Ahowe444: student
myasovlavashe: me :)
okeeeeeee: university XD
qatarking24xd: im in high school
data_dude: My job is watching this stream
joshperri: I like philosophical hotz
myaocat: me
teerv: unemployed students
xxblueshift: student
rutynasirrutyna: SAP/CRM
parktype: I watch
tatted_Schnitzel: comcast IOT test automation
booberrystew: google
semPa_: student
NotKarar: NEET.
janpoonthong: From Thailand
pigporkman: school
phsverdadeiros: poker player
btastical: software engineer
不好意思: NEETs
Raiwo: Me raiwoBlush
Pryetranka: me :)
grenaderaven: me
iotku: NEET
korojy: student
darkronus77: devops engineer here
Vinndy: Amazon
num_air: phd student
prafaeltsantos: college grad
Xiffix: Mechanical Engineer
linearpup: HERE Maps
masterRiddi: Cyber Analyst
mr_ahab_: 16 y/o
ido1m: Tesla
rodeocrazy: Ad tech
asdhxc: studying cs at uoft
lzrdkng21: About to enter master in foundations of cs
FargioFarmani: google engineer
marj444n: intern
tonycoco2001: Googler.
hjklhjklhjkl2008: i used to intern for google but i'm back at school doing research
rstk1: Net infra
solitaryyy: micro$oft
synthblade7080: student
b2kemann: phsyics
Bowlgirlblergh: we are all robots MrDestructoid
kuj0oo: SE
ck1956: I work for a state gov
uiq3eu: backspace.ai
knilecrack: I work for BMW
BrodatyWhiteBear: Invoices/management .NET C# webapp
Solias_3: students procrastinating :)
Sleeper009: Lottery winner
foti_kasparov: Phd
THX1342: what's a NEET?
Prinz_Sissi: watching my furture hahah
onemanarmy1147: mechanical engineer
linearpup: HERE
Ne0Zer0: embedded software
mattdacentaur: im a master baiter
TheLongWillow: Ubisoft
quinquanonagintilliard: devops
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: Im doing my Masters in mechanical engineering, but I do computational fluid dynamics
breadhamandegg: garbage collector :)
TusKaN_BaNaNas: Data Scientist at tiny old private company
sakateo: Aeronautics
palac105: African refugee learning how to code
nevermoreee: senior university
janpoonthong: Students
pilliam2: CS student in Melbourne
rigerzz: Dutch IoT company
Feeldat123: i am on my first job working with go
insignia_microwave: student
Markidane: Almost 24, unemployed, learning skillz
jbpratt: :( i work in finance industry, IT security that no one cares about
SHAVEYY_: comma.ai
renerocksai: researcher, AI, DL
pigporkman: PANW
christianthefalco: Google, working on Dialer app
EpicDreamGod: Amazon
myaocat: i watched u since 2 years ago
Fettyawper: i work at comma.ai @georgehotz
coconutiraqi: Devops engineer
Aenopixel: procrastinator
gomi_01: student
MatiGoG: unemployed
lef_xyz: netflix
l_mbert: Web Dev Agency in Germany
localcanofdutchgold: warlord hacker
nbkar: biotech researcher
glorybrew: NYSE
ido1m: SWE at Tesla
B1_Renekton: cs 2nd year, 99.91 percentile
god_damn: gamer B)
Kyoto_o: what do you think on writing emulators as a hobby? @georgehotz
onpoint212: work at arbys
recursive_x: my cellphone
leuza0: Junior developer
salman2301: selftaught freelancer
SHAVEYY_: comma.ai @georgehotz
O_Dunravin: CEO of google
ak0ya_: quant finance
Higor12cs: vw dealer
Czleqq: mechanical engineer
prafaeltsantos: MIT
xxblueshift: @georgehotz Professor Hotz
anguscupcake: Work as dev remotely
Vinndy: $AMZN
DrRobotvinnik: I teach computer music
mlejva: Founded software company to make development easier
Saeq1: web dev
doomhammerorgrim: work in Deep learning at a startup
Repunk: eye bee emm not so proud loool
breadhamandegg: CEO of Tesla :)
num_air: Phd student in Germany
atzehji: data science student
btastical: software engineer
rodeocrazy: Ad tech in Toronto
dorkmo: accounting
illogicalism: DELIVERY HERO
kimmie_hedd: Nasa
rutynasirrutyna: Oracle
silentslayer88: What do you think about nvidias self driving ?
b2kemann: viking from norway
Solias_3: robotics engineer student
mr_ahab_: 16 y/o
sendmeintothevoid: NSA
bruh_imcoding: student
grenaderaven: janitor
FirstNameAndLastName: Doctor
tatted_Schnitzel: IOT testing
xxblueshift: computer science student in ireland
breadhamandegg: Thank You :)
Ne0Zer0: all comma ai employeese slacking off watch george stream LUL
Grav48: Highschooool
quinquanonagintilliard: You know, a little escape from the real world
iotku: I'm doomed to fail because I don't have a job and my skills are unmarketable
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: Im doing my Masters in mechanical engineering, but I do computational fluid dynamics. gonna do my PhD. fuck a real job
bomberloli01: Student
sakateo: Aeronautics
silentslayer88: What do you think about nvidias self driving Software?
recursive_x: North American Security Agency
onpoint212: i sell hacked poker chips
ido1m: @georgehotz I work at commaai. I'm the cleaner.
Fettyawper: i write code for kindergarden math
Sleeper009: PPP loan hacking
myaocat: im going to mars
solitaryyy: What if you work for Raytheon @georgehotz
localcanofdutchgold: @xxblueshift what school?
pigporkman: @georgehotz what do you think about Urbit/Curtis Yarvin?
ag3n: I work at Lufthansa
xxblueshift: @localcanofdutchgold ulster uni in belfast
yungtoad4: I work at the NSA
god_damn: @solitaryyy got offered a job there, is it good
parktype: MonkaS
knilecrack: what's nim?
atthem0ment: @georgehotz would you buy tesla short shorts for 69.420$ ?
Fettyawper: @yungtoad4 same and the CIA
yungtoad4: I am your NSA agent that watches you
linearpup: Which is the cleanest looking language?
localcanofdutchgold: @xxblueshift belfast DansGame
silentslayer88: What do you think about nvidias self driving Software?
recursive_x: lol
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @georgehotz what do you think of Chainlink (LINK)?
xxblueshift: @localcanofdutchgold Dublin DansGame
whit_314: Wish Elon modelled them.
hobocoder: bullshit Kreygasm
atthem0ment: LUL
janpoonthong: @yungtoad4 NSA dont have to watch this stream
localcanofdutchgold: @xxblueshift assumption andy WeirdChamp
solitaryyy: @god_damn I don't work there, I just meant working there in terms of "do no evil"
Raiwo: Kreygasm
Thiagovgamg: display 4k?
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: MY LINKY STAY SUPER STINKY
xxblueshift: @localcanofdutchgold Cork DansGame
Fettyawper: elon and grimes is part of the a secrets society
myaocat: if someone leaks ida pro its good or evil Kappa
localcanofdutchgold: @xxblueshift Jebaited
al3frop: @georgehotz hey George, what do you think about the future of low level security, especially binary exploitation?
christianthefalco: @georgehotz did you watch the lex interview with Joscha Bach
xxblueshift: @localcanofdutchgold OMEGALUL
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4hR4rDbJPM4
O_Dunravin: fork hay
gutschilino: do you know a good site to learn python?
anguscupcake: Gib tendies pls
b2kemann: coronoa boring, hanging out fun
Bowlgirlblergh: @georgehotz did you see that the chance of "the big one" happening on the san andreas fault has tripled since the ridgecrest earthquakes last year?
localcanofdutchgold: @xxblueshift TriHard
linearpup: brew is slow af
Fettyawper: What's your goal with the coronavirus project? @georgehotz
recursive_x: kaleiSip
illogicalism: You can add and commit with one command
insignia_microwave: killall brew
linearpup: is zsh posix compliant?
al3frop: yep
mattdacentaur: NotLikeThis
linearpup: cool
silentslayer88: What do you think about nvidias collaboration with Benz on self driving cars ?
parktype: holy shit @fdfdfdfdfdfdff thats a good video
linearpup: i use fish and it ain't
zuggles: @georgehotz without giving away your IP-- would you be able to talk more about comma's approach to AI/ML compared to tesla? i watched an interview awhile back where your approach at "modeling the way humans drive" was so interesting. would love to hear more in the future. how one accomplishes said task.
myaocat: dudeamax99.github.io
Fettyawper: killall bro
god_damn: @myaocat thats huge
hobocoder: @myaocat that's a cool project OpieOP
insignia_microwave: @silentslayer88 they will use openpilot
logicny: @georgehotz tabs or spaces?
insignia_microwave: @logicny spaces
b2kemann: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Curtis_Yarvin lol at his wikipedia
Fettyawper: who here uses Atom?
b2kemann: curtin yarvin the alt-right golden boy
linearpup: @logicny he's more of a retab kind of a guy
quinquanonagintilliard: use repl.it ...
Grav48: gnnn
Ne0Zer0: also gotta install nimcompoop
Poisonslash: Operation Nimrod PogChamp
soreox: @georgehotz What kind of computer are you using? :)
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @Fettyawper EMACS or bust
ziyad_sk: @Fettyawper does anyone still uses atom ?
myaocat: @soreox toaster pro
name100015: nim rod FeelsDankMan
gunz4kids: @georgehotz use https://github.com/alaviss/nim.nvim/
daxyxy98: @soreox Comodore
maizeq: Is that iterm2 + tmux + vim?
Fettyawper: @ziyad i do LUL
myaocat: @georgehotz see my project https://dudeamax99.github.io
myaocat: won first place at hackathon
eaterenrgy: @maizeq just tmux + vim
Fettyawper: @quinquanonagintilliard is relp.it good?
al3frop: @georgehotz hey George, what do you think about the future of low level security, especially binary exploitation?
maizeq: @eaterenrgy what's the terminal he using
foti_kasparov: python2 like
insignia_microwave: @maizeq iterm2
JRHonda121: What is he doing?
myaocat: @al3frop you can defend stack smashing and memory corruption using rust but not logic bugs
ziyad_sk: @Fettyawper vscode gang here , once you use it , you cant go back lol
eaterenrgy: @maizeq he's on a mac buddy.
quinquanonagintilliard: @Fettyawper good! it also support vim key binding, I'd say that's a better way to try a new language instead of installing things to your computer that you know you only use it once
insignia_microwave: @ziyad_sk but I did go back to vim
al3frop: @myaocat it will take at least 15 years for Rust to be close to c/C++ popularity
al3frop: al least
quinquanonagintilliard: or emacs keybinding if you prefer
linearpup: IDA or GHIDRA?
soreox: @georgehotz what do you think of Force Dark Mode for Web Contents through chrome://flags ?
kingherring: based Nim! we use it in production ;)
gunz4kids: @georgehotz your type is seq[int]
ziyad_sk: @insignia_microwave vim is a must but sometimes u need that visual ide with extra super powers
myaocat: @al3frop facebook is using it for Libra. And for ARM the pointers are protected
Digital_donger: lua Kappa
hjklhjklhjkl2008: yea do matlab Kappa
GrumpyJeff_TTV: lua
insignia_microwave: @ziyad_sk I dont though
PhineasPhreak: @eaterenrgy tf does that mean
kingherring: o/
quinquanonagintilliard: lua
lef_xyz: nope
myaocat: Julia
shanumbra: Me
insignia_microwave: add to voiceapp
parktype: matlab KEKW
SHAVEYY_: Jython Kappa
al3frop: @myaocat pointer authentication is bypassable
iotku: I think people just use nim to say that they use nim
B1_Renekton: 12 people ig
al3frop: not a silver bullet
kingherring: use seq not array, unless you want C-style array
eaterenrgy: @kingherring Hello!
kingherring: oh shit, sup
myaocat: @al3frop you cant bypass PAC without having the key
parktype: Sikh PogChamp
christianthefalco: All my homies are sikhs
cleofn: make a i
solitaryyy: Seek
kingherring: George hotz says to never call him but he never replies to email. interesting SeemsGood SeemsGood
hotplay: I am really curios about asking the question...but I dont want the timeout Kappa
MrYasser2194: what is this? are you not in the cloud anymore ?
breadhamandegg: @hotplay just do it 4Head
maizeq: What status bar line is that at the bottom of his terminal
linearpup: tmux
egghead0102: just joined, what is he coding?
Vinicius_Scallop: Sup hotz
hotplay: anyone in chat know the model? before asking PogChamp
foti_kasparov: Random shit
eaterenrgy: @maizeq Ive told you tmux.
kingherring: @georgehotz any data visualization efforts at Comma.ai ? We do data visualization at scale. Previously did work at Samsung on their GPU team visualizing GPU data
noodlelicker: yyjAYAYA
kingherring: Nim is incredibly based. I hope George enjoys it
christianthefalco: What does based mean
linearpup: @kingherring browser based visualizations?
NotKarar: based on what
qatarking24xd: LUL
6majed: ttyped*
kingherring: @linearpup yep
bubblesnot: What is he building
yungtoad4: Jesus boomers in the chat
god_damn: @christianthefalco the 'based mean' is a form of average commonly used in biology
6majed: why nim ?
PhineasPhreak: yooo is this iterm2?
JRHonda121: JRHonda121 subscribed at Tier 1.
mattdacentaur: yea
pilliam2: if i had 5% of this guys skill id be set
sangi_med: hello
kingherring: ease of use of python, power of lisp, and performance of C or close to it :)
kingherring: what more could you want?
bubblesnot: Is he building a time machine in 20lines or less?
christianthefalco: Based apparently means addicted to crack cocaine
6majed: Nice
JanTSV: -1
maizeq: @PhineasPhreak it's iterm3 the lesser known sequel
mattdacentaur: nice
yardanico: @georgehotz Nim slices are different, use p ..< len(a)
yardanico: in m2
MrYasser2194: just because he can, this basically anwser 90% of questions xD @6majed
PhineasPhreak: @maizeq dont u dare @ me i'll bang u outsidfe lidl bruv
yardanico: you're going out of bounds with len(a)
pharaohskaro: weeeee still doing merge sorts? arrrdddddd
yardanico: since seqs start at 0
foti_kasparov: Code in Brainfuck
6majed: @MrYasser2194 LUL
yungtoad4: based just means its cool because it does its own thing
garykillleesang: Leopold 750r so nice PogChamp
MrYasser2194: @6majed he's in the zone right now so don't expect any awnser xD
lef_xyz: LUL
mattdacentaur: LUL
kingherring: don't be mean to Nim!!!
jgiljr: what lang is he using?
bubblesnot: Is this R?
eaterenrgy: @garykillleesang with reds Kreygasm
god_damn: @jgiljr hes English
yungtoad4: kekw
solitarynative: bros is he programming in nim now
jgiljr: programming language
kingherring: @eaterenrgy tfw want to stream but all my shit is proprietary
lef_xyz: @jgiljr dogshit nim
JumpTwiice: what are we doing now? i was away
Koduck007: light levels low: monsters might spawn soon
jgiljr: lol
kingherring: @lef_xyz I will kill you
bubblesnot: Him
yardanico: @georgehotz it's "var p1"
yardanico: "var p1 = 0"
yardanico: not "let var"
kingherring: kek
lef_xyz: @kingherring D:
insignia_microwave: take calls on voiceapp
yardanico: @kingherring I like nim a lot too :)
eaterenrgy: @kingherring Looks like everything is working out though!
recruit_main707: you can use 0..<len(a) so that its not inclusive. and you either use let or var, not both, let is basically inmutable var
b2kemann: is nim for datascience?
yardanico: @georgehotz also it's "and" not &&
qatarking24xd: @garykillleesang is he not using hhkb
bubblesnot: Why nim and not python?
yungtoad4: haHAA
mattdacentaur: he already did python
lef_xyz: haHAA
pilliam2: how often does this guy stream?
b2kemann: once every fullmoon
solitarynative: rarely in bursts
insignia_microwave: @pilliam2 like once every 5 years
bubblesnot: Once a quarter
JumpTwiice: what is he coding?
bubblesnot: It’s in his twitch contract
oosed: whenever a pandemic comes around
garykillleesang: Types so fast YouWHY
lef_xyz: 10 times a yaer
lef_xyz: 10 times a year
6majed: @JumpTwiice Merge sort Kappa
JRHonda121: What are your thoughts on the OpenCV AI Kit and do you see any opportunities to use it in the world of Comma.ai?
eaterenrgy: @kingherring Whenever you do stream I'll be there!
MrYasser2194: @JumpTwiice been watching for 20 mins and still don't know
phantasy1: I'm totally cluess on what's happening in this guys screen but it is somewhat entertaining
bubblesnot: This is highlighted text.
recruit_main707: nim has a gc
smurfd0: covid riskchart by xkcd https://xkcd.com/2333/
recruit_main707: you can also use arc if you wat
insignia_microwave: take a call on voiceapp
linearpup: @JRHonda121 I checked it out recently. looks pretty neat. but the depth estimation looks very inaccurate
JumpTwiice: nymn PogChamp
kingherring: Nim's GC is different though. the new GC is ARC and reference counted
xxxdeja: What happened to the living room? ;-;
foti_kasparov: Brainfuck
Ne0Zer0: hahaha
6majed: it's cool
pigporkman: Are you going to do Hodor?
Bretel: implement quicksort
recruit_main707: brainfuck or riot
her3hero: sick
JRHonda121: Yeah @linearpup I'm shocked how much backing is behind it on Kickstarter
Maxii254: !git
charlesbukowski: wait what is the goal here? writing mergesort in multiple languages?
Maxii254: !githyb
her3hero: !git
Samael616lilith: why so weak testing???
god_damn: will PR fetlang
soreox: Lmao you call yourself a georgehotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
Maxii254: !github
Koduck007: saved from creepers
DrRobotvinnik: cheers SeemsGood
insignia_microwave: have a good rest of your day
Samael616lilith: why so weak testing?
blakeswelt: !githyb
yardanico: nim's not on kickstart :P
JRHonda121: No the OpenCC AI Kit
mattdacentaur: Lmao you call yourself a georgehotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
gigafact: I like this streaming time. It's optimal for EU
JRHonda121: OpenCV
christianthefalco: @georgehotz did you watch the lex interview with Joscha Bach?
yogi_1010: lol
janpoonthong: !github
her3hero: let's code a shell mmo next stream PogChamp
bubblesnot: This is another highlighted message.
dr_set: lex interview with Joscha Bach was amazing
Ne0Zer0: mattdacentaur LUL
her3hero: rpi?
Koduck007: what it do
her3hero: it does ai
codingquark: My SD cards keep dying, rpi are too risky that way
kingherring: I'm sending George an email
linearpup: OpenCV has a competition along with it https://opencv.org/introducing-oak-spatial-ai-powered-by-opencv/
prostidude221: 'cute' LUL
eldac_kno: have you seen latest news about Nanite in Unreal engine 5? It doesn't work with foliage and skinned meshes. I was so hyped though
silentslayer88: Can you give your opinion on nvidias self driving software ?
codingquark: Joscha
insignia_microwave: if I buy a meeting does it have to be professional
bubblesnot: What about 1000 twitch points?
FaceTheWolf: <3
t3rabyt3_: PrideShine
ZuppaSalata: LUL
bigbawsboy: Do you have any plugins on your vim @georgehotz ?
soreox: pretty mmuch the same @bubblesnot :)
Mussels: What courses did you take at CTY when you were younger? I took robotics and forensic anthropology. robotics was cooler.
yungtoad4: This is a stream of diaper masks
bubblesnot: Nvidia caters to the rich
yungtoad4: Diaper mask streams for life
foti_kasparov: Can we add more languages?
omniilismo: what do you think about neuralink?
b2kemann: what ? someone ordered a meeting to shittalk? but whyy
parktype: Lmao you call yourself a georgehotz fan? I'm fucking loaded on channel points bro. I highlight every message because I'm just that jacked. Try talking in chat again when you're a true fan
yeah_haey: Are you jewish
solitarynative: real
ZuppaSalata: LUL
pigporkman: Would you ever get into quant trading?
solitaryyy: The Geohot 2020 Sorry Tour
lef_xyz: monkaS
prostidude221: you look high as shit for someone that doesnt smoke LUL
codingquark: ha ha
drewc830: LUL
d4rkvist3r: dafq
MrYasser2194: some people*
leander_ms: Commski never works
GrumpyJeff_TTV: LUL
recruit_main707: favourite streamer just for that sentence
soreox: PogChamp
bigbawsboy: Wait I missed that @georgehotz ... so no plugins?
christianthefalco: Oh geohot didnt like the bach interview?
uiq3eu: Do you think that idea behiond backspace.ai is still valid?
Koduck007: true
Ne0Zer0: LUL
RapidEU: @parktype same
foti_kasparov: BURN COMMUNISTS
solitaryyy: Would you consider CCP communist?
jgiljr: shrooms?
drewc830: nice to see a techbro who isnt a commie
parktype: Communism has failed everywhere it's been tried
bubblesnot: CNN will twist that to “geohot supports communism”
leander_ms: Is that a new appartment tho?
yungtoad4: This guy says he doesnt smoke lmao man smoked on stream
Ne0Zer0: the sxsw talk was amazing LUL
uiq3eu: Do you think that idea behind backspace.ai is still valid?
prostidude221: FeelsAmazingMan Drugs
loopylol: muh drugs taylor96Alex taylor96Alex
linearpup: have you ever tried DMT?
codingquark: I agree
recursive_x: lop
leander_ms: FeelsAmazingMan
JumpTwiice: capitalism is communism for the rich LUL
RapidEU: Your competitor Elon Musk smokes
yungtoad4: No no no the guy in chat said you dont smoke
Ne0Zer0: drugs are for nerds
kingherring: what drugs do you take though Geroge hotz? if you want to be high
bubblesnot: He smoked the autism
hartator1: yesterday?
foti_kasparov: COFFEE IS A DRUG
yungtoad4: WE all know you amoke
leander_ms: Respect it dude
drumbledope: KKona
uiq3eu: Do you think that idea behind backspace.ai is still valid?
prostidude221: so fucking true
duncansclarke: nicotine is harder imo
codingquark: I skip coffee every weekend as a rule
salman2301: My Bro says you almost all the time use Drug that's why u hype most of the time
eldac_kno: try nicotine then
janpoonthong: What kind of weed you like to smoke?
soreox: tab or space @georgehotz ? :)
Zanfr1980: whats with the topic? somethingnhappened?
hartator1: Did you ever try to micro dose LSD?
b2kemann: computation
foti_kasparov: Are you 7?
god_damn: Inspiring words
Poisonslash: Weed for me has been the hardest thing ti quit just cause life is so fucking boring lately, especially with the covid locldowns :(
leander_ms: That is not necessarily true tho
JRHonda121: Do you believe Elon when he said they are very close to Level 5?
DrRobotvinnik: will you use Nim again? @georgehotz
yungtoad4: you make 1k a year we know it
jgiljr: nice dose of dmt from the pineal gland?
duncansclarke: Tabs are 1 finger stroke bro
Ne0Zer0: this is a tab-free zone
janpoonthong: What kind of weed you like to smoke?
soreox: haha <3
yungtoad4: "man of the people" makes 1k a year lmao
Perrrooooo: Didnt you feel like you lost braincells from smoking weed everyday :D
bubblesnot: Gateway drug
lasercatboss: lets be real here the only reason to not be on modafinil permanently is tolerance
lef_xyz: caffeine is easy too after 1 week
mazsociety: How hard is it to quit chewing ice cubes Kappa
muffclap: do u think weed helps you when you code
prostidude221: lmao
SigmaHeavyIndustries: tabs are great get a grip
Mussels: withdraarll
eldac_kno: sugar is hardest to quit
solitarynative: caffeine is the devil
ZuppaSalata: LU
marschr: backspace.ai reminded me of the openai code gen from comments that sam altman showed the other day
bubblesnot: Coffee is a gateway drug
wazaR: For me is freakin cigs, hard as shit @georgehotz
SigmaHeavyIndustries: all that weed you're smoking is making you think tabs are bad
Poisonslash: @georgehotz I wouldn't really say I'm 'addicted' to weed, more of that i'm just so bored these days there isn't much to do other than work and work out.
solitaryyy: lack of oxygen lolz
eldac_kno: sugar>> caffeine
codingquark: I cannot work at all after cigs
duncansclarke: you never enjoy nicotine the first time around
mmi18: have you ever watched rick & morty?
bubblesnot: I can read, but i can not remember.
pharaohskaro: holy shit hahahahahaha
localcanofdutchgold: lul
chillguy269: LUL
leander_ms: Can someone tell me what his Chrome Theme is called? LUL
Ne0Zer0: yikes LUL
ZuppaSalata: LUL
Muzyd: BRUH
bluespeck: Ever had problems focusing? how do you get around that?... having such a scatterbrain, and can't focus on anything for longer than a few minutes lately
Koduck007: broooo
solitarynative: vaping is fun with low nic
yungtoad4: KEKW
soreox: Mine is sugar tbf :/ and aspartam
prostidude221: its called snus here, pretty popular in norway
iskjmss: that's one way to avoid cigs for the rest of your life
mattdacentaur: LUL
Koduck007: lrn2ettan
kingherring: my email is sent ;)
b2kemann: in norway and sweden we have snus
weeva: nicotine poison is terrible LUL
bubblesnot: No that’s the good stuff
mattdacentaur: 5Head
JRHonda121: Do you believe Elon when he said they are very close to Level 5?
yungtoad4: My vices: sugar and freebase cocaine
that_lad_koby: vaping is more fun tbh
bubblesnot: Swallow the chaw
joshperri: Nicotine sucks ass
codingquark: I in fact feel bad, lethargic after cig
arbitrandomuser: what about coffee?
eldac_kno: do you eat sugar?
linearpup: have you done psychedelics?
charlesbukowski: nicotine should be illegal
muffclap: weed + coding?
b2kemann: snus is the best way to get nicotine
MrYasser2194: my uncle droped a 10 year smoking addiction, can't drop the coffee
pilliam2: @georgehotz how do you stay focused?
andreadaedra: have you tried LSD?
myaocat: can you cheers ? i am drinking coca cola :)
Poisonslash: Cigs actually make me sick af. I'm convinced i'm allergic to something in it but I guess that's a good thing LUL
charlesbukowski: i mean illegal
uiq3eu: Do you think stuff like GPT-3 gonna open new possibilites?
janpoonthong: have you tried LSD?
foti_kasparov: Suggest any book from your bookshelf
ag3n: How can you earn money with programming, besides an actual job? Like working on the side.
charlesbukowski: not possession, just selling it
yungtoad4: You already know geo is all drugs legal type guy
reeldill120: sup pimp. doin some ctfs?
wingdini: best strain?
bubblesnot: There is already a sin tax on it
wazaR: @georgehotz everything should be legal, if you die, i mean, its your problem
pharaohskaro: lol why?
charlesbukowski: massive companies shouldn't be able to get people addicted to their products through a chemical dependence
eldac_kno: yeah it's impossible to avoid sugar in the US lol
charlesbukowski: that we can at least control
andreadaedra: have you tried DMT?
Dicki__Minaj: Would u pls share ur room and table set up?
bubblesnot: Have you tried a butt plug?
codingquark: That's sad, yes
bigbawsboy: @georgehotz I’m guessing the vimrc on your repo is out of date?
arbitrandomuser: @bubblesnot why would anyone try hunter2?
num_air: Talk some more about BACKSPACE ! What tools do you think are missing ?
veryape69: have you had anal sesh with your homies
prostidude221: LUL
RapidEU: lmao
solitaryyy: dat butt plug life
crawcraw66: thats addictive
pxlluu: pxlluu subscribed with Twitch Prime.
soreox: what?
feed2: you should try
lef_xyz: that escalated quickly
myaocat: what do you think aboht apple lie in past they won't merge OS and now they did Big Sur is iOS with macOS
mattdacentaur: yea
pilliam2: @georgehotz how do you stay focused?
charlesbukowski: have you tried kissing your dad?
bubblesnot: Butt plugs are a gateway drug
prostidude221: someones asking the real questions LUL
Ne0Zer0: LUL
b2kemann: loool
foxubu: Shall I ban him? :D
egilsdrups: I'm green leaf in programming :D :D :D :D :D but as now i'm on twitch i'll try to learn from George ..... OMG them Drug questions are like scream for help :D :D :D :D weed is good as it stimulates neurons to creates new connections , but as you mentioned if someone smokes and doesn't study then their brain will stay on low iq mark :D :D :D :D
her3hero: im so confused
linearpup: Has Joe Rogan invited you yet?
RapidEU: have u ever had an addiction to livesex cams?
leander_ms: But does a technology like that not mean that people are going to be jobless? Like web desginers? Or will that happen with AI regardless
phrixus_bro: hahaa
marschr: the “retina” theory of AI
janpoonthong: @georgehotz how do you stay focused?
codingquark: lol you guys
bubthefi5h: Lmao
b2kemann: hahah
andreadaedra: have you tried DMT?
Dicki__Minaj: Would u pls share ur room and table set up?
RAMBOxBEAST: What's the latest video game you've played?
bubblesnot: @foxubu no :(
Perrrooooo: Are you planning on streaming Hackthebox once more? Loved those :)
solitaryyy: We need the Geohot podcast
chillguy269: :(
eldac_kno: wait you said caffeine is most addictive thing, but quitting sugar is much harder
NotKarar: FeelsBadMan
prostidude221: why?
ZuppaSalata: D:
myasovlavashe: BibleThump
pharaohskaro: dude your joe rogan podcast would be SICK!
yungtoad4: Sadge
arbitrandomuser: then maybe he shouldnt put it up on youtube
sharknight11: did you get gpt-3 api access?
Poisonslash: @georgehotz How long have you been doing comp-sci for? I'm only 5 years into it but your technical analysis skills and aptitude for this stuff impresses me.
RapidEU: 800 viewers is popular
leander_ms: I am not a computer science student, I study economics LUL
qatarking24xd: you are already famous
mattdacentaur: we can see your nipples
whit_314: if your twitch gets too popular we'll see you on bitwavetv!
pigporkman: Thought you wanted to be instagram famous?
weeva: fuck that
god_damn: naval has a bit about this
amuzinc: @georgehotz hopefully they wont get too popular
kingherring: @georgehotz CEO to CEO, how do you continue to program when there is so much business things to do?
lasercatboss: i feel like if this gets popular just code more and the morons leave again
myaocat: are you for or against apple (git) merged iOS and macOS?
kingherring: so many*
wazaR: should we just watch on y2be? sthen
muffclap: how much attention do you pay to developments in quantum computing
MrYasser2194: rich > fame
boogiebrice: kind of edgy
dr_set: if it gets to famous just put a programming challenge to filter out the casuals
bubblesnot: Serious question how can AI be implemented within cyber security
eldac_kno: good looks are like fame but better
crestedpuffin: xD
chillguy269: LUL
janpoonthong: lol
d4rkvist3r: ok
andreadaedra: you're CPO: Chief Party Officer.
ImNotTrolling: you are a god
chillguy269: DPRK
kingherring: LUL LUL
yungtoad4: No that guy just wanted us to know he was a ceo
solitaryyy: Vladimir Hotz
muffclap: how much attention do you pay to developments in quantum computing
t3rabyt3_: more money more problems
codingquark: lul
andreadaedra: CBO: Chief Buttplug Officer.
veryape69: what's your bideltoid?
egilsdrups: so true
amuzinc: look at irans full name
amuzinc: LUL
MrYasser2194: its like markting
solitaryyy: LOL
leander_ms: They need to put them in there to make people believe LUL
prostidude221: im ceo too :)
d4rkvist3r: tesla
janpoonthong: Vladimir Hotz lol
Ne0Zer0: lmfaooooooooo
RAMBOxBEAST: Do you enjoy video games? What's the latest game you have played?
mazsociety: have you tried chewing ice?
myaocat: why engineers of big companies doesn't invest 10% of their time to make products for nurses/hospital?
RapidEU: I'm the CEO of my house
veryape69: ^^
her3hero: good game
Jon8RFC: baba is you is a good one...check out filament, too
Denis0109: @georgehotz I like your eyes, can I buy them?
num_air: what programming tools are missing for BACKSPACE to succeed ?
uiq3eu: Is quantum computing gonna change sth?
iilliilliillli: have you tried shungite?
joshperri: I’m the CEO of uranus
codingquark: Yeah that game looks real fun
amuzinc: Im CEO of democratic republic of CEO
SigmaHeavyIndustries: I'm the CEO of the homeless shelter I stay at
RAMBOxBEAST: Cool
bubblesnot: I am the CEO of my buttplug
bananaconda: do you play chess?
JRHonda121: Do you believe Elon when he said they are very close to Level 5?
kingherring: but seriously @georgehotz how do you find time to program as President
eldac_kno: Baba is you turing complete btw
reeldill120: have u ever got laid for hacking the iphone/sony stuff?
codingquark: I am playing TIS-100 these days
ImNotTrolling: jump king
linearpup: Are you at your parents' house?
colanzio5: You should check out this game https://www.mobiusdigitalgames.com/outer-wilds.html
amuzinc: @georgehotz are you friends all CEO's
uiq3eu: Is quantum computing gonna change sth?
RapidEU: Do u play COD?
random11_real: try antichamber
d4rkvist3r: ori an the will of the wisps
random11_real: its a puzzle
Dieun: If anyone wants a super chill game, I'd recommend NightSky on steam
Mussels: have you considered power-lifting to increase T levels and make you a better programmer?
hobocoder: LUL
Roman182: LUL
ZuppaSalata: LUL
her3hero: wait wasnt it an hour before?
leander_ms: LUL
myasovlavashe: LUL
crestedpuffin: LUL
bananaconda: KEKW
drumbledope: KKona
brofessorbob: Have you been to Hong Kong in TJ yet?
pharaohskaro: this is the best thing you've onde yet lol
her3hero: your rate went up
egilsdrups: :D :D :D :D
Ne0Zer0: ez LUL
Arksam: Who's comma ' ?
redemer666: what a scam
feed2: and i got you here for free :)
t3rabyt3_: PrideShine
codingquark: TIS-100 is assembly simulation thing
soreox: only 1k?
knilecrack: real boos
Perrrooooo: LUL
litesam: What's your hiring strategy!
booberrystew: LULW
airinspiration_: what a sam LUL
uiq3eu: Is quantum computing gonna change sth?
bubblesnot: That is hilarious
knilecrack: boss*
egilsdrups: time = money right done
whit_314: Maybe we can all chip in chat to pay for a call
myaocat: @reeldill120 he got a car and money for it. i heard about you in reddit they said you dropped hs and lockpicking :))
phrixus_bro: I can get 10 minutes with Kevin Sorbo for $100
crestedpuffin: nuance1Elon nuance1Elon nuance1Elon nuance1Elon nuance1Elon nuance1Elon nuance1Elon nuance1Elon nuance1Elon
feed2: i dont support amazon that way :)
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: BUT IM HOMELESS
Denis0109: Can I have your mac? Then I can program too!
litesam: What's your hiring Strategy!?
kingherring: kingherring subscribed with Twitch Prime.
xxblueshift: yo i subbed broooooooooooooooooo
rodeocrazy: rodeocrazy subscribed with Twitch Prime.
0xbadidea: what happened to your old twitch channel?
Dieun: Common twitch primes, where ya at???
loopylol: then youll stop streaming till next month lmfao
leander_ms: You have no emotes sir.
bubblesnot: What was the name of that puzzle game?
RapidEU: Do u send Buttplugs to subs?
prostidude221: SUBSCRIBE? HELL NAW TriHard
eldac_kno: money>looks>fame tbh
chillguy269: But you said if it gets too big you kill the stream, so Im not subbing
lef_xyz: @phrixus_bro LUL
iilliilliillli: i have no money bro
yungtoad4: HYPEEEEEE TRAINNNNN
agravkire: Are you going to hack ps5 ? Kappa
ch1ck3n_b0y: FeelsGoodMan
soreox: scam train Pog
pilliam2: more subs = more views = less streams
KryekGG: @elonmusk DONATEEEEEEEEEEE
Curlicue7: @georgehotz Why do you like streaming?
tdubey: sub chat only for 5 dollar convo with the president of comma
bebytesback: This is great!
janpoonthong: i have no money bro
mattdacentaur: hack ps5 and I sub
muffclap: if too many of us subscribe then ur gonna disappear though?
litesam: What's your hiring strategy!?
amuzinc: 1bit too many LUL
kingherring: I SUBSCRIBED
christianthefalco: Has anyone ordered the meeting?
0xbadidea: what happened to your old twitch channel??
teerv: make an hour $ 1.999 deal
Mussels: yeah wait, can the call have 50 people on it? lets go 50 people to chip in $20
JRHonda121: JRHonda121 is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
Perrrooooo: PogChamp
random11_real: im 14 and poor
JRHonda121: JRHonda121 gifted a Tier 1 sub to idlewise!
JRHonda121: JRHonda121's Gift shared rewards to 25 others in Chat!
yungtoad4: SourPls SourPls SourPls SourPls SourPls SourPls
JRHonda121: JRHonda121 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Cydinlol!
JRHonda121: JRHonda121 gifted a Tier 1 sub to 0xreself!
JRHonda121: JRHonda121 gifted a Tier 1 sub to 0wld3v!
JRHonda121: JRHonda121 gifted a Tier 1 sub to 1_7_2_9!
Arksam: monkaS
daxyxy98: are you in contact with suge knight ?
ch1ck3n_b0y: Pog
0xbadidea: Pog
linearpup: How much did you earn this stream?
soreox: dodged PogChamp
janpoonthong: thanks
aensaevhaerne: dodged
b2kemann: gift me a sub
reeldill120: @myaocat wut?
RapidEU: @JRHonda121 notice me
xxblueshift: LUL
iskjmss: do you have a 20-OFF code for the meetings? LUL
iilliilliillli: dodged ez
lef_xyz: haHAA
thecoldwar32: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
vicfred: jimsQueso jimsQueso jimsQueso
bubblesnot: I am chill when i have my buttplug in
litesam: What!?
Kabbone: what happened to the plan getting instagram famous?
her3hero: can we get a train?
0xbadidea: what happened to your old twitch channel??
feed2: wait you still push to master? Kappa
sawamoha20: wow
NotKarar: D:
nevsis: nevsis subscribed with Twitch Prime.
georgehotz: https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
solyyd: thoughts about nietzche?
joshperri: Why do you want subscribers? Can’t be for the money...
zelkh9: chess grind stream when
RapidEU: Do u think your chat will ever turn to a normal Twitch spam chat?
t3rabyt3_: The hype train is pulled into the station. All on board. Choo Choo
knilecrack: you dind't get verified ?
hobocoder: still no checkmark BibleThump
snapcs1: snapcs1 subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 1 month streak!
brofessorbob: Have you been to Hong Kong in TJ yet?
airinspiration_: "sued by sony" LUL LUL
knilecrack: brahhhh
Denis0109: @georgehotz Do you watch porn when you don't program?
bubblesnot: You never post on insta
chillguy269: That's really a thing?
solitaryyy: You live in LA now?
PyotrKropotkin: wow, cool instagram, i hope you become famous someday
yungtoad4: Nice pinecone
eldac_kno: but you said being famous is overrated
kingherring: All clubs are closed @georgehotz
redemer666: I can give you a follow for $10
iilliilliillli: you cant follow if you dont have ig WeSmart
sharknight11: influencer life
foti_kasparov: To the Castle
0xbadidea: yikes
veryape69: what's your iq?
loopylol: trueeeee
Arksam: We not the elite NotLikeThis
lef_xyz: healthy stuff
myaocat: gift me a sub and I'll write you a program or app in c/swift/obj-c/kotlin/rust...
brofessorbob: The elite club is in TJ called Hong Kong
leander_ms: You are not doing very well Sir NotLikeThis
mlejva: Let’s keep this underground my CS fellows
Dieun: @georgehotz Have you tried faceapp on yourself?
amuzinc: @georgehotz elite club with Epstein and weinstein ???
parktype: parktype is gifting 5 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 5 in the channel!
parktype: parktype's Gift shared rewards to 25 others in Chat!
parktype: parktype gifted a Tier 1 sub to Gwas__!
parktype: parktype gifted a Tier 1 sub to dafuqpod!
parktype: parktype gifted a Tier 1 sub to 3aaa7923!
parktype: parktype gifted a Tier 1 sub to 1donald!
parktype: parktype gifted a Tier 1 sub to 32bitrobo!
prostidude221: that shit sounds so fucking toxic
atthem0ment: the middle one is hq
6majed: 6majed subscribed at Tier 1.
arbitrandomuser: how does this work ?
snapcs1: PogChamp
Ne0Zer0: PogChamp
ZuppaSalata: Pog
renerocksai: why not buy followers on insta then?
xxblueshift: @georgehotz can we start a petition to get you verified
soreox: easy dodge 4Head
insignia_microwave: subs comin in
JumpTwiice: Pog subs
myasovlavashe: Pog
RapidEU: Omg wheres my sub!
lef_xyz: fuck em
Perrrooooo: Perrrooooo subscribed at Tier 1.
JumpTwiice: PogChamp didnt get a sub
jgiljr: social media is sucks!!!
airinspiration_: LUL
pioterexe: pog
egilsdrups: :D :D :D :D :D :D :D
bubblesnot: Do you own a Ferrari?
hobocoder: KKona hell yeah
random11_real: i want a sub im 14
NotKarar: LUL
wutango: KKona damn right
qatarking24xd: Kkona damn right
yungtoad4: FeelsAmazingMan
lifeofjona: hi
wazaR: Some people use big butplugs for follows... i mean weird world @georgehotz
crestedpuffin: @georgehotz can we post links?
b2kemann: WORKERS UNITE, FREE SUBS
her3hero: her3hero is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 1 in the channel!
her3hero: her3hero's Gift shared rewards to 5 others in Chat!
her3hero: her3hero gifted a Tier 1 sub to CampingNova!
ch1ck3n_b0y: EZ
yungtoad4: POGGERS
PyotrKropotkin: very levelheaded. glad to help you become famous.
codingquark: I follow you from multiple insta accounts dude
mattdacentaur: 4Head
Perrrooooo: Ez subs
eldac_kno: to be honest good looks has all perks of being famous without any downsides
egilsdrups: WELL SAID !!!!!
nudax: !uptime
arbitrandomuser: what are your thoughts on Communism ?
0xbadidea: @georgehotz whats your favourite twitch streamer?
redemer666: if you tell the truth you get canceled bro
egilsdrups: TRue never misguides """
Denis0109: I told the the TRUTH, but now I'm dead
hobocoder: lol
foti_kasparov: Do you like our respect ?
Arksam: LUL
localcanofdutchgold: he 2 timed your wife
snapcs1: true
feed2: They found out he was not a doctor :)
ZuppaSalata: LUL
NotKarar: FeelsBadMan RIP My doc
arbitrandomuser: did communism get *'d out ?
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: When you first meet with new people do you tell them you are a streamer or the owner of comma ai?
leander_ms: What happend to the Doc for real tho
knilecrack: yeah
GoTo3: when is Shkreli out of prison? @georgehotz
pioterexe: nice
bubblesnot: Tell us the truth then...where is your buttplug right this very moment?
foti_kasparov: For you?
knilecrack: fuck twich
wutango: 2 time 🏆
that_lad_koby: true
CampingNova: Didn't dodge FeelsBadMan
RapidEU: I have a friend who is a multi millionaire, and hes all about playing games all day HAHA
Perrrooooo: Hackthebox when PogChamp
solyyd: i told the truth, got fired three times lmao
crestedpuffin: xD
litesam: PogChamp
guileBR: u cant be smart and good looking at same time Kappa
blabbernab: clout chaser
num_air: I am ugly and stupid :(
kingherring: same, I told the truth and I got fired
her3hero: true
solitarynative: not true
litesam: !uptime
mattdacentaur: not true
airinspiration_: true
redoni18: thoughts on kanye running for president??
KryekGG: Im both
asdhxc: Shkreli is still in jail for another 3 years
myaocat: but if you go to job interview and asked you if you know X and you lie is it bad? im not liar i tell truth but didn't get far
xxblueshift: @georgehotz can we start a petition to get you verified
arbitrandomuser: socialism ?
tdubey: losing weight will get you lots of friends
codingquark: Are there cognitive studies around ethnic groups and their perception of good looking people?
veryape69: >one chance at life
mlejva: If you are a president of people republic democratic country you are respected man
veryape69: >be ugly
her3hero: LULW
Penguino138: Mannn I keep waking up late to attend
RapidEU: He said " I TOOK MILK FROM WORK"
Ne0Zer0: LUL
Dieun: He told his boss about his secret bu... Nevermind.
foti_kasparov: HE TOLD HE HAD CORONA
lef_xyz: people dont really want to hear the truth
Mussels: favorite flavor of gatorade / weather phenomenon? mine is polar vortex and polar vortex
TusKaN_BaNaNas: the way you tell is as important as the truth
myasovlavashe: D:
crestedpuffin: LUL
leander_ms: You tell your Boss he stinks and you get fired that does FeelsBadMan
iilliilliillli: telling the truth is a scam
two_eight: He shared CIA secrets
chillguy269: ROFL
Ne0Zer0: hahaha
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: ahahahaha
RapidEU: or "I use buttplug while at work"
JakeJ24: The truth about thruthology
MrBankster: 250 is healthy for me
airinspiration_: lmao
her3hero: any milkers in chat
Denis0109: Can you have Sex at CommaAI Toilets?
atthem0ment: KEKW
litesam: Let
litesam: My
bubblesnot: I got fired for my buttplug falling out mid meeting
illogicalism: have you considered doing a session with the twitch psychiatrist?
uiq3eu: best tech book?
egilsdrups: :D :D :D :D: DTHAT WERE BREAsT MILK I BET :D :D :D :D
her3hero: got no job, but got milk homie
solitarynative: very sexy pic bottom left
brofessorbob: You haven't lived life if you haven't been to Hong Kong in TJ though.
sharknight11: thoughts on personal knowledge management systems ?
crestedpuffin: Milk Thefts
parktype: Dr K
Ahowe444: Dr. K
Ne0Zer0: Dr. K
MatiGoG: Dr.K
lef_xyz: a new fun projects ?
chillguy269: Dr K.
that_lad_koby: HealthyGamer?
localcanofdutchgold: K dude
christianthefalco: What if the truth is that there is no truth
foti_kasparov: Play Life if Good by Drake
chillguy269: Thats the homie
prostidude221: dr.k is good
lef_xyz: any new fun projects ?
B1_Renekton: Dr. K
leander_ms: Dr K
redemer666: Dr K is the man bro
corona_virus_spreader: Hey George how are you dealing with covid, has it affected you mentally?
booberrystew: Dr. K
yungtoad4: YESSS WE WANT HEALTHYGAMER STREAM
veryape69: StoneLightning StoneLightning
TheCellarDoor: Dr K is badass
prostidude221: TALK TO DR. K PogChamp
crestedpuffin: https://www.twitch.tv/healthygamer_gg
ActForImpact: yeah dude go talk to him
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: Yes go Dr K.
myaocat: (not commaAI comment) but you read it. Kappa
bubblesnot: When will you release buttplug.ai?
tugendhat: hes streaming RIGHT now
parktype: He's not hateful at all
redemer666: dr K is brown Jesus
Solias_3: dr K PogChamp
prostidude221: tTALK TO DR. K PogChamp
Ne0Zer0: nah so=uper wholesome
parktype: Just went live
TheCellarDoor: Dr K is wholesome
lef_xyz: he is really nice
her3hero: U can have a session with dr. k. he is chill
wutango: harvard andy
6majed: Yeah did he....
SurfCat: Oh lol if you would talk to him would be hilarious LUL
soreox: No it ain't hateful at all
yungtoad4: That shit would be insane
janpoonthong: Dr K is wholesome
NotKarar: FeelsBadMan reckful <3
chillguy269: Stream might get too big if he talks to him
kingherring: @georgehotz any thoughts on Max Stirner's egoism? You seem like a rational egoism type of guy
that_lad_koby: Love him
ch1ck3n_b0y: Wow
GiantSweater: reckful FeelsBadMan
Solias_3: it's the opposite of hateful
parktype: he just went live on twitch.tv/healthygamer_gg
Penguino138: How to convince someone who believes 0 scientific evidence and studies?
prostidude221: TALK TO DR. K PogChamp
0xbadidea: @georgehotz whats your screen resolution?
AwaisDota: Kappa
Ahowe444: LOL cringe
MrYasser2194: this screams "look at me im damaged pitty me"
brofessorbob: Who is this cuck
eldac_kno: Lol
ch1ck3n_b0y: talk to Dr. K
solitarynative: lmao
christianthefalco: Ewww
Arksam: cmonBruh
wazaR: Dr.K needs a buttplug... fuck it @georgehotz
SigmaHeavyIndustries: wow this is not a christian channel
janpoonthong: Dr K is wholesome
bubblesnot: White knight found
airinspiration_: cringe KEKW
codingquark: cheesy?
lef_xyz: you should go talk with destiny
SigmaHeavyIndustries: swearing
TomatoePasta: thats a bad clip @georgehotz
Madill_: Do you believe that humans are deterministic?
yungtoad4: No thats out of the norm
janpoonthong: LOL cringe
JumpTwiice: he talks personal problems with streamers
pigporkman: What do you think about michael reeves?
yungtoad4: Hes not cringe
soreox: That was a bad clip I do agree
localcanofdutchgold: DESTINY OMEGALUL
phrixus_bro: hes the new oprah
two_eight: so cringe bro 😂😂
Penguino138: Christian Channel everyone get your golden crosses out
walz_: toxic??!?
GiantSweater: LUL
veryape69: do you still listen to lil peep?
walz_: lmao
JumpTwiice: how is it toxic LUL
corona_virus_spreader: George how are you dealing with covid, has it affected you mentally?
litesam: pogchamp
redemer666: Dr K is like Jesus
cortickal: Destiny is cringe. Dr K is cringe.
janpoonthong: so cringe bro 😂😂
paradox109: hasan
leander_ms: Wow there are books in the background does that mean you read boi?
foti_kasparov: Have you listened MGK EMO?
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: How often do you pray to god?
christianthefalco: Doctor drew for people with gamer chairs
litesam: PogChamp
gcbourdon: Play league
GiantSweater: Hes not that toxic
eldac_kno: twitch now has its own televangelists
localcanofdutchgold: destiny cucks lul
linearpup: Why are you in New Jersey?
feed2: Life is cringe :)
RAMBOxBEAST: RAMBOxBEAST subscribed at Tier 1.
3ygun: He's not toxic nathanGod1 nathanGod2
litesam: Poggers PogChamp
Mussels: destiny is the geohot of philosophy only he's wrong and youre right
MatiGoG: hasan streams politics topics
yungtoad4: Uppercase C covid
dejvid1998: lmao autistic chat calling people cringe for helping other people
lef_xyz: any new fun projects ?
SurfCat: moon2MORMOON wholesome channel Keepo
B1_Renekton: micheal reeves codes with 15k viewer on twitch
xxblueshift: @georgehotz yo bro play fortnite xDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDDD
yungtoad4: Dr k is a woke bae
ego_naut: destiny white knights LUL
bubblesnot: When will you release buttplug.ai?
kingherring: What is your thought on rational egoism?
leuza0: Look for michael reeves channel on youtube, its great
TomatoePasta: haHAA SAN
snapcs1: Choo Chooo HypeDaze
parktype: Choo Chooo HypeDaze
JRHonda121: Choo Chooo HypeBounce
prostidude221: Dr. k is actually doing alot of good on the platform, he's pretty chill
6majed: Choo Chooo HypeDaze
litesam: Wanna see cool! Text art
two_eight: TRUE
codingquark: YES
MrYasser2194: @dejvid1998 on stream for views ? fuck'em
TheCellarDoor: true
solitarynative: real
CommanderZilyana: true
t3rabyt3_: Choo Chooo PrideWorld
kingherring: HypeDaze
B1_Renekton: true
foti_kasparov: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BCsM35H9TFA Watch this about Self Hel books
janpoonthong: true
sharknight11: have u tried roam research?
PyotrKropotkin: if you want a book that's going to improve your life, go watch a movie
parktype: Feel good books PogChamp
guileBR: why read books if u can read PDFs?
3ygun: True
6majed: Got scammed Choo Choo
feed2: Self help the author Kappa
mudkipzzzz: so how do you get better then?
eldac_kno: feels good man
mmi18: reading makes me feel bad
kavifa6176: self help olny help the author get rich and upsell their next product
localcanofdutchgold: self help is decent when you're like 18, read one and move on
jgiljr: would you go to the moon if elon hooked it up?
Arksam: DendiFace FeelsGoodMan But books
soreox: They feel good in the sellers pocket LUIL
Denis0109: how to stay motivated in this Cruel World?
parktype: @6majed lmfao
codingquark: Do you consider The Alchemist a self help book?
linearpup: Watch some David Goggins videos
litesam: Yo do HackerRank and shit!
B1_Renekton: LAW OF ATTRACTION LULW
lew_kas: xtheAutoW
leander_ms: But then the people would realize they do not improve their lives and then they do not feel good my man
dejvid1998: @MrYasser2194 He's profiting thats for sure, and I dont like it either. But if it helps people I dont mind
MrBankster: do you think we're heading for an economic depression?
prostidude221: Have you heard about HasanAbi? @georgehotz
prostidude221: LUL
phrixus_bro: whats the best indian food to order
davidnsun: will VODs ever be made public?
foti_kasparov: Have you seen the Self-Help Books - George Carlin video?
leuza0: btw I think michael reeves follows you on instagram @georgehotz
yungtoad4: Best self help book is lost in the cosmos by walker percy. Author says the only way to cure depression is to seriously consider suicide.
codingquark: LIke by design toxic?
sharknight11: social media + quarantine seems disastrous
3ygun: @prostidude221 LUL
feed2: TRUE
mmi18: i like watching tony robison on youtube makes me feel good
AlfaAnanasz: BITCOIN PogChamp BITCOIN PogChamp BITCOIN PogChamp BITCOIN PogChamp BITCOIN PogChamp BITCOIN PogChamp
cortickal: In the future, PhDs will write dissertations on the philosophy of Destiny
kingherring: @georgehotz have you heard of fair code ? alternative to open source. faircode.io
iReaper147: LuL
Poisonslash: @yungtoad4 LUL wut?
eldac_kno: what do you think about tik tok being chinese spyware
Penguino138: Geo have you seen the new DOG E coin meme?
bubblesnot: Rothschild
jotembruv: like reeeeeeeallly long term
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @georgehotz do you agree with this? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4hR4rDbJPM4
UrosRiznic: Choda jel gledas ?
lef_xyz: its about managing
veryape69: thoughts on nihilism
pilliam2: bullish on crypto longterm? what does he mean
codingquark: Ah, https://scuttlebutt.nz/
Poisonslash: You can't just randomly 'cure' real depression.
soreox: gl curing depression
GabrielHa: depression != depressed
codingquark: Alternate internet: https://scuttlebutt.nz/
Koduck007: the emotion but not the illness
feed2: we need crypto that doesnt benefit the first movers too much
sharknight11: tbh would want a therapist to take me to the extremes
Perrrooooo: LUL you sounded like Michael Scott there
jotembruv: @pilliam2 thinks it will be in a better place in the future
wazaR: everything should be legal, if you die, its your problem... i mean @georgehotz
leander_ms: @fdfdfdfdfdfdff I agree with that one
corona_virus_spreader: Your refreshing attitude towards mental health makes me feel hopeful
pilliam2: @jotembruv thanks
Landepbs: What are your general thoughts on caompanies advertising nowadays?
codingquark: https://scuttlebutt.nz/
sharknight11: massive increase in antidepressants
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @georgehotz do you agree with this? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4hR4rDbJPM4
bubblesnot: Why are you attacking cocaine man?
veryape69: your thoughts on nihilism?
mmi18: but how can something that makes you feel good be bad for you
codingquark: https://scuttlebutt.nz/ is blockchain based social network
ego_naut: drug addictions help my drug tolerance
janpoonthong: why dont you marry?
christianthefalco: Wellbutrin is a good drug for me
0xbadidea: @georgehotz what happened to your tomcr00se channel? still active?
MrYasser2194: @dejvid1998 profiting for a therapy session is fine, he just said a round of a applause. it's a performance.
brofessorbob: Coked up girls though....
wingdini: what's your favorite strain?
foti_kasparov: is nihilists and anitnatalists existence absurd?
prostidude221: @georgehotz i think you would love HasabAbi's view points pepeLaugh
Penguino138: Weird deja vu we talked about this cocaine thing before?
two_eight: “I would feel real trapped in this life if I didn't know I could commit suicide at any time.” ― Hunter S. Thompson
jotembruv: @0xbadidea this is it just namechange i think
JumpTwiice: drugs are a cancer
PhosphoricAcid: @georgehotz thoughts on chain link ?
hobocoder: OpieOP
uiq3eu: We need simulator for biotech!
corbold: Are you back in the room where you recorded the sony rap?
codingquark: https://scuttlebutt.nz/ is blockchain based social network
Denis0109: You don't need friends to be Happy!
ConfuciusIvan: SSRIs made me feel like i was getting better but then i couldn't cum
tastedpuma581: do yo have scheduled streams?
eldac_kno: scarface was pretty fun movie tbh
christianthefalco: Anti what?
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: BUt you will be able to do cocked up streams!
duncansclarke: cocaine is also a shit high and doesn't last
Penguino138: Gonezo
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: @georgehotz please watch this on stream re: crypto https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4hR4rDbJPM4
cortickal: Shill URBIT, @georgehotz
0xbadidea: @jotembruv monkaHmm
kingherring: +1 for coked up george hotz stream
sanneck: the best book behind you?
MrYasser2194: life's kill button, a trigger
foti_kasparov: LUL
prostidude221: its a good 30mins though
bubblesnot: Suicide is selfish
lef_xyz: what is with this chat and drugs
brofessorbob: Do you mountain bike? We got great trails near Balboa Park
dejvid1998: Papa George, do you ever get off ampethamines?
echotaco: Just stream enough to get partner and that better sub split ratio with twitch ;)
sharknight11: do u believe in tech determinism?
Penguino138: Read any good books lately?
astrocraft23: hi
yungtoad4: Ill gift 50 subs for coked up geo stream
duncansclarke: @bubblesnot bad take
solitarynative: is smart contract dev a good idea
zelkh9: thoughts on glizzys?
leander_ms: I agree man you gotta do 1 stream on coicaine tho
MrYasser2194: well thats a giff
Jon8RFC: haha, not selfish
foti_kasparov: I think the crypto video the guy posted is worth it
tastedpuma581: do you smoke pod?
sanneck: the best book behind you?
Denis0109: NSA Secretly owns DarkNet
MrBankster: would you recommend adderrall to improve productivity in programming?
crestedpuffin: xD
codingquark: https://scuttlebutt.nz/ is blockchain based social network (last time won't paste again I promise)
mikey9988: Kappa
NotKarar: Kappa
pilliam2: Dr K is live
GiantSweater: Kappa
klaazdw: weed
localcanofdutchgold: @bubblesnot it's selfish for others to call it selfish
prostidude221: Mdma?
Joooooooooonas: becareful cause of TOS
musabkilic0: yo im back how is going guys and what is he doing rn
tastedpuma581: sorry I meant pot
myaocat: do you think Fuschia will be better than iOS?
solyyd: what are you working on these days?
lef_xyz: overconfidence
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: Psychedelics ?? Psychedelics ??
christianthefalco: Wait why dont you like wellbutrin? Curious cuz I like it
AlfaAnanasz: @georgehotz any experience with LSD?
duncansclarke: works as well as placebo in terms of confidence
Mussels: the only "cure" for "clinical depression" is to eat properly, wake up when the sun comes up, and lift heavy weights. It's also the cure for "ADD"
wazaR: suicide for tha virgins, good trade....
TusKaN_BaNaNas: @MrBankster nah just caffeine and nicotine
Zeldorino: Bad at life FeelsBadMan
brofessorbob: What about Provigil though
codingquark: Nice
feed2: Good idea
undefined_kek: Hi
yungtoad4: Abacus.ai???
ego_naut: fascinating
Shubsterz: who can get in
solitaryyy: "Truth"
parktype: wouldn't that be becoming what you hate?? @georgehotz
PhosphoricAcid: we cult now PogChamp
adibaby04: acceptance rate?
ProfessorMagikarp0: George Academy like Khan Academy KEKW
kavifa6176: What classes would you have at that college
kingherring: @georgehotz microdoses , he has no need for stimulants
crestedpuffin: SeemsGood
Aenopixel: Modafinil is safer, been using it low doses every day, working out good
tastedpuma581: What about API's
MrYasser2194: u gonna be teaching ?
pigporkman: What do you think about affirmative action?
veryape69: what is it like to eat ass
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: @AlfaAnanasz He said he has done it on previous streams
musabkilic0: the title is still coronavirus btw @georgehotz
ConfuciusIvan: Nah I took Concerta and I did SO much better at work
prostidude221: @adibaby04 100% if you pay 1000 dollarsa
bubblesnot: How can AI positively impact cyber security today?
foti_kasparov: Education is power
ego_naut: any thoughts on phenibut ?
ornis1: Кодзима Гений
lef_xyz: yes
AlfaAnanasz: @alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx yea but did he say how was it?
duncansclarke: @veryape69 tastes sour but feels good if youre horny
Hawklite: that's what Scientology is Kappa
leander_ms: Yes it does
MrYasser2194: sign me up
weeva: you will be labeled a cult at the very least
joshperri: This is the new college
wazaR: just do krokodil, fuck it
NotKarar: placebo PogChamp
JeanFrag: how would you maintain your goal of the college after your death? @georgehotz
yungtoad4: Cultism is not in what you believe but the ways you choose to follow those blieefs
eldac_kno: mathematics were cult in ancient greece
veryape69: @duncansclarke thanks ^^
tastedpuma581: What about Mexicans?
duncansclarke: lol
ch1ck3n_b0y: Русские хакеры на месте?
localcanofdutchgold: ai
sharknight11: as a temporary solution, isnt believing you did better not a bad thing ?
foti_kasparov: stop ruski
davidbarreroo: He is not going to die
Denis0109: Scientology is full of ALIENS
TusKaN_BaNaNas: gotta fix that problem by fixing death
eldac_kno: на месте
codingquark: Philosophy indeed
yungtoad4: Hes not gunna die
MrBankster: i can live where i want for the next 6 months to a year. where should I go? I want to go somewhere warm and cheap by the beach
JRHonda121: Do you believe Elon when he said they are very close to Level 5?
yungtoad4: He said that earlier
ego_naut: pythagoras was a cult leader
MrYasser2194: AI dude
cortickal: Yudkowsky is a cult leader
adibaby04: but ignorance is bliss.
Repunk: would you cryo-freeze your body if/when you die?
crestedpuffin: Make an AI overlord to rule the college with an Iron Fist
Dieun: Have you read Ayn Rand?
solyyd: next big project?
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: Whats your favorite designer brand? I've only ever seen your Saint Laurent hoodie
linearpup: Any good technical book suggestions?
soiax_: so why dont you believe in longevity then?
Markidane: Is there an objective truth?
JRHonda121: LUL
Raiwo: monkaS
lef_xyz: but you want to live for ever
Penguino138: People used to wear less cloths in ancient times and throughout history religion has taken it backwards Kreygasm
codingquark: :D
prostidude221: you think its possible to reverse effects of aging ?
yungtoad4: Do you hate noam chomsky
jotembruv: living forever is a fools errand
davidbarreroo: Any thoughts about Ai for trading ?
leander_ms: @georgehotz when you are dead just import heartbeat again, that is the answer
PhosphoricAcid: we don't talk about fight club
myaocat: why we have social media and everything but still everyone for him self?
venkateshtata: Did you watch westworld ?
PyotrKropotkin: lmao
SnakeAz: faith, is more effective than we thought.
ConfuciusIvan: Well I accept the placebo effect as a truth. But I wouldn't have gotten promoted without it
alrealre: @georgehotz do you follow any longevity regime like Jack Dorsey doing 24 hours fast ?
kavifa6176: Truth is fluid, it changes over time
whit_314: Maybe ray kurzweil is correct and we are close to escape velocity for aging and death.
pilliam2: what book did he say?
kingherring: @georgehotz thoughts on anarcho-capitalism?
lef_xyz: do u think elon is cringe (i do)
codegito: when do you think the singularity will happen?
christianthefalco: Talk about Joscha Bach
foti_kasparov: Would you prefer to live for 1 day in the past or the future?
myaocat: @pilliam2 sandstorm by Edi Schmidt
davidbarreroo: Any thoughts about Ai for trading ?
codingquark: @pilliam2 the fountainhead and atlas shurgged
venkateshtata: Did you watch westworld ?
eldac_kno: thoughts on unreal engine 5 demo? what did you think about nanite? turns out it doesn't work with foliage and skinned meshes
ego_naut: my take on ayn rand = capitalist's manifesto
leander_ms: @lef_xyz how dare you
mmi18: how do i make learning fun?
Denis0109: Do you believe the good in People?
duncansclarke: Chomsky's work in linguistics is also fantastic
yungtoad4: Is elon a megachurch pastor for atheists!
ThePepe3012: Do you think Bezos is cringe?
yeah_haey: Do you think that orgasm makes men weaker
inDOObitablee: Would you have voted for Kanye?
feed2: past is better
pigporkman: What do you think about the discrepancy between the stock market and the economy?
littlebighead82: CmonBruh
feed2: Kappa
leander_ms: @ThePepe3012 we dont like Bezos round here
PresBObama: get those lottery numbers real quick
MrBankster: haven't you guys seen back to the future
snowbola: What would u do if u were magically transported to a third-world country without any money
localcanofdutchgold: will we change the national anthem once kanye becomes president
Tekrific: ayn rand died while on welfare checks. The irony
whit_314: I'd love to be frozen and wake up in a 100 years just to see how things are
lesserthangood: KEKW
aurumvorax421: live one day in the future and look all he stock prices
AlfaAnanasz: @georgehotz were your experiences with LSD positive?
MrYasser2194: spoilers man u don't want that
mlejva: I took tramadol (opioid) and it helps me concentrate when coding a lot and not worry about other stuff. This way I am able to do much better work
venkateshtata: Did you watch westworld ?
bubblesnot: How can AI affect cyber security today?
GiantSweater: lol
Curlicue7: What do you like about streaming @georgehotz
foti_kasparov: Let's put this too. Would you like to get back ?
brofessorbob: I'm writing you in on my vote
volkerai: do you support Trump or Biden?
Jon8RFC: kanye? kan-nay
her3hero: would you be able to build computers, if you would time travel 100 years back?
cortickal: Noam Chomsky is a manufacturer of consent
Denis0109: Im Voting for George next President. Make America Smart Again!"
ego_naut: any thoughts on phenibut?
uiq3eu: Any interesting tech on the horizont?
codingquark: You can meditate to achieve such a state
mudkipzzzz: @georgehotz how do i get better at life?
eldac_kno: thoughts on unreal engine 5 demo? what did you think about nanite? turns out it doesn't work with foliage and skinned meshes
hackyhacks: Shouldn't you tell the truth coming out of that booth?
taylor4432: suicide is a permenent solution to a tamporary problem.
yungtoad4: elon is a megachurch pastor for atheists
pigporkman: Would you ever be interested in a position in politics?
TusKaN_BaNaNas: @cortickal manufacturing consent to what?
Curlicue7: what do you like about streaming
hobocoder: monkaS
K177: OMEGALUL
lef_xyz: @yungtoad4 I really liked that tweet
rustduck: monkaS what
wutango: monkaS
fdfdfdfdfdfdff: queue the DFW quote in Infinite Jest about suicide
Joooooooooonas: @georgehotz MonkaTOS
GiantSweater: monkaS
Raiwo: monkaS
ch1ck3n_b0y: monkaS
ego_naut: google blacklisted
poopboy7: wtf
Raiwo: monkaS wtf dont
atthem0ment: monkaS
yungtoad4: Woah man you are streaming
Zeldorino: could i commit suicide? probably not Kappa
JumpTwiice: this chat is talking about depression and suicide is something you can just "get over"
poopboy7: dude
PiecesOW: Dont monkaS
veryape69: everybody's gotta die some time
weeva: knock on the door in 10 mins LUL
foon123456: monkaS
leander_ms: monkaS Google does not let you do it
two_eight: Use another search engine. Google is cucked
illogicalism: wow your ip will be flagged
hobocoder: george stop NotLikeThis
ProfessorMagikarp0: monkTOS?
insignia_microwave: use duckduckgo
Cuke: lol that fucking number at the top
kavifa6176: thats the magic of seo ;)
god_damn: nooo dont kill yourself just call the hotline noooo
ego_naut: duckduckgo?
NotKarar: Try bing FeelsBadMan
6majed: Google filters shit now
GiantSweater: squad
Michaeltth: google manipu
codingquark: They've intentionally fucked the results up. LIke a propaganda
lesserthangood: use bing bro
FruitellaJesus: How do you know so much about drugs?
her3hero: monkaS
PresBObama: pros and cons
Zeldorino: duckduckgo
taylor4432: he is actuaay using Googl
alrealre: google is a cringe factory
leander_ms: @NotKarar Bing teills you how to do it LUL
eldac_kno: it Lost all Hope?
Solias_3: monkaW
ch1ck3n_b0y: D:
yungtoad4: FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan FeelsBadMan
loopylol: i remember this wtf
NotKarar: FeelsBadMan <3
davidbarreroo: linkk
foti_kasparov: link please?
ego_naut: subhuman?
AlfaAnanasz: link?
xxblueshift: link
leander_ms: Link it in here, sounds interesting
PiecesOW: can you link in chat? @georgehotz
BurntOut157: metanoia dot org /suicide/
BurntOut157: without spaces
lef_xyz: https://metanoia.org/suicide/
ThePepe3012: You're awesome George
eldac_kno: thoughts on unreal engine 5 demo? what did you think about nanite? turns out it doesn't work with foliage and skinned meshes
AlfaAnanasz: http://metanoia.org/suicide/
veryape69: https://lostallhope.com
bubblesnot: DONT DO IT GEORGIE
yungtoad4: Thoughts on shungite??
hjklhjklhjkl2008: ur still streaming wot?
cortickal: Wow so deep...
Raiwo: 5Head ahh yeah
atthem0ment: u dont feel anymore
codingquark: Wouldn't the state of no feelings be a great state to be in? True freedom?
prostidude221: why do you know so much about drugs
myaocat: can you stop answering stupid questions? why doesn't FAANG modeling human body and producing vaccines for all the diseases in the world?
SnakeAz: pain is a feel too.
asdhxc: ???????????
K177: wat
loopylol: taylor96Woodygoodpoint
Cuke: well said
FusRoDead: Well, isn't relief just not feeling the current pain?
dontcrysomuch21: what do you think of quantum computers?
linearpup: PCA or t-SNE?
solyyd: tell us the google / project zero story plz :D
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: Relief is the absence of pain though , so you do feel it
JumpTwiice: what?
NotKarar: I don't know
leander_ms: That is some statement
Ahowe444: t-SNE!
foti_kasparov: What do you mean by consider?
tastedpuma581: What have you been doing last days?
solitarynative: so what do you think of niim
ego_naut: that makes me an intellectual?
b1nk: umap
2sin54: PCA and t-SNE do very different things lol
PeinlicherAffe: @linearpup PCA
lef_xyz: dogshit
l_mbert: I was thinking about building a Captcha using the Heartbeat. You would put the Finger over your Cam and it would check like this if you are a Human. Do you think People would use something like this? :)
mmi18: we live for teh feels
random11_real: thanks
venkateshtata: Thoughts on westworld ?
GiantSweater: nymn Pog ?
prostidude221: NymN?
lef_xyz: inm
mlejva: Could you share that reddit opioid epidemic post you mentioned?
TomatoePasta: SoyBoy
lef_xyz: nim
pigporkman: What do you think about the urbit system in general? (Not just hoon)
bubblesnot: Consider like throwing in one .45 and spinning the cyclinder for a one shot Ricky?
b2kemann: would the world be better with more haskell?
rustduck: what about Zig
JumpTwiice: oh boy
sad_ost: notice me senpai owo uwu o3o
prostidude221: PogU NymN?
veryape69: have you ever simped?
sad_ost: do i have to sub to get noticed
eldac_kno: thoughts on data oriented programming?
newuser8000: i have a 85 iq and i cannot understand this stream, its look like magic
neilsweb: Life Pro Tip: Before you commit suicide rub one off. Post rub clarity is effective.
Muzyd: That went from suicide talk to NIM real quick
kavifa6176: its called cython
codingquark: guys suggest me a good laptop for dev
christianthefalco: Thoughts on Jonathan Blow?
arbitrandomuser: @mlejva i think its about the guy who tried it once and got hooked on it within a week
2sin54: LUL ⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀⠀ You are now permanently banned.
leander_ms: it does exist, its Python 1.8 dude
linearpup: @2sin54 both can be used for reducing dimensions
veryape69: post nut clarity saves lives
TomatoePasta: LULW
jotembruv: you do it
pigporkman: Cython?
myaocat: Can you write a program that convert python to assembly?
Zanfr1980: use numba bro
insignia_microwave: why am I banned
B1_Renekton: its called c++
lef_xyz: fast for what
marschr: thoughts on Jonathan Blow?
bubblesnot: How would you make python fast?
illogicalism: CYTHON
arbitrandomuser: its called PYPY
PyotrKropotkin: julia?
jamieemb_: wait why did i get banned?
blabbernab: urbit thoughts?
pigporkman: Jython lol
kavifa6176: maybe rust?
MoProject: c++thon =)
arbitrandomuser: RPYTHON
illogicalism: JYTHON*
solyyd: google / project zero story ?
UnevenSquare: I thought Julia was the fast python
bebytesback: What about Rust?
myaocat: convert python to assembly
l_mbert: I was thinking about building a Captcha using the Heartbeat. You would put the Finger over your Cam and it would check like this if you are a Human. Do you think People would use something like this? :)
codingquark: People are trying to rewrite emacs in Rust
marcosbrolkin: julia
newuser8000: cplusplus is slow?
tastedpuma581: wha about multiproccesing task
myaocat: convert python to llvm
Joooooooooonas: Somebody trolled guys.....
beginbot: 49 raiders from beginbot have joined!
solyyd: thoughts on Scala ?
iskjmss: julia takes forever to run LUL
bebytesback: I wrote a Blas impl in Rust
adibaby04: just use go
pigporkman: Golang?
marschr: Blow had a nice speech on education + programming few days ago
alrealre: What do you think of Fortnite ?
bubblesnot: Python can be used faster when you have a buttplug in
codingquark: lol, seriously though
mikey9988: Java LUL
sad_ost: hihihihihi
Jon8RFC: have you talked with John Carmack before?
eldac_kno: did Jonathan Blow tried to convert you into his cult of writing new game engine?
Tekrific: golang is traash
lef_xyz: people learn rust just to prove that they are better than their coworkers
iskjmss: <3
MoProject: facebook hack language
Perrrooooo: nooooo
ego_naut: <3
BaloSaar: thoughts on Destiny the streamer?
AdamIsSoPro: yeeet
Denis0109: Love you have a good Time baby
Dieun: HeyGuys
xxblueshift: LUL
linearpup: https://github.com/larryhastings/gilectomy
codingquark: https://github.com/remacs/remacs
marschr: thanks bro
Digital_donger: $1k meeting B)
that_lad_koby: Thank you for the stream
wutango: easy 1k
Penguino138: Oh shiiiiiit
myasovlavashe: <3 <3 <3
OddClone: <3
AdamIsSoPro: whats the phonecall for?
bebytesback: Planing to improve it with Apple silicon.
xxblueshift: ez 1k gg
B1_Renekton: <3
flmat: !uptime
foon123456: <3
that_lad_koby: <3 <3 <3
Penguino138: time to rewatch the stream
leander_ms: Is that me calling LUL <3
6majed: EZ Clap
parktype: <3
lef_xyz: smart enough LUL
foon123456: <3 󠀀
amuzinc: LUL
TomatoePasta: LUL
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8 /
RAMBOxBEAST: Take care and have a nice day
yungtoad4: does the 1k meeting go into your pocket or the companies???
xxblueshift: <3 <3 <3 <3 <3
parktype: <3 <3
Perrrooooo: <34
davidnsun: <3
Perrrooooo: <3
hobocoder: peace george <3
0xbadidea: <3
veryape69: have you ever simped?
rustduck: no one is smart enough for c++
foon123456: LUL
2sin54: cya
Inexpensiive: <3
unluckychickenn: squadL
Digital_donger: Kappa
sinisa_koscec: <3
god_damn: ☎️ B) 🤙 That'll be $1k
amuzinc: im smart as C++
bubblesnot: Put on a 30min timer and hang up right on 30min mark!
SnakeAz: thx
ego_naut: <3 <3
Penguino138: will always sub
booberrystew: <3
BurntOut157: I <3 you George, thanks for your insights
NotKarar: <3 nymnL
presidentjrduppd: bye <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3 <3
bebytesback: Thats why you would use rust.
Ne0Zer0: o/
qatarking24xd: <3
sebtwitch2015: Hi, are you the apple jailbreak genius ?
Denis0109: Can I trust you?
pilliam2: thoughts on java?
linearpup: SHOW THE STREAM EARNINGS :P
punpunho123: bye bye <3
codingquark: See you later man!
Penguino138: dotsHappy
bebytesback: Thanks!
myaocat: TearGlove bye
codingquark: This was fun
thodeannn: raid someone
jamieemb_: @georgehotz read mindset by carol dweck
iotku: guilty
veryape69: see ya
Denis0109: Use Archlinux again plss
Goulfred: bye man enjoyed the live
MrBankster: so one hour?
codingquark: Except we took a simple algo to implement
WillGreen98: Hello There
yungtoad4: RAAAid
mikey9988: LUL
2sin54: TRUE LULW
Perrrooooo: <3
dontcrysomuch21: very nice stream
PhosphoricAcid: LUL
lef_xyz: bye dude
feed2: bye
yungtoad4: RAIIIIID
that_lad_koby: bye
weeva: LUL
hjklhjklhjkl2008: D OMEGALUL C
B1_Renekton: bye
qatarking24xd: bye <3
ch1ck3n_b0y: bye
localcanofdutchgold: THE SHUNGITE
wutango: the 5g got him
K177: lata
6majed: c ya
codingquark: Bye
d4rkvist3r: come one elon
RapidEU: bye my friend
god_damn: bye man
NotKarar: primeagenRust
LeeFranser: bye
jule4n: bye love you
TheCellarDoor: bye bye
lef_xyz: shike
alexxxxxxxxxxxxxxx: baaaa baai
gigafact: thank you
leander_ms: Bye
localcanofdutchgold: byte
Digital_donger: :) /
adam_xxd: bye
insignia_microwave: see ya
brattstm: Bye
mlejva: Have a great day! Enjoy life! Explore stuff!
veryape69: have a nice day
prafaeltsantos: <3
myaocat: dont go omg
phsverdadeiros: tanks
THE_korbi: lol just came
NotKarar: Good night forsenE
0xbadidea: grubD
Poisonslash: Thanks for the chill stream @georgehotz
xxblueshift: bye man
THE_korbi: bye
awesomeo113: Love you